Chapter 1061: I’m Back

"The income situation? I'm not sure." Tang Rou didn't show any sort of confusion, merely saying this calmly.

The reporters took a moment to react. This answer really wasn't what they were expecting. They might have asked such a question, but this was just to set up the following discussion. The income of a pro player was something that any normal Internet cafe player would drool over for half a day. Yet Tang Rou had replied with "not sure". This sort of answer was setting things up in the wrong direction!

Some veterans who heard this response from Tang Rou all sent meaningful stares at Chen Guo. They thought that this was a plot by the Happy boss, to keep the players ignorant and naive so that they were easier to control. But unfortunately, when they went to scrutinized Chen Guo, they found that she didn't seem at all unsettled or nervous at Tang Rou's answer, and instead smiled happily and that was the extent of her reaction.

What was going on?

Now the reporters were confused. Never mind pro players, no matter what job, who would go in completely blind to the income situation? Was this pretty lady messing with them on purpose?

The reporters looked around doubtfully until the press officer asked to rush them again, "Are there anymore questions?"

All these hold ups in the press conference today was causing him to get a little impatient.

"Could you guys leak a little information on the treatment Team Happy's players are getting right now?" The reporters kept at it, but they no longer focused on Tang Rou, throwing the question at Chen Guo instead.

The reporters did have a rather keen judgement. This question striked at Happy's heart. Chen Guo answered a little stutteringly, "In the Challenger League, we all gathered out of our love for Glory. Now that we're going to be a pro team, we're going to begin discussing the contracts in detail. We have yet to start, so there's nothing to leak, yet."

The reporters were thunderstruck.

If this was a tourist team that a few players created just to have fun, then this sort of circumstance would be definite. However, Team happy was the winner of the Challenger League who defeated Excellent Era and had God Ye Xiu. Chen Guo seemed to be saying, that with their lineup and circumstance, they didn't seem to have any sort of income; it was all out of joy.

"So what you mean to say is that, until now, Team Happy's players aren't earning an income?" Someone finally asked carefully.

Chen Guo felt a little awkward, but she wasn't the kind of person to hide things and would never tell a blatant lie in such a situation. She could only nod and say, "Yes."

A cacophony rose from the crowd at once and someone immediately pursued the issue. "Even God Ye Xiu?"

"Um… yeah." Chen Guo hesitated for a moment. It was probably better to not talk about the income he gained as an employee of the Internet cafe...

Nothing needed to be mentioned about the chaos that erupted then. Happy's situation was truly too shocking. Even disregarding the no income thing, Chen Guo's words suggested that they had yet to talk about contracts. That was something they definitely had to report on.

You had to keep in mind that they already had the qualifications to attend the Pro League next season and everyone was about to become real pro players. Were they waiting to have a big sale of players upon entering the Alliance or something, still not ready with the contracts to ensure the players stayed? With the performance Happy's players had in the Challenger League, the reporters knew that a lot of pro teams would show interest. Hadn't a lot of gossip come out when the Challenger League?

Speaking of, there were teams who were interested in Happy's players even back then, but now, Happy's lineup was still whole and none of them had been moved by what the other teams said. Yet, from what the boss had said, there had been no incentive given for the players to stay. Happy's players formed a team and stayed true to it of their own volition?

That was unscientific...

　

The other teams probably knew how strangely Team Happy operated and therefore didn't make any moves on their players. If this information was released… Team Happy wouldn't be immediately dismantled, would it?

The reporters even started worrying for Happy about this. However, they knew that this would most certainly get out. There were so many reporters here and they couldn't be certain that everyone was willing to keep this information to themselves, so the thought of helping them hide this information out of sympathy was childish and illogical. Someone was probably already organizing this information into a draft to publish.

Overall, Happy really was a new experience for the media! They actually leaked something so important in a press conference. The reporters lamented over this, gradually having the suspicion that Happy was acting nonchalant after gaining something big.

The conference was a little chaotic and, looking at the time, the Alliance press officer realized it was late, deciding to announce that the next question was going to be the last one after discussing with Happy.

The reporters had gotten a lot of information from today's press conference. They couldn't pry too much for the last question so any experienced reporter wouldn't ask anything too complicated. There was little point in ending this on low-spirits.

"After being apart from the Alliance for so long, is there anything you want to say right now?" The last question was still directed at Ye Xiu.

"Hahaha." Ye Xiu chuckled and then said, "I'm back."

I'm back!

This simple sentence displayed immense determination. Although a surplus of interesting information had been dug up in the press conference and even though everyone had started drafting out their articles on this information during the press conference, in the end, the media stands all chose this one sentence as their headlines.

　

Ye Xiu: I'm Back.

Apart from that, the media groups all did did their best to compile, collate and express, reporting the other contents.

A year of preparations was what gave Happy the win. Opportunity smiles only upon those who are prepared!

Excellent Era's ex-captain strikes in the press conference, condemning Excellent Era's boss, Tao Xuan, for abandoning Excellent Era!

Happy, brought together by love!

...

This news all had plenty of substance to it and were written in whatever way that would elicit the best reactions. Yet this was nothing more than leaking the information from the press conference. The true value of this discussion was in using the information to guide the people.

Those reporters that liked Excellent Era used Ye Xiu's speech and the best of their writing capabilities to segregate Excellent Era from Tao Xuan. All the dirt on Excellent Era's name was shifted onto Tao Xuan. The other neutral reporters didn't point them in a different direction either, faced with the clarity of truth.

　

It isn't the team's fault, but a specific person!

With this description, everyone found it reasonable after reading! All these incidents were created by a single person, the boss, who had ordered this. It was his control that had brought the team down with him.

　

Thus, in an instant, the winds changed.

Many Excellent Era fans had already disbanded. They couldn't tolerate all the shocking situations that Excellent Era had revealed and were giving up on Excellent Era. However, with the freshly printed articles, their sorrow and disappointment all turned to anger. They gathered once more to protect their Team Excellent Era. They wanted to exorcise the real malice behind all this.

Get out of here, Tao Xuan!

Within the day, signs like these were all over Club Excellent Era's walls, their grounds and in the hands of the players. Beg for Excellent Era to not be sold? No such player ever appeared again. They had already realized that the sale of Excellent Era wouldn't cause it to collapse, but if they let Tao Xuan continue his ways, then Excellent Era's name would be forever tarnished.

Excellent Era belonged to all of them, but it was nothing but fixed assets in Tao Xuan's hands. That was Excellent Era's physical form, but not its soul.

Where was its soul? Its soul was in the hearts of all its fans.

The loyal Excellent Era fans condemned Tao Xuan while at the same time began to call out, asking for someone who truly loved Glory and Excellent Era to take over Team Excellent Era.

In that instant, Excellent Era was revived.

The fans were always the greatest wealth a team had.

No one was willing to take Excellent Era in full because all the things that had happened with Excellent Era had caused them to lose the support of their fans. This sort of mess wasn't something that anyone was willing to deal with. Yet now, the fans had saved themselves. They realized where the problem had occurred and found a way to solve it. They came out to support Excellent Era once more. This was something everyone noticed.

This sort of Excellent Era could stand on its own once more. However, there was a requirement to that, and that was that Tao Xuan had to leave. He could leave with all his possessions, but he couldn't take a single fan with him. Even if there was nothing here any longer, the fans would stand guard here. With their protection, Excellent Era could rise again from nothing and be reborn.

How did this change happen? It started from the words Ye Xiu had said to the reporters. They awakened so many fans.

Ye Xiu was their captain forever!

No Excellent Era fan would ever doubt that again. Even though Excellent Era had been sent out of the Pro League by him personally, that was a match and that was all there was to it. Wasn't this always their captain's attitude on the field?

After departing for a year, their once captain officially announced: he was back.

It was just unfortunate that he didn't return to Excellent Era. Though some people were already calling for Ye Xiu to come back and lead Excellent Era again, most of the fans couldn't ask that of him anymore.

It was too selfish.

Ye Xiu had done enough for Excellent Era. They had no reason to relentlessly demand him make any more contributions.

Ye Xiu didn't owe Excellent Era anything. It was Excellent Era that owed him too much.

Disregarding everything else, this was true from just looking at the contract he had signed. Han Wenqing, who had slaughtered his way through the Alliance from the very beginning alongside Ye Xiu, had the heftiest contract in the Alliance. As for their captain? All these years, he still held the contract that had been signed at the beginning of the Alliance, a contract that gave him a pitiful income in these times.

Talking about money was somewhat blunt, but Excellent Era owed their captain this bluntness. However, he had never expressed anger about it because he had never cared.

All he wanted, all he ever wanted was one thing: victory. This was something that would never change for him, no matter where he was. All the Excellent Era fans could do was give him their blessings.

Chapter 1062: Keep Winning Through the Booing

The commotion surrounding Excellent Era was still going on, but Excellent Era was big, not nearly as easy to take over as Team Everlasting. Even disregarding everything else, just the God-level account, Battle God One Autumn Leaf, was probably more valuable than all of Team Everlasting's assets put together. Plus, Excellent Era had been a part of the Alliance for years, so they had their own training grounds.Their own stadium that had been built over the years of the Alliance's rapid development. Excellent Era was massive. There was nothing that you could just buy on a whim. Public opinion and the support of the fans had reawakened its inner value. This might have elicited interest, but it also made a purchase harder. Considering this inner value, Excellent Era's worth was even greater.

However, what was good for buyers was that Excellent Era's boss, Tao Xuan, had been pushed to a point where he had to sell Excellent Era. Team Excellent Era had the chance continue continue to grow and create profit in anyone's hands except his, for that would turn it into a sinking ship with the loss of fan support.

　

With the path clear, how the future transactions concerning Excellent Era would go was up to the buyer and seller to negotiate. From popular opinion, most believed that Excellent Era wouldn't be completely bought out as a whole. After all, Excellent Era had a lot to it. Such a large investment would require several years of good business, and that was only if Excellent Era could swiftly return to the Pro Alliance and compete as a viable champion team.

However, there would always be risks in competition. If Excellent Era had another bad year and couldn't get back to the Alliance, then that would really be something to weep about. Therefore, popular opinion said that Excellent Era would most likely sell some of its basic hardware to decrease its overall value and risk. That way, someone would be willing to take it on.

How far negotiations had gone so far, no one knew, and the playoffs for the ninth season of the Pro Alliance was fast approaching.

After testing things out at the Challenger League, the Alliance eventually decided that the playoffs for the Pro Alliance would be conducted using the headcount rules of the offline Challenger League tournament matches. Additionally, after asking obtaining the opinions of multiple parties, the scoring method was set as a point for every opponent killed. Whoever had more points would be the victor.

　

Apart from that, another large change was made to the rules. The new playoffs wouldn't be decided through the sum of the points of each team for two rounds of matches. Instead, the Alliance would use the overall victory of each individual round to make a judgement. The victor would be decided best two of three. That meant it had changed from needing to fight two rounds to possibly three.

　

Without a doubt, this was a change for the better from both competition and economic viewpoints, and the reason this change could be made was because of the use of the new rules.

The old rules split a round into three parts, individual competition, group arena, team competition. Under the situation where the team competition took up the majority of the points, the overall victory could be decided by two parts and the group arena would lose its purpose. However, if the points of the team competition were lowered, the victory could be decided with just the individual competition and group arena, and there might not be a reason to hold the team competition.

The Alliance didn't want any of these situation to happen, and the new rules would prevent any of the aforementioned situations from occurring. And if the headcounts of the two sides were tied at the end, then that could be dealt with through overtime, so it wasn't a problem. With that, the two best of three rules would be implemented.

Then, amidst the enthusiastic promotion by the Alliance, the playoffs came closer and closer, once again taking center stage in the Glory circle. The members of the eight teams that had made it to the playoffs all appeared onstage, raising support for their teams. Now that they had gotten here, any team had the reason to anticipate getting that trophy sitting at the pinnacle.

However, when being interviewed, all eight teams had been asked questions regarding Happy. Even if those questions had been asked long ago, the media didn't rest. For someone who didn't understand the backstory to this, they would probably think that Happy was a hidden bBoss in the playoffs or something upon reading these interviews. Otherwise, why else would every interview for every team mention the name Happy?

"What are your opinions on Ye Xiu's return?" In the interview with Tyranny, all the reporters were willing to ask Han Wenqing this question.

"I eagerly await to meet him on the stage." As a long-time rival, Han Wenqing's welcome to Ye Xiu was still with his fists.

"As another player who retired and returned, is there anything you would like to say to Ye Xiu?" Zhang Jiale was also a focus in the interview.

"He accomplished something I had thought impossible. For that, I truly admire him," Zhang Jiale replied.

"What are your thoughts on Ye Xiu's return?" In the interview with Blue Rain, the same question appeared.

　

"The skill level of the entire Alliance will rise a stage," Blue Rain's captain Yu Wenzhou expressed.

"Don't you think that without Excellent Era, it would be more of a loss?" A reporter asked.

　　

"Hey, don't worry too much about that. Does Excellent Era's skill level not rely on their players? With their situation, there's little chance their players would stay. I think they'll find an opportunity to transfer and we'll definitely see them in the Alliance again. How about we guess where they'll go? For example, Sun Xiang, I think…"

　　

"Next question." The press officer from Blue Rain cut Huang Shaotian off stoically. He had gotten used to doing this because of how many times he had to in the past. Huang Shaotian's feelings? What was that? Never heard of it.

"Hm...…." In the Samsara interview, Zhou Zekai gave a "hm" before falling into a lengthy silence when faced with the question of Ye Xiu's return.

It wasn't until the atmosphere of the place had gone a little strange that he abruptly spoke up and added two words, "very difficult."

　

"You mean to say, that it'll be very difficult to deal with Ye Xiu?"

"Yes." Zhou Zekai nodded.

Ok, this was Zhou Zekai. Being able to get this sort of response was already good enough. If they wanted to know more opinions, it'd be better to just go and find their vice-captain Jiang Botao.

The eight teams all had different responses. The media had gotten what they wanted. However, in truth, these eight teams definitely wouldn't put their focus on Ye Xiu, who they would only see next season. The fight for the season nine championships was about to start and the first match was the gossip-filled match between Tyranny and Hundred Blossoms. The first round would be held on Hundred Blossom's turf and the tension was obvious. Even today, there were many Hundred Blossoms players who couldn't accept Zhang Jiale's decision to join Tyranny after returning.

When Zhang Jiale appeared, thunderous booing instantly flooded the stadium.

Zhang Jiale was emotionless. This wasn't the first time he had gotten this sort of reception. During the regular season, he had already received such treatment in this stadium, the very stadium that he had fought in for years, the stadium he was oh so familiar with.

Now that it had come to the playoffs, Zhang Jiale was facing a similar situation to Ye Xiu and had to fight to the death with his original team.

　

What was he feeling? Zhang Jiale had been asked such a question in the pre-match interview. He didn't answer because he didn't know what he was feeling. He had once thought he could deal with this calmly, but now that it came to it, he found that it wasn't so simple.

　

Amidst the boos, Zhang Jiale silently walked towards the preparations room.

"Go die!" A bellow rang out from the spectator stands and they saw a group of enraged Hundred Blossom fans throw filled drink bottles down. This life and death elimination match had scattered their rationality.

It was good that they were rather far away and the closest weren't very accurate. Zhang Jiale hurriedly dodged this attack. The security guards had already split into two teams, one team went to stop these fans and the other rushed over to protect Zhang Jiale from further harm.

　

The troublemaker fans had been sent out of the stadium. No matter what, this sort of act would be condemned heavily.

Zhang Jiale quietly watched the fans being escorted out and some still had their heads turned to curse at him. Zhang Jiale sighed, before realizing that someone next to him was staring at him.

Zhang Jiale turned his head to look and paused for a moment before squeezing out a strained smile. "Little Le…"

Little Le was one of the security guards at Hundred Blossoms, and had been one when Zhang Jiale was still there. At the same time, he was also a loyal fan of Hundred Blossoms and the entire team was very familiar with him.

"Welcome back," Little Le said, walking closer, but his face was unsmiling.

　　

Zhang Jiale wasn't sure how to react for a moment, about to say something when Little Le suddenly sent him a punch.

The stadium was rather chaotic right now and no one expected that even security guards would do something so irrational. Little Le was quickly restrained by his fellows. He didn't struggle at all, just gazed at Zhang Jiale without a hint of a smile.

"Let him go…"

Zhang Jiale could still feel bile coming up from the punch, but managed to squeeze out the sentence.

The guards knew the severity of what Little Le had done, but if Zhang Jiale wasn't going to press, then there was room to maneuver. They all rather obviously favored Little Le and hurriedly let him go upon hearing Zhang Jiale's words, but kept him back to prevent him from acting rashly again.

　

"To be a champion, I will win!" Zhang Jiale threw these six words down before turning and leaving. None of Tyranny had clearly seen the chaos that had erupted just now, only seeing the security grabbing another person, guessing that something must have happened. However, Zhang Jiale simply shook his head and didn't say much more. Everyone knew that this match was very difficult for Zhang Jiale and didn't pry.

"Don't worry, I'm fine." After sitting in his spot for a long while, Zhang Jiale suddenly spoke up. Though his teammates didn't ask, he could still feel the worry they had for him. The team was a whole. He needed to use his attitude to disperse their worries and get everyone focused on the match.

"We must win." After taking a deep breath, Zhang Jiale stood amidst the boos.

　

In the public announcement just now, the players for each side had been announced. The first to go up for Tyranny was Zhang Jiale.

After several minutes, when he walked down from the stage, Team Tyranny had already gained two points. Zhang Jiale had successfully accomplished a one versus two in the group arena, only falling against the third person.

For the championship, I have to be strong and keep winning!

With this in mind, Zhang Jiale returned to Tyranny's bench amidst the boos with his head high and back straight.

The first day of the playoffs saw Team Tyranny winning their away game against Team Hundred Blossoms, 11 to 7. The MVP that day was the Team Tyranny player, Zhang Jiale. Account: Spitfire, Hundred Dazzling Blossoms.

Chapter 1063: Semifinalists

In the post-match interviews, Zhang Jiale was faced with many more sensitive questions as the MVP and Hundred Blossom's ex-captain. Zhang Jiale was composed, only expressing his determination to win the championships.

For the championships, Zhang Jiale mercilessly crushes Hundred Blossoms...

The media, who always liked to twist things a little, had to write much drama into the topic. The match of the second day arrived amidst the clamour and discussion.

This match wasn't as drama-filled as Tyranny versus Hundred Blossoms. Samsara still had Zhou Zekai as their ace and core, while Void, as always, had their Ghostblade Duo of Li Xuan and Wu Yuce. In the end, Zhou Zekai's fast shooting broke through Void's Ghostblade Duo and Team Samsara won their away game 11 to 8 against Void.

On the third day, it was Wind Howl versus Misty Rain. Wind Howl's Zhao Yuzhe desperately wanted to become the Alliance's number one Elementalist. In the Rookie Challenge, he had tried to imitate his captain, Tang Hao, challenging Misty Rain's ace, Chu Yunxiu. Unfortunately, he lost in the end. The two teams were paired in the playoffs and, for Zhao Yuzhe, this was another good opportunity to prove himself. Unfortunately for him, he was far from being the star of the show. Tang Hao was undoubtedly the star of Wind Howl. They also had number two player Fang Rui. As the representative of playing dirty, how dirty he could play each match was always something people eagerly anticipated seeing.

For Misty Rain, Chu Yunxiu had never been an extremely competitive person, so there wasn't all that much to see about Zhao Yuzhe challenging her . Zhao Yuzhe's ambitions had never aroused much attention. It was the beautiful twin sisters, Shu Keyi and Shu Kexing, that Misty Rain had dug up during the winter season who gained the most public attention. Team Misty Rain didn't give them two new characters. They used the two male Sharpshooters that they had used originally in the game, Lower Your Head and None Dare Attack.

In the end, Team Misty Rain had three female players, yet not a single female character appeared on the field. The three characters played by the female players, Windy Rain, Lower Your Head and None Dare Attack, were all male characters.

Of course, after being equipped with pro level equipment, the strength of the two new characters had skyrocketed. In the latter half of the season, the twins had more and more chances to appear on the field. The two were both doing their best to get used to the pro circle and enter a better state. Everyone was wondering. Would these two become Misty Rain's ace card in the playoffs?

Not disappointing everyone's hopes, Shu Keyi and Shu Kexing ended up being a part of the starting lineup in the team competition for their opening match of the playoffs. Unfortunately, they didn't become the aces to Misty Rain's victory, because Misty Rain seemed to have forgotten that Wind Howl had Fang Rui, a man who would die if he didn't play dirty, and playing dirty was definitely the way to suppress noobs. The twins' first journey in the playoffs wasn't a smooth one and Team Misty Rain lost 9 to 11 to Wind Howl in their home game.

Three matches of the first round of playoffs had gone by and what resulted was a flood of visiting teams winning home teams. It was on the fourth day that this status quo was finally broken. In the much-anticipated Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain match, the home team, Team Blue Rain, finally won back some face for home teams and won 11 to 9 against the visiting team, Team Tiny Herb. These two teams were already archrivals. Now that both had spectacular rookies, this match was full of ups and downs, a wonderful experience for the audience. This match was definitely the most spectacular match amongst the opening round matches.

With the opening round coming to curtain call, next up was the second round. In the end, the first match of the second round was a totally unexpected victory for Team Hundred Blossoms who managed to win against Team Tyranny in a close call 11 to 9.

Team Hundred Blossoms hadn't had any sort of obvious advantage throughout the match, but gave a performance full of persistence and desperation. The entire team was feeling the pressure. In this season, they hadn't started out well and were plagued by criticism. It was good that they were able to catch the last bus to the playoffs after the big update. This achievement filled the team and fans with hope that they might be able to advance in the playoffs. Yet, the very first match was coincidentally against the team that Zhang Jiale had joined, the team that public opinion said was the most likely to be the champions, Team Tyranny. The fans all hoped that they would be shown their place.

But while hopes and dreams were wonderful, reality was cruel. In the first round, they lost their home game, bringing the Hundred Blossom fans back to that chilling season opening. Especially since Zhang Jiale had gotten the MVP for that match, that made things unbearably painful. However, Team Hundred Blossoms didn't give up. They managed to surge up under this pressure and counter with a heavy blow to Tyranny on Tyranny's home turf. There were no weak teams in the playoffs. The Hundred Blossom fans were proud of their team. Their tie with Tyranny was enough to make many media groups write the headlines of the following day as "The flourishing resurgence of a Hundred Blossoms".

No such reversal appeared in the two matches of the next two days. Samsara defeated Void in their home game, Wind Howl took down the visiting Misty Rain, and the two teams were set as semi-finalists.

Team Void always managed to enter the quarterfinals, but would also always get stopped there. Their Dual Linking Ghost Boundary duo was a classic pair in the Glory circle, but this pair never managed to achieve a convincing accomplishment. Should Team Void make some greater adjustments to achieve a breakthrough? This was something many people started discussing after this match.

As for Misty Rain, they might have lost the match, but their fans gained hope. This hope came from the twins. Though these twins were girls like Chu Yunxiu, their demeanor on the battlefield definitely wasn't like some maiden-in-distress. The two had open and strong personalities and great cooperation. Team Misty Rain had often been seen as lacking in a headstrong temperament because their ace was female, but now this might change because of these other two female players. Misty Rain's tactical system was changing rather obviously. This pair of twins might very well become the future core of Misty Rain, if they developed their skills well. As for Chu Yunxiu, she was changing from a DPS based Elementalist to a support. Perhaps this role was better suited to her personality. Then, Misty Rain's other All-Star level player, Li Hua, was a sneak attack and assassination expert. People were eagerly anticipating Misty Rain's future developments.

　　

Then, on the fourth day, it was Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain again, but this time they were competing on Tiny Herb's turf. This time, it was Tiny Herb who had used their home advantage to wipe out Blue Rain. From this, it was clear that the two teams were very close in skill level, having to eventually use the home advantage to influence the scales of victory.

　

Tyranny versus Hundred Blossoms and Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain both needed a third match to decide the victor. The third round of competitions would continue on the same home turf of the second round matches. That meant, it would still be the higher ranked Tyranny and Tiny Herb's home games. However, for the third round, the home advantage would be greatly reduced.

The home team would only have a familiar environment and the support of local fans, but this round, they would no longer have the right to choose their maps.

The right to chose the map was the greatest home advantage in Glory competitions and the Alliance considered how to make this as fair as possible. They were giving the team with a higher rank a part of the home advantage, but this advantage couldn't be too influential on the final victor. In the past, it was just the situation of away then home that gave them an easier time taking control of the situation. Now, the third round had been handed to them, but the right to choose the map was too big of an advantage, so they took away this right. The map for the third round would be randomly chosen from the map bank that had been prepared for the playoffs. These maps were designed specifically for the playoffs by the developers and info on them wouldn't be leaked at all. That meant that the third round would be played with the teams having zero knowledge of the map.

This sort of match would definitely be a test of the adaptability of the two teams.

The first match of the third round was Tyranny versus Hundred Blossoms again. The experience veterans had helped them greatly on this sort of unfamiliar map. Having one senior was like having a treasure, and Tyranny had three, no? In the group arena, this sort of advantage wasn't evident, but in the team competition, the veterans understood the map better and were better able to find opportunities in battle than Hundred Blossoms. Team Hundred Blossoms might be persistent, but they were still suppressed by Team Tyranny. In the end, Tyranny won 11 to 8.

Hundred Blossoms lost.

But this time, they weren't the target of any blame.

Tyranny's strength this season was clear as crystal to anyone with eyes. Though the fans hoped for more from Hundred Blossoms, they were satisfied that the match had gone this far. Team Hundred Blossoms had found their rhythm. So long as they continued down this path, they believed that victory would descend on them. The team and the fans both bid the playoffs goodbye with this sort of confidence in their hearts.

As for the other match after this, it was Tiny Herb versus Blue Rain. One of the two powerhouses was doomed to be eliminated in the opening round. This was quite the shame. In the end, Team Tiny Herb managed to win this match. What had influenced the scales of victory, in the end, wasn't the tiny home advantage that Team Tiny Herb held. In the match, Team Blue Rain's rookie, Lu Hanwen, made a serious mistake which became the turning point for the match.

This optimistic and energetic young man finally shed tears in the post-match interview, causing the reporters to be unable to blame him at all. No one would forget, this was a teenager who wasn't even fifteen yet. But would Blue Rain be hindering his growth, letting such a young player bear the weight of such a heavy responsibility?

"Next time, I'll be stronger!"

　

No one would've thought that in the end, Lu Hanwen would wipe away his own tears and say this to the reporters with determination.

He was truly an amazing rookie!

The reporters were surprised. They had seen plenty of players be finished for good after experiencing a setback, especially those that had dragged down their team in important matches like this. But this young man wouldn't. He would be regretful enough to shed tears for his mistake, but this didn't dishearten him. He turned this all into motivation to get stronger.

A player like this, full of positivity, wouldn't just get stronger, but someday, he'd become a role model for all pro players, wouldn't he?

　

Everyone had full confidence in this in that moment.

The quarterfinals of the playoffs came to a close there. Tyranny, Samsara, Wind Howl, Tiny Herb. The top four of the regular season had all defeated their opponents, reaching the semifinals.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

The TKA OVA will be coming out on 4/27 and it'll be covering the season eight All Stars arc! For more information + trailer: https://www.patreon.com/posts/18394462/

Chapter 1064: Bleak and Desolate Excellent Era

The playoffs advanced like wildfire. Happy's group had received invites from Lou Guanning and stayed over at Club Heavenly Swords for a few days. The two sides scrimmed with each other every day and watched the matches together. Apart from that, Lou Guanning started a discussion for any possibilities of continuing their collaboration with Happy.

The two sides would be direct opponents in the league next season. There would be a direct collision of interests unlike before. Lou Guanning could be considered as starting off as a commoner and later becoming a nobleman. They first discussed and did a gentleman's agreement of what would be appropriate and what would be inappropriate for future collaborations in order to avoid any future disputes that would ruin the good relationship between them.

After a hanging around for a few days, Happy returned home. When they left, Lou Guanning carefully told Ye Xiu a piece of news: "Excellent Era seems to want to sell One Autumn Leaf. They're currently making inquiries of our thoughts on the matter."

"Oh?" Ye Xiu's expression was the same as always, "So what are your thoughts?"

"20 million….. I think that's too much..." It wasn't known if Lou Guanning intentionally gave Ye Xiu the price. Lou Guanning laughed bitterly, "At our current level, having this type of character is too much of a waste."

"You're quite rational now!" Ye Xiu felt moved.

"One step at a time!" Lou Guanning smiled.

"That's good. See you!" Ye Xiu called out and got ready to leave.

"Then..." Lou Guannign hesitated, but still spoke, "One Autumn Leaf….. If you're short on cash, just say the word."

"No need." Ye Xiu smiled, "It's the same as Excellent Era. It's all in the past."　

"But what about Little Tang!" Lou Guanning pointed at Tang Rou.

"If she wants it, then she can buy it herself." Ye Xiu said half-jokingly.

Lou Guanning stared blankly. Then, he remembered Tang Rou's background and suddenly let out a laugh. Finally, he shook Ye Xiu's hands and bade farewell.

City H, Club Excellent Era.

It had been several days since the commotion. The current Club Excellent Era felt cold and desolate despite the scorching summer heat. There were no fans gathered outside the club. The signs scattered everywhere had already been cleaned up by the sanitation workers. There were only a few traces left in certain areas.

The main entrance to Club Excellent Era was still shut tight. The surrounding people all said that the gate seemed to have never opened these past few days.

In front of this entrance, Ye Xiu raised his head and looked at the Team Excellent Era emblem hanging there. Before, the team emblem was cleaned twice a week. Now, the team emblem hadn't been cleaned in several days and looked a lot duller.

Zhi zhi zhi....

The main entrance was carefully opened a tiny bit. Half a head peaked out and looked at Ye Xiu. That person was slightly surprised and then opened up the door a bit wider.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng walked in. The main entrance was immediately closed afterwards. The interior of Club Excellent Era seemed just as cold as the outside. Not a single person could be seen in the entire yard. The two walked towards Excellent Era's training center. Over here was where Excellent Era's players lived most of their daily lives: eating, sleeping, practicing... apart from away matches, it was completely possible for a player to not leave a step out of this area. Ye Xiu had lived that type of life for many years.

They entered the building and went upstairs to the player residences. When they passed by the practice room, Ye Xiu heard the tapping of a keyboard and the clicking of a mouse.

It was Glory.

Ye Xiu could tell. This was a game that he was incomparably familiar with. When he heard the rhythm of the keyboard taps and mouse clicks, he could even imagine what that player was doing.　

There was still someone playing Glory in the Excellent Era practice room at this time?

"You go pack up. I'm going to take a look." Ye Xiu said.

"Okay." Su Mucheng nodded her head and continued onwards to her room in the player residence area. Ye Xiu walked into the practice room.

The door to the practice room wasn't closed. Ye Xiu walked inside gently and saw someone in front of a computer. He was playing Glory, the online Arena. This person was playing a Battle Mage and was currently in an intense battle with an opponent. However, with just a few glances, Ye Xiu had a rough idea of the situation. Everything went like he expected. Not even a minute passed and the Battle Mage was killed by the opponent…..

"You suck." Ye Xiu said.

The person sitting at the chair suddenly turned his head. When he saw Ye Xiu standing behind him, he stared blankly at him. For a long time, no words came out of his mouth.　

Tao Xuan…...

At this moment, the person playing Glory in the Excellent Era practice room was actually Excellent Era's boss, Tao Xuan. That Tao Xuan who usually stood up high and only came to the practice room for inspections.

Ye Xiu took out a cigarette box and nimbly shook a cigarette out towards Tao Xuan: "Did you stop smoking?"　

Tao Xuan was surprised at first and then extended his hands out: "I'll take one!"

After lighting up the cigarette, Tao Xuan immediately sucked in a deep breath. It was as if he had found something to place his burdens on.

"How's the sale going?" After smoking until about half a cigarette left, Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

"Not too well." Tao Xuan said, "There's too much. There are very few people who could even take it all in the first place. We aren't in the Alliance either, so the risk is too great. I've talked to several people, but the price was pushed down too much. It was impossible to negotiate."　

"So?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Split it up." Tao Xuan said.

"And then?" Ye Xiu asked.　　

"Then….." Tao Xuan stared blankly, "There is no then."　

Yes, there was no then…...

Whether he sold the entire Excellent Era at once or parts of Excellent Era at a time, he would still be able to earn a huge amount of money. However, the timing was too poor. A situation where the seller must sell. There was no situation that could be worse than that for a seller. Any buyer who understood this point would calmly drag it on up until the price was satisfactory.

Tao Xuan had always been trying to maximize profits, but in the end, he could only quietly watch as the originally high prices were pushed down. It was a huge mockery to him.

But in any case, Tao Xuan would still be earning a considerable amount of money. But then what? Nothing. There was no place for him anymore in the Glory scene. The only thing that would accompany him would be the money that came from selling Excellent Era.　　

And then…..　

Tao Xuan had thought about it, but he couldn't come up with anything. Having so much money should have been something that anyone would be overjoyed about, but he was at a loss. He seemed to be trapped in that painful situation where he had nothing but money. He didn't know how to get out of it. Invest? Start a new business? Tao Xuan had thought about it, but he always felt dispirited and downcast. He might as well just play Glory and have some fun.

Glory. He had obviously been a player once. If not, how could he have gotten to know Ye Xiu and Su Muqiu? But his skill level was limited and he was old. He wasn't someone who could stand on stage. In the end, he became a team manager.

One charged out onto the battlefield. One operated the logistics of the business.

Tao Xuan had originally thought that they would be the best partners together, but he realized after a while that they were moving farther and farther apart.

Business is business. He began pursuing profits, while his partner only knew how to fight on the battlefield, not keeping up with his path.

Gradually, Tao Xuan began thinking that if it wasn't for this partner holding him back, where would Excellent Era be at now?

As Excellent Era failed to make profits year after year, this thought started to grow firm and take root in Tao Xuan's mind. The best partner that he had once envisioned had become the greatest hindrance to Excellent Era's growth.

Finally, he set out to kick Ye Xiu from the team. But when he thought about it now, was that really for the sake of profits? Or was it due to envy? Tao Xuan didn't know. He only remembered that everyday, when he thought about how that guy was holding him back, he would often think about how if he were the Battle God, if he were One Autumn Leaf, he would certainly have led Excellent Era to even greater heights.

He also longed for glory. After all, he had once been a Glory player too…..

But what was the point of thinking about all of that now?

Tao Xuan laughed bitterly and shook his head. Suddenly, the sound of the practice room door creaking could be heard. A person pushed the door open and walked in.　　

Ye Xiu thought it was Su Mucheng. When he turned his head, he saw that it was Qiu Fei.

"Senior..." Seeing Ye Xiu, Qiu Fei was startled.

"It's been awhile." Ye Xiu smiled and gave a greeting.

But then he saw Qiu Fei wrinkle his eyebrows at the two of them: "No smoking is allowed in the practice room."

No smoking is allowed in the practice room? The two stared blankly. Yes, those were club rules, but at this moment, who cared if you followed the rules or not?

One person was the boss of the club. The other was the team's former captain. They slowly put down the cigarettes in their mouth. Afterwards, they saw as Qiu Fei walked to his seat and sat down. He opened the computer and then started practicing.

Practice?

Ye Xiu looked at the clock in the practice room. It was 9 AM. Yes, this was when Team Excellent Era would start practicing in the morning. Usually, the morning was targeted tech practice through a customized practice routine. In the afternoon, they would start practicing Glory for real. Qiu Fei was currently doing this morning routine, despite not knowing if Team Excellent Era even existed anymore.

Ye Xiu was stunned for a long time. Finally, he let out a smile. He got up and left the practice room. As for Tao Xuan, he just watched as Qiu Fei practiced with single-hearted devotion for a long long time.

Not long after leaving the practice room, Ye Xiu saw someone flash by him like a ghost. That ghost suddenly stepped back three times and rewinded back to that corner. He turned his head and looked carefully at Ye Xiu.

"Old Ye? You're back?" That person suddenly asked.

"I'm just passing by." Ye Xiu chuckled, "What are you doing?"

"All club operations have stopped. I've got to go too. Sigh, it's a pity for that new plan I just had..." This person sighed. Club operations had stopped. All employees would be dismissed. They would clearly be facing unemployment soon, but this guy was more worried that his new plan wouldn't be able to implemented.

"Alright then, why not go to my place to continue doing research, Rongfei!" Ye Xiu said.

"Your place?"　　

"Yeah, Team Happy." Ye Xiu said.　　

"Oh, research what?"

"A lot of things like the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Have you heard of it?" Ye Xiu said.　　

"The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella!" This person's eyes instantly lit up. Immediately afterwards, he asked: "So when do I start?"

Chapter 1065: Never Come Back Again

For his job, Guan Rongfei was just an ordinary member of Excellent Era's R&D team. However, if you were considering his importance, he was the true core member of the research and development team. He was passionate about researching all sorts of Silver weapons, and this passion didn't lose to the passion that all pro player had for victory. Hearing the words "Myriad Manifestations Umbrella", Guan Rongfei immediately became impatient to leave, making Ye Xiu uncertain if he should laugh or cry as he said, "Wait a moment!"

As he said this, he saw Su Mucheng coming out of her room, carrying a large suitcase. The reason they came back this time was mostly because she had to pack up.

"Rongfei is coming with us, too," Ye Xiu told her.

"Really?" Su Mucheng gazed at Guan Rongfei cheerfully. "You're in luck then, there's a lot of stuff for you to do there."

"Can we go now?" If any Excellent Era members saw Guan Rongfei's impatience, they would probably be absolutely heartbroken. He had worked at Excellent Era for so long already, but he didn't seem to have any feelings for it at all. This had coincided with Excellent Era's members disbanding, but considering this guy's response, even when Excellent Era was all well, he would have probably been immediately lured away with a "Hey, we're researching the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, you coming?"

It had been rather early on when Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been reported back to the club by the guild department. Excellent Era's R&D department had also done some research and that was when Guan Rongfei was first introduced to this prodigious creation. However, since this weapon was only useful for unspecialized, it didn't have much value to Excellent Era, so they didn't look into it too deeply. This wouldn't stop Guan Rongfei looking into it in his spare time to try and figure out how this thing was created.

"You're just leaving like that? Is there nothing you want to take with you?" Ye Xiu looked at Guan Rongfei, a little lost for words.

"Oh yeah!" Guan Rongfei smacked his own forehead and then ran off.

Yet it wasn't long before he was back, his hands empty and apparently having not packed anything, but his expression was relieved as he said, "It's all good now."

"What… did you pack?" Su Mucheng asked.

"The research and data I've done on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. I almost forgot it." Guan Rongfei took out an external hard drive from his pocket, waving it in front of the two for a bit before putting it back into his pocket. He looked at the two with eagerness, his face clearly asking: why aren't we leaving yet?

"Let's go," Ye Xiu decided and took Su Mucheng's luggage for her. The three left together, but bumped into Tao Xuan, who was just leaving the training room, on their way out.

Seeing Guan Rongfei with the two, Tao Xuan seemed to understand and didn't say anything, just nodding in greetings. It was Guan Rongfei, who didn't even glance at the boss that had given him his paycheck all these years, already leaving.

"So about Dancing Rain. Why don't you name a price?" Ye Xiu said to Tao Xuan.

Tao Xuan was puzzled for a moment before remembering the promise he had made when he had first gone to Happy to find Ye Xiu. At the time, he had thought Ye Xiu would ask for One Autumn Leaf, but never expected that it would be Dancing Rain instead.

　

"How about 450,000?" Tao Xuan suggested.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng exchanged a glance.

This price obviously wasn't Dancing Rain's true value. As the Number One Launcher character, Dancing Rain was extremely valuable. Even ten million wouldn't be unexpected.

450,000! If any passerby heard this, they'd probably think they were hallucinating, but Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng knew where this price came from. 450,000 was the price Tao Xuan had originally bought out this character for in Excellent Era's name.

During the very beginnings of the Alliance, the characters were all brought into the club by the players. These were all characters that the pro players had slowly built up themselves. Back then, the club management had already realized that strong characters would be an important asset of the club, so they arranged for the ownership of these characters to be removed from the players and given to the club early on. That's how the system today was created: the ownership of characters all belonged to the club, and there were rarely any characters that belonged to the individual. Then, after that short period of time in the beginning, these resources were able to be utilized. If any new players joined, the club would provide characters directly. These characters would usually be far stronger than the characters that the players originally used in the game.

Su Mucheng joined the Alliance in season four. By then, it was rare for powerful characters to be brought into the club by the player. However, there would be special circumstances where players would continue using their online characters. Because the characters that the players had brought with them wouldn't be that strong, the clubs wouldn't buy them for an exceptionally high price. They treated it as giving that the player a small money bonus for signing the contract.

　

Dancing Rain was bought by Excellent Era under these circumstances. 450,000 wasn't a price that any random character in the online game had. It was because Ye Xiu had already put some effort into strengthening this character that it was worth more. But for a completely unknown character, that was the most it could be sold for.

　

The Dancing Rain back then couldn't be compared to the Dancing Rain today.

　

Apart from powerful equipment, the current Dancing Rain also had the accumulation of all the effort put into her all these years as well as the halo of the title of Number One Launcher. This sort of character wouldn't just increase the strength of a team, but also how influential they were.

Situations like during last the summer, when Team Samsara had bought the Tiny Herb Grappler Flying Drops and dismantled him into equipment, were extremely rare. In the end, it was because Flying Drop's influence wasn't enough. He wasn't like Hundred Dazzling Blossoms who could send his player into the All-Stars purely through the nostalgia fans held of him.

Flying Drops wasn't so grand, so what if he was dismantled? If it was a God-level account, never mind the fans objecting, even Samsara themselves would never bear the thought of dismantling it.

Dancing Rain had only been bought for 450,000. After so many years, even if Dancing Rain's strength hadn't been raised at all, just through sheer renown, the character's price would definitely be higher.

The 450,000 Tao Xuan had given today was undoubtedly a friends rate.

"Okay, that's settled then!" Ye Xiu nodded and didn't say much more.

He could tell that everything ended here. This 450,000 RMB transaction would probably be the last interaction they had that bore any sort of emotional investment. After that, they would go their separate ways. They wouldn't know if they would ever interact again, but the past would never repeat itself again.

　　

"Good luck." Tao Xuan offered his right hand to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu glanced at it before finally stretching out his hand to shake.

"I never need luck." After that, he turned and left.

Guan Rongfei didn't let up with the impatient looks at all as they left, forcing Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng to hurry. Getting to the ground floor, the entrance of the training center, they saw two people walking in from the front door.

"Ms. Su Mucheng… Ye Qiu… I mean, God Ye Xiu." The person on the left slowed down upon seeing the three and greeted them. Then he looked at Guan Rongfei and, not recognizing him, didn't greet him.

Ye Xiu looked at Su Mucheng, feeling a little lost. Though he was a God as well, he was so discreet all these years that he wasn't at all used to this sort of celebrity situation where others recognized him and he didn't recognize them. It was Su Mucheng who smiled at the newcomer and greeted him with a hello.

The person didn't introduce himself, just starting a conversation with Su Mucheng, "I hear you're joining Team Happy?"

"Yes."

"What a shame. I really hoped that we would get a chance to cooperate." The other replied.

　

Su Mucheng simply smiled.

　

"Then… I wish you three a good day. Excuse me." The person didn't have the intentions to chat for too long and left with that.

"That person from Tiny Herb is probably here to negotiate some sort of transaction…" Su Mucheng didn't wait for Ye Xiu to ask before explaining. Since Ye Xiu was so lowkey in the past, he mostly only knew pro players in their circle. Apart from that, he would keep his interactions with other members as low as possible. This was one person he had never seen before.

"Oh…" Hearing Su Mucheng's explanation, Ye Xiu nodded.

"It's probably… about Qiu Fei's transfer?" Su Mucheng guessed. Team Tiny Herb had never hid their interest in Qiu Fei. They had expressed interest during the Challenger League. It was evident that it didn't matter if Excellent Era was eliminated or not, Qiu Fei was someone they would be interested in transferring over regardless. However, Tiny Herb probably felt that they had more of a chance with Excellent Era's current situation!

Thinking of that figure still in the training room, Ye Xiu realized that Qiu Fei did have that sort of 'I won't give up even if the world is ending' demeanor to him. Tiny Herb… Would he join them?

As they were thinking of this, the door was opened once more and someone else entered. This person wasn't just someone Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng recognized, even Guan Rongfei recognized him. In the past year, this was the person who took the position of Excellent Era's vice captain. With his eyes set on the future, he was like coal in the harsh winter for Excellent Era. Yet the coal hadn't even flickered to life yet before they had all frozen to death together. Xiao Shiqin's figure seemed to hold that sort of desolation. It hadn't even been a month since the end of the Challenger League Finals and this guy seemed to have already gotten thinner.

　

The two sides met at the door and spent a long time in silence, enough so that Guan Rongfei began to look impatient again.

"You haven't left yet?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Yeah." Xiao Shiqin nodded.

"What are your plans?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I don't know." Xiao Shiqin shook his head. He had sacrificed a year and made a resolute decision. However, he had completely failed. The defeat at the Challenger League wasn't a small blow for Xiao Shiqin.

"How about you come to Happy?" Ye Xiu suggested. Xiao Shiqin's contract was only a year long. That meant, he was the same as Su Mucheng. His contract ended at the end of June and he could transfer for free. Happy was willing to try and get a player that didn't require a transfer fee.

"Happy?" Xiao Shiqin thought for a moment before smiling bitterly and shaking his head, "What can I do in Happy? Happy doesn't need me."

Ye Xiu didn't know how to react to that. Xiao Shiqin's talent was tactics, but Happy had Ye Xiu. The loss in the Challenger League, in reality, was also Xiao Shiqin's loss to Ye Xiu in tactics. This loss had killed his confidence in Ye Xiu's presence. It was clear that he didn't think he would be of any value in Happy.

"I still have something to do. Excuse me." Xiao Shiqin didn't seem to want to speak with Ye Xiu further and quickly excused himself and left.

　

"What a shame." Ye Xiu gazed at Xiao Shiqin's retreating figure with disappointment.

"Are we leaving or not!" Guan Rongfei wouldn't hold in his impatience any longer.

"Alright alright alright, let's go." Ye Xiu didn't know if he should laugh or cry, leaving Excellent Era with this guy. After walking out of the doors, he couldn't help but glance back.

This place… he'd probably never come back again.

Chapter 1066: Needing To Be Formal

By the time the team members returned, Happy Internet Cafe had returned to normal.

When the Challenger League ended, players and reporters swarmed there to see if they could catch a glimpse of anything. Unfortunately, the protagonists weren't there. And now that the finals had started, the reporters wouldn't be missing this annual meeting, and the players couldn't stick around the Internet cafe endlessly. As a result, people gradually took their leave.

Ye Xiu's trio didn't return to Happy Internet Cafe after they left Excellent Era. In fact, ever since they rented the gaming house in Forest Park, everyone apart from Chen Guo rarely went to the Internet cafe. This included Ye Xiu and Tang Rou, who previously worked in the cafe. Chen Guo employed new people to take their place, so they could commit their efforts wholeheartedly towards Glory.

Chen Guo felt that the house in Forest Park was no longer enough for them though.

The terraced houses were two stories tall: the bottom floor was used as a training room, while all the rooms in the top floor became the bedrooms, which accommodated two members each. In the beginning, Chen Guo thought this was enough, but after thinking about it now, she realised that she thought too simply of a team's structure.

Nowadays, players were the main core of the team. To keep up their fighting power, the guild and R&D departments were necessary.

Wu Chen was now completely committed towards Happy's guild department. The players they had met in the tenth server like Seven Fields didn't originally plan on joining the Heavenly Domain again. However, after seeing how successful Team Happy became, their hearts were moved. All of them planned on completing the Heavenly Domain Challenge, so they could fight their way through Heavenly Domain and assist in the team's expansion.

However, members like Seven Fields could only support part-time. Happy only had Wu Chen to take care of the guild full-time. However, the team would grow. No team would only have the guild leader alone in the guild office. Just from the number of people alone, the guild department would be the largest group in a club. There would be both full-time and part-time members. But since their job was limited to the game, most of them wouldn't come to the club for work. In the end, it didn't matter whether they worked at the club or not. But because they belonged to the club as permanent or contract employees, their numbers would be great.

As for the R&D department, it was the department requiring the highest confidentiality, so they appeared to be the most absolutely necessary part of the internal affairs fo the club. So even though the number of people working in there would be far less than those in the guild department, it was required of them to work at the club.

Happy wasn't that large yet, but as it continued to grow, they would eventually have to build these up. After taking in all these factors, the terraced houses in Forest Park wouldn't be enough to fit all of them in.

Should we rent another house?

While Chen Guo was thinking about how she should solve this problem, Ye Xiu brought a person before her.

"Guan Rongfei, the core God of Excellent Era's R&D department." Ye Xiu introduced Guan Rongfei to Chen Guo.

"Hi, welcome!" Chen Guo took the initiative to go up to shake his hand. She was extremely excited, because she knew that the person Ye Xiu brought here wasn't here to just look around.

"Hi." Guan Rongfei greeted Chen Guo simply. He didn't even bother to ask about her identity before he turned his head to ask Ye Xiu. "When should we start? Where's my computer?"

"Uh, over there." Ye Xiu had to search around the living room before he could finally point out a position. In the training room Chen Guo set up, there were twelve computers in a circle. If Happy included Su Mucheng, as well as Chen Guo, who was always using one, there was only one unused computer left. This remaining computer was allocated to Guan Rongfei by Ye Xiu.

"Oh." Guan Rongfei replied and quickly moved towards the computer. When he reached there, someone sat in the middle seat between the three computers and didn't even look at him when he went over.

"I'm Guan Rongfei." Guan Rongfei introduced himself.

"Mo Fan." That person only reported his name without even turning his head.

After that, Guan Rongfei sat down to turn on the computer and didn't pay attention to Mo Fan's reply. The two sat together without any bit of interaction as they did their own work.

The first thing Guan Rongfei did after the computer turned on was to connect to his external hard drive. He went through the documents as he controlled the keyboard and mouse with familiarity. He would occasionally murmur "This can" and "This can't."

Chen Guo followed along earlier. She saw Guan Rongfei move all the "can" documents into the computer while he instantly deleted the "can't" documents.

"Why can't we use those?" Chen Guo couldn't help but ask out of curiosity.

"Those are confidential, so they can't be used." Guan Rongfei said.

"Huh?" Chen Guo didn't really understand.

"It's the R&D department's NDA." Ye Xiu came over to explain.

Members of the R&D department definitely needed to sign an NDA, otherwise there wouldn't be any secrets about Silver equipment; a person could leave a club and take away large amounts of information.

The club couldn't stop the people from leaving, so signing the NDA was required. Although the agreement couldn't completely prevent the club's information from being taken, at least it wouldn't be used in such a broad and open way. People would often find loopholes, but it hadn't gone far enough that they could not tolerate it anymore and took it to court.

Guan Rongfei dove into his job without having a second word spoken. His increasing enthusiasm was rather shocking for Chen Guo. This God of the R&D department from Excellent Era... What sort of compensation was needed to keep him up and going?

For the past days, Chen Guo had constantly been pondering about these problems. However, it would be underestimating Boss Chen if her mind was completely blank. During the days they stayed at Heavenly Sword's place in City B, Chen Guo had humbly asked Lou Guanning about managing a team. As for Lou Guanning, he had even gathered the actual managing team of Heavenly Sword to help Chen Guo analyse Happy's current situation.

From what the professional team saw, Happy's current situation was excellent.

After defeating Excellent Era and advancing forward to enter the professional scene, no new team had ever received such widespread attention. How could Team Happy not get any sponsors in the new season? For them, this was simply impossible. In their current situation, sponsors might come to their doorsteps without even having to search for them.

The fact that Excellent Era might possibly split and be disbanded was very beneficial news for Happy's development. For sponsors in the same city as Excellent Era, if they still prized Glory as a good way to advertise, it was very likely for them to directly switch their sponsorship to Happy. By having a sponsor that was in the same city, they would naturally be able to establish a regional reputation. Since Glory was a popular esports, a team that won the championships would give pride to the whole city. By supporting a team in the same city, it would naturally give them a beneficial foundation in their local region.

Heavenly Sword taught a bunch of everything here and there to Chen Guo, and she was genuinely determined to learn this time. If there was anything she didn't understand, she made sure she could ask and be clear about it. She gained a lot within the few days. Even though she would constantly ponder about matters such as the compensation towards the team members, she was finally able to ease her heart. According to what the professionals in Heavenly Sword had said, Happy was a project that could not fail.

"What if we become the champion?" Chen Guo asked.

The professionals of Heavenly Sword looked at one another speechlessly. After a while, a glasses dude pushed up his spectacles before speaking. "If that really happened, I think this is probably what we call lucrative…..."

After returning from City B, Chen Guo was enormously proud and was thinking about how she could improve their training environment. Now that Guan Rongfei was brought here, it really reached the point where they couldn't stay unchanged. The twelve computers were all used up. If someone else joined, where should they be distributed? In addition, it was unpresentable for a team to have the guild and R&D department to sit together! For technological jobs like Guan Rongfei's, they probably needed peace and quiet, right? However in guilds department, there would constantly be yelling and screaming.

After Chen Guo made up her mind, she pondered on the different kinds of ideas. From what she saw, now was the right time to discuss this matter, so she looked for Ye Xiu.

"Hold on, I'll give this to him first." Ye Xiu was organising Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's information for Guan Rongfei. Guan Rongfei was the one being impatient, not Ye Xiu. When he was finished with his external hard drive, he started to hurry Ye Xiu up with his eyes.

"It's nothing important. I was just thinking that since we have become a formal team, team members would increase in the future, which is why I think this place is a bit unsuited. I currently have two ideas. Hear me out." Chen Guo spoke.

"Sure, go on." Ye Xiu nodded as he continued to import the documents.

"I am personally leaning towards the first idea, as it's also more homely. I was planning to clear out the whole of floor 2 in Happy. That level would become the training center and no longer be used for the Internet café business. After visiting Heavenly Sword, I feel it's enough for our training center and as well as some space for the guild and R&D department." Chen Guo said.

"Mm, not bad." Ye Xiu nodded.

"The other idea is to find a proper workplace and hire three to five rooms as our base. I keep feeling like it wouldn't be proper though." Chen Guo said.

"Are you telling me that you were planning on having us practice in an office?" Ye Xiu asked.

"It's not proper, right?" Chen Guo asked.

"Not at all!" Ye Xiu said.

"Then we'll go along with the first idea. We're currently unable to build another floor anyways!" Chen Guo said.

"The first idea is pretty good. Did you know that when I first started, the place where the team trained was in an Internet cafe. I'm merely walking through the same path from before again. However, we didn't have such good conditions at the time. The most we could do was to reserve a row of computers just for us in the Internet cafe." Ye Xiu said.

"Oh... Speaking of it, what did Tao Xuan used to do?" Chen Guo asked.

"Him? He used to be a boss of an Internet cafe as well..." Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1067: Sponsorships

Tao Xuan used to run an Internet cafe as well?

This answer was shocking for Chen Guo. She had never felt a lick of anything but distaste for Tao Xuan, yet now she found out that this guy used to be in the same line of business as she was and immediately felt shame for him.

"I really couldn't tell." Chen Guo said in disgruntlement.

Ye Xiu smiled, but didn't say anything.

"And after that?" Chen Guo then pursued because she suddenly realized that Excellent Era's rise to power back then was something she could probably learn a lot from.

"After? After that was going around competing in competitions. By then, the Alliance might've already been created, but it was just starting out and didn't have the same influence and renown as it does today. There were plenty of Glory competitions just like it and we would enter them all. Online matches, offline matches, so long as there was no scheduling conflict, we wouldn't miss a single one," Ye Xiu said.

"To train the team?" Chen Guo guessed.

"No… to win the prize money and make sure the team lived on and make sure the players lived on." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was stunned. Though she was older than Ye Xiu, she hadn't been a part of Glory for as long as he had. She had started out playing casually to pass the time to becoming a fan to follow the pro scene. By then, the Alliance had already been already well established, and the teams and players had become shining stars. At the very least, Club Excellent Era had already settled opposite to Happy Internet cafe and the resplendent team logo was already hung up. It was no longer what Ye Xiu described, needing to play in all sorts of matches to win enough prize money to live on.

"I no longer remember how many matches we played that year, how much prize money we won, how much prize money we won but never received. However, the Glory Pro Alliance was the most stable competition, which also gave the heftiest cash rewards. A year later, it had already gained much attention from the populace. More sponsorships, promoting it far and wide meant that the competing teams would get larger bonuses and more prize money. With this cycle, the teams and the Alliance began to grow rapidly, side by side.

Chen Guo nodded. She understood now. Even some of the things Ye Xiu didn't explain explicitly, she could guess. Excellent Era had successively won the first three championships of the Alliance. Without a doubt, disregarding the Alliance itself, they were the organization that took the greatest share of profit from the Alliance's first years. It was with this that Excellent Era managed to go from an Internet cafe team, a team that sounded downright poverty-stricken, to a top powerhouse.

As for the current Happy?

Chen Guo suddenly realized that the most difficult section of Happy's journey had somehow gone by without notice. Recalling their journey, from nothing to something, and then to the Challenger League, facing a massive powerhouse like Excellent Era, this was an impossible journey. But they did it. Would there be anything as difficult as this?

Taking the championship title?

Of course it would be difficult, but winning or losing the championships didn't affect the continued survival of a team. Team Happy had even managed to get through a life and death situation. Wouldn't the future be smoother?

In that moment, Chen Guo's confidence returned to her in full. She immediately left the house and returned to the Internet cafe. From now on, she was going to focus completely on doing the best she could for her team.

Before, she had turned part of the second floor of their Internet cafe into a training center, but she was still a little anxious inside. After all, the Internet cafe was her most stable source of income. But now, Chen Guo wasn't afraid anymore. Happy had come this far; there was no reason they'd fall now.

On the way over, Chen Guo had already picked up her phone to make a call and booked for renovators to come and take a look at the Internet cafe. After getting back to Happy and welcoming said renovators, they all went to the second floor together. She relayed her requirements to the renovators as they looked over the place of discussion. After discussing for almost a full day, the other went back to begin on blueprints. As for Chen Guo, she took her second big step after this first one.

"Is this Little Chang? It's Sis' Chen!" Chen Guo dialed the City H Esports Home reporter's number.

Of the two Esports Home reporters assigned to City H, one was in heaven and the other was in hell.

　

Glory was currently the hottest esports in the country. Although Esports Home was a comprehensive esports media group, they still focused primarily on Glory. The reason for the construction of City H's reporter base was entirely because of the local Team Excellent Era.

Logically speaking, there was no longer a reason for City H's reporter base to exist anymore with Excellent Era's relegation. However, no one had ever doubted Excellent Era's ability to immediately slaughter its way back into the Alliance from the Challenger League, not even Esports Home. Thus, the City H reporter base remained. Even though this year was a desolate one for the renown reporter Cao Guangcheng, he didn't despair, patiently waiting for the day Excellent Era would return to the Alliance.

But no one had ever thought that Excellent Era would fail just like that. What was even more awkward for Cao Guangcheng was that the one to defeat Excellent Era was Team Happy, Chang Xian's treasure, but a team that Cao Guangcheng didn't approve of.

Team Happy had Ye Xiu, so this shouldn't have been a team that Cao Guangcheng would look down on. However, Cao Guancheng did, because he had thought he knew more than anyone that it didn't matter if Ye Xiu was there or not since he couldn't be interviewed anyways. If he couldn't interview Ye Xiu, then what value did Team Happy have to him? What, you think they would actually win the Challenger League?

But they did.

Happy became the champions of the Challenger League and Chang Xian had a monopoly over Happy's interview resources. His publications continuously appeared on Esports Home. He had even gotten an exclusive interview from Ye Xiu. Everyone knew that Ye Xiu no longer shied away from this sort of thing, but, why didn't that asshole show this attitude earlier? If Cao Guangcheng had known that Ye Xiu would be willing to accept interviews, would he have so easily given Happy's lane to Chang Xian to run? Of course not!

Unfortunately, there were no 'if's.

The Excellent Era that Cao Guangcheng had his bets on and followed was now facing the problem of disbandment. And Happy, having defeated Excellent Era, was now a news hotspot. Chang Xian's attitude towards him hadn't changed any, still treating him respectfully as a senior, but Cao Guangcheng understood clearly that their roles had changed. In the future, City H's reporter base would be Chang Xian's turf because if the reporter base in City H were to remain, then it would be there for Happy. Chang Xian was on good terms with Happy and this was no secret in their circle. Through his connections, Cao Guangcheng had also gotten wind that the higher ups had no intentions of switching out Chang Xian and instead couldn't stop praising him.

During this period of time, Happy was a news hotspot and Esports Home had the best reports of all things Happy. This was entirely thanks to Chang Xian. The people in their circle were all too satisfied with Chang Xian's work and didn't have any intentions to try for his place.

Cao Guangcheng despaired. None of the higher-ups even tried to take this chance to pick peaches. It was probably impossible for him to replace Chang Xian. Follow around and wait on his past disciple? Cao Guangcheng couldn't bring himself to do that. He had already applied to his higher-ups, using Excellent Era's absence as a reason, to be switched to a different place.

　　

Cao Guangcheng's application hadn't been accepted by Esports Home yet, but he was set on not staying in City H. He had already begun preparing Chang Xian to take over.

"Ah ah, Sister Chen, hi!!"

The sound of Chang Xian taking a call met Cao Guangcheng's ears. He knew who Chang Xian was talking to: Team Happy's boss, Chen Guo.

A call from the boss of a team. Little Chang really had it good. Even though he knew Happy's current situation and the boss personally calling wasn't anything big, Cao Guancheng couldn't help but be a little jealous.

"Oh oh, I think we should have some of that! I'll look into it for you and call you later?"

"Okay, I'll do that then. Bye, Sister Chen."

The call was hung up. It sounded like Chen Guo had asked for Chang Xian to look into something.

　

"What did Happy want?" Cao Guangcheng asked casually. Usually, a question like this meant that he had eavesdropped on Chang Xian's phone call. Even though Chang Xian had no intentions to hide it from him, this still wasn't very good, especially between reporters. It was a sort of taboo. However, Cao Guangcheng was down-in-the-dumps and didn't care to consider this.

"Oh, Brother Cao, I was going to ask. It'd probably be more convenient for me to just ask you," Chang Xian said.

"What?" Cao Guangcheng asked.

"Happy wanted to ask, what sponsors does Excellent Era have, big or small. The more details we have the better," Chang Xian replied.

"That? Do they really need us to help them look into that?" Cao Guangcheng couldn't help but laugh at the answer he had gotten. What was a sponsor? They were the ones who gave you money and in return, you had to promote them. Thus, sponsors wouldn't be any sort of secret. Excellent Era had to find every way to show the world what sponsors they had. If you took a look at that, wouldn't Excellent Era's sponsors become clear?

"Uh, she wants to know all the sponsors they've ever had, including ones that backed out, so I think I should still take a look for her," Chang Xian said.

"Oh, I'm not too certain about that either. How about you look into it!" Cao Guangcheng said. As for the reason Happy wanted to look into this information, never mind him, even Chang Xian could easily guess that. It couldn't be anything but that Happy was starting to look for sponsorships, and they wanted to take the sponsors from Excellent Era, who were facing disbandment. This was an appropriate move to make.

However… wasn't Happy simplifying everything too much? If a sponsor sponsored Excellent Era, then that showed where they stood. Now, Happy had defeated Excellent Era and blocked them out of the pro alliance, pushing them to the dire situation they were in. Happy was Excellent Era's enemy. Those who were only just sponsoring Excellent Era a moment ago would turn around and sponsor Happy instead? Businesses cared about how they looked. Doing this would be no different from calling whoever had milk mother. Who would want that sort of image?

Taking Excellent Era's sponsors was a good idea.

However, Happy's boss Chen, it seems like you really don't understand. Glory is a competitive scene. If anyone were to invest in this area, it was a little different. Especially for local sponsors, it would be more than difficult for them to turn to Happy the moment Excellent Era fell.

"Oh yeah…" Cao Guangcheng suddenly remembered something, calling out to Chang Xian. "If Happy wants sponsors, there's one I recommend."

"Ah? Who?" Chang Xian asked.

"Dry Tea Green," Cao Guangcheng said, a barely perceptible smile flashing over his face. He didn't want to compete for anything anymore, but, maybe watching Happy humiliated would help get rid of the frustration in his heart.

Chapter 1068: Dry Tea Green’s Sponsorship

"Dry Tea Green?" Chang Xian stared blankly. He wasn't a City H person, but he had worked as a reporter here for quite some time. He was no stranger to this name. It was a name that could be seen everywhere in City H.

Dry Tea Green was a privately owned tea beverage company in City H. The various tea drinks that they produced were best sellers in the country. In City H, it occupied a large market share.

Beverages had an extremely wide range of uses. They could sponsor practically anything. However, for esports, the goods that gained the most benefit from sponsorships were tech-related products. As a result, the vast majority of team sponsorships were tech-related products.

Cao Guangcheng said that he had a good recommendation. Chang Xian originally thought that it was a tech-related product, but it turned out to be a tea drink? How could you say that was a great recommendation?

Cao Guangcheng saw Chang Xian's hesitation and obviously knew what he was hesitating about. He smiled: "Go do some research!"

"Okay!" Chang Xian replied and went to look up related information. Since Cao Guangcheng had recommended Dry Tean Green, he would naturally pay particularly close attention to it.

"What do you think?" Cao Guangcheng asked a short while later.

"This Dry Tea Green really is Excellent Era's most faithful sponsor!" Chang Xian was moved. The data showed that Dry Tea Green had sponsored Excellent Era for a good seven years. Starting from season three, Dry Tea Green had been Excellent Era's most loyal sponsor.

"Take a look at this season." Cao Guangcheng said.　　

"Oh?" Chang Xian checked the season nine data. Dry Tea Green was still a sponsor. Although the amount wasn't as high, Excellent Era had been relegated this season, so all their sponsors substantially lowered their sponsorship amounts. That wasn't anything strange, no? 　

"Dry Tea Green still sponsored them during season nine." Cao Guangcheng said.

"Yeah! Most of Excellent Era's sponsors stayed. After all, with Excellent Era's position, these sponsors probably hadn't included any clauses in their contract that would nullify it as soon as they were relegated." Chang Xiang said.　

Yes, clauses that cancelled the contract once the team was relegated. Whether it was sponsors or players, these types of automatic clauses would show up. However, those were for mid-tier and bottom-tier teams. For a powerhouse like Excellent Era, adding in that sort of clause was an insult. How could Excellent Era get relegated? Not long before, no one thought it was possible. As a result, whether it was sponsors or players, no one would be concerned about adding in this clause in the contract. It was a groundless fear!

"Haha, the vast majority didn't, but there are exceptions." Cao Guangcheng said.

"Could you mean Dry Tea Green..." Chang Xian realized what Cao Guangcheng was getting at and immediately checked the data.

"We don't have any of the details of the contract here, but I know that the contract between Dry Tea Green and Excellent Era has always included this clause. However, in season nine, even though the contract could be cancelled because of the clause, they did not cease their sponsorship. They only reduced the sponsorship amount. This at least shows their determination in sponsoring Glory!"

Chang Xian nodded his head. Cao Guangcheng's words were reasonable. But after looking at the data some more, he asked again: "But this Dry Tea Green….... Their sponsorship amount isn't really that high!"

"Dry Tea Green is determined to sponsor Glory, yet the sponsorship amount isn't high. What does this mean? It means that there's room for negotiation! After Excellent Era won three championships in a row, they fell on the decline. Their performance was just passable. But Happy has instantly become famous. Their reputation is rising accordingly. There really is an opportunity for them to get a deal with Dry Tea Green." Cao Guangcheng said.

"You're too right!" Chang Xian was excited. He sincerely hoped the best for Happy. After organizing the information, he immediately called Chen Guo, sending her this information, while stressing the name Dry Tea Green.　

Dry Tea Green…...

Chen Guo grew up in City H. She was very familiar with this name. Saying that she grew up drinking their tea was a bit too much, but she had the circumstances to. Chen Guo just didn't really like it that much, that's all.

In the beginning, Dry Tea Green was focused solely on tea drinks, but they had expanded their market into all sorts of areas now. Their tea drinks were still their most popular products though, especially in City H. This company's strength didn't need to be mentioned. If Team Happy could get a sponsorship from them, that would be a huge step forward!

Chen Guo asked about everything she could from Chang Xian. After hanging up, she smugly started to prepare her attack.

According to Lou Guanning's analysis, Team Happy just needed to wait for sponsorships to come knocking on their door. However, Chen Guo wanted to be more proactive.

Dry Tea Green was their first target! Chang Xian had told her who to contact. Chen Guo immediately contacted him. The person on the other end was clearly just an assistant or secretary responsible for taking calls. After hearing Chen Guo's purpose for calling, the secretary was slightly startled and seemed to ask someone for more instructions. Then, the secretary gave Chen Guo a reply: tomorrow at 9 AM.

Not bad!

The other side had quickly arranged for a meeting. It looked like the other side was very interested in sponsoring them. Chang Xiang's recommendation was good. This Dry Tea Green valued sponsoring Glory quite a bit!

Chen Guo excitedly returned to Upper Forest Park and told the news to Ye Xiu.

"Dry Tea Green?" Ye Xiu heard the name and wrinkled his brow.

"What's wrong?" Chen Guo was a bit confused about Ye Xiu's response.

"I'll go with you tomorrow to take a look." Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?"

"How did you think to contact them?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Little Chang recommended them." Chen Guo said.

"LIttle Chang?" Ye Xiu was surprised, "Why did he recommend them?"

Chen Guo told him what Chang Xiang said. Ye Xiu nodded his head: "That's reasonable!"

"Yeah! Then let's go tomorrow morning. We can't be late." Chen Guo said. 　　

"Understood." Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Chen Guo excitedly logged into Glory and started playing. As for Ye Xiu, his QQ blinked. He saw a message from Su Mucheng.

"Dry Tea Green?"

"Yeah... we'll take a look tomorrow and then we'll see." Ye Xiu replied.　　

"Okay." Su Mucheng didn't say anything more.

The next morning, Chen Guo dragged Ye Xiu out the door. She didn't want to leave a bad impression on the other side by being late. But when the two arrived at Dry Tea Green, it was only 8:30 AM. After being guided by the receptionist, the two came to Dry Tea Green's external affairs department. The person to receive them was the person who had picked up Chen Guo's call yesterday. Because it wasn't yet the appointment time, the secretary arranged for the two to wait a bit at the lobby.

Everything seemed to be going well, so Chen Guo was very excited.

"External affairs... hm, will we need this type of department in the future?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

"Of course." Ye Xiu nodded his head.　

Time passed. In the blink of an eye, it was 9 AM. Chen Guo was looking forward to it, but then that secretary came back on time with an apologetic look: "Sorry.... Mr. Xiazong still has some business to take care of. I'll have to ask you two to wait just a bit longer."

"Oh... no worries. We'll wait then. Thanks!" A thread of disappointment flashed across Chen Guo's face, but it disappeared soon. It was just a bit longer. It was nothing.　　

"Then let's wait a bit!" After the secretary left, Chen Guo let out an expression of disappointment and then sat back down.

"This meeting... it's best if you don't put too much hopes on it." Ye Xiu suddenly said.

"Why?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"Do you know who the Mr. Xiaozong she mentioned is?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Yeah!" Chen Guo nodded her head, "Xia Zongtian, Dry Tea Green's external affairs director. Dry Tea Green is his Xia family's business. He's the son of Dry Tea Green's CEO Xia Dongnan. More importantly, he's a huge Glory fan."

"Correct." Ye Xiu nodded his head, "He's a Glory fan. What's more, he's a very loyal Team Excellent Era fan."

"Oh?" Chen Guo was slightly surprised. Even though she hadn't realized anything, she could feel that Ye Xiu was hinting at something.

"How much do you know about Dry Tea Green's sponsorship for Excellent Era?" Ye Xiu asked.

"They've been sponsors for seven years, starting from season three of the Glory Alliance. Dry Tea Green's sponsorship for Excellent Era has never stopped even when Excellent Era was relegated this season. Despite having a clause saying that they could null the contract after the team was relegated, they insisted on sponsoring them and only reduced the sponsorship by a bit." Chen Guo said.　

"Correct..." Ye Xiu nodded his head, "Then what if I told you that Dry Tea Green's sponsorship for Excellent Era is actually Xiao Zongtian's personal decision. What would you think?"

"Personal decision?" Chen Guo was puzzled.　　

"Yes... in reality, the company Dry Tea Green doesn't have much interest in sponsoring a Glory team. However, Xiao Zongtian is a big fan of Glory and also a loyal Excellent Era fan, so he stood his ground against everyone else and insisted on sponsoring Excellent Era. Dry Tea Green is the Xia family's business, so the department turned a blind eye towards it and approved his request. You can say that this sponsorship isn't a business contract, but rather a fan's personal support for the team." Ye Xiu said.

"Why do you know so much?" Chen Guo was astonished.　

"Hello? If I remember correctly, I was once Team Excellent Era's former captain?" Ye Xiu said.

"So you're saying that apart from Excellent Era, Dry Tea Green isn't interested in supporting any team other than Excellent Era?" Chen Guo said.

"Yes." Ye Xiu nodded his head.

"Then why did Little Chang strongly recommend Dry Tea Green?"　　

"Uh, he's probably too young and didn't understood this crux of the matter!" Ye Xiu said, "From the surface, a sponsorship from Dry Tea Green truly has a lot of potential."

"Then why were we called over?"

"I'm puzzled about that too." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo had originally been excited, but now she was nervous. In the blink of an eye, it was 10 AM. In terms of their appointment time, they had waited for an entire hour.

"Xiazong, they've already waited for an hour. Shouldn't you meet them?" In Xiao Zongtian's office, the secretary asked.

"No time. I'm busy. Have them wait some more." Xiao Zongtian didn't even glance at his secretary. He just looked at the screen as sounds of mouse-clicking and keyboard-tapping sounded incessantly.

Chapter 1069: Xia Zhongtian

Ten turned to eleven. Eleven turned to twelve.

The entire morning passed, and there were still no signs of Xia Zhongtian. Meanwhile, his secretary appeared before Ye Xiu and Chen Guo for the fourth time already, telling them awkwardly: "It's already noon. Mr. Zhong told you two to come by again in the afternoon."

"Oh? The afternoon? What time in the afternoon?" Chen Guo asked.

"We have a meeting in the afternoon." The secretary replied deftly. She did not say when Xia Zhongtian would meet with them. She only said that there would be a meeting in the afternoon.

"Miss Wang, sorry to trouble you." Chen Guo smiled at the secretary, who was putting on a fake smile. Chen Guo had started managing the Internet cafe in her teens. The industry that she fought in wasn't very high-end, but she had at least experienced many things. After hearing about the history behind Ch'ien Tea Green's sponsorship for Excellent Era from Ye Xiu and seeing that the other side wasn't sincere at all, calling him over was mostly likely just to play with them.

"Then please make yourselves at home." The secretary smiled apologetically and left first. Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu and sighed. The two got up.

As they left, they walked past the external affair offices. Secretary Wang's office was just outside the door. She heard a phone call, entered the room, and when she went out of the room, she saw the two of them. She gave a smile and nodded her head.

"Miss Wang, do you know what Xia Zhongtian was busy with this morning?" Ye Xiu suddenly asked.　

Secretary Wang was surprised by the question, but she quickly put on a professional smile: "I'm afraid that it's not convenient to say."

"Haha, he's just playing Glory. What's not convenient?" Ye Xiu laughed.

Secretary Wang was stunned. It was obvious that Ye Xiu was correct. Chen Guo had originally been pondering over whether they should come back in the afternoon. Maybe Xia Zhongtian really had been busy and was testing their sincerity? But now it looked like that guy was actually playing Glory the entire morning, intentionally having them wait there. She immediately became angry. If he didn't want to sponsor them, it would only take a few words to tell them. Instead, he felt the need to bully them. What's up with that? Chen Guo stepped forward. Accompanied by a shout from Secretary Wang "What are you doing?", she arrived at Xia Zhongtian's office and pushed the door open.

"What is it now?" Xiao Zhongtian was sitting behind his desk. The monitor on his desk was at least 42 inches. His head was buried behind it. He couldn't be seen at all. When he heard the door open, he didn't even peak his head out to look. He simply asked a question.

"I'm Team Happy's boss." Chen Guo huffed.

"Didn't I tell you to come again in the afternoon? I'm busy here!" Xia Zhongtian didn't even tilt his head.

"Busy with what? You're almost dead." Ye Xiu also walked in with Chen Guo and suddenly spoke up.　　

"Sorry, Xiaozhong. I'll lead them out immediately." Secretary Wang chased after them in a panic and apologized to Xia Zhongtian first.

Xia Zhongtian didn't utter a word. The sounds of keyboard taps and mouse clicking intensified, but soon afterwards, the noise suddenly came to a halt.

"It's fine. You can go. This has nothing to do with you." Xia Zhongtian suddenly said. The secretary, who was urging Chen Guo and Ye Xiu to get out, was surprised. She quietly left the room and closed the door.

Xia Zhongtian's head finally peaked out from the monitor. He glanced at the two of them. Arrogance hung on his face: "Hey, if it isn't Ye Qiu. Wait, no, God Ye Xiu! What a rare guest!"　　

Xia Zhongtian held a long face and spoke in a weird tone of voice. It was as if he was trying hard to put on a mocking look. Chen Guo looked at this young person. He was like her back then. He was a big Glory fan and a big Excellent Era fan. He took advantage of his business to sponsor Excellent Era. Even though he was a bit capricious, his love and passion for Glory and Excellent Era easily showed.

This type of person probably wasn't a bad person.

Chen Guo didn't know why, but that was what she felt. Even after Xia Zhongtian made them wait the entire morning and despite his disrespectful attitude, Chen Guo realized that she really couldn't feel disgusted towards him.　

"You want a sponsor? One word, no. You can go." There was no point toying around with Happy any longer, so he directly expressed his position.

"Don't be like that, Mr. Xia. It wasn't easy for us to make this trip here. We've waited for so long. Why not at least hear us out?" Chen Guo suddenly said.

This reply surprised Ye Xiu. He had thought that with Chen Guo's personality, she would definitely start arguing furiously with Xia Zhongtian. However, instead, she displayed this kind of attitude. She still wasn't giving up and still wanted to fight for a sponsor? Xia Zhongtian wasn't a normal Excellent Era fan. As someone who grew up in City H, apart from the normal dedication of a fan, he also had pride for his region. His support for Excellent Era was entirely for this team alone and would never change. He was undoubtedly an extremely loyal Excellent Era fan. Even until today, he detested Ye Xiu and hated Happy. Getting him to change his mind and support Happy would be extremely difficult. Even though Chen Guo was brave and did what she said she would do, Ye Xiu also knew that persuasion wasn't her strong point.

"Alright, go ahead! In any case, my decision isn't going to change. You can waste your time." Xia Zhongtian said expressionlessly. Then, his two hands started to move again. His actions clearly expressed: you can say yours, I'll play mine. No matter what you say, my final answer will be: no.

Chen Guo didn't seem to care and started speaking: "Then I'll be speaking. Um, let me first tell you about our Happy Internet Cafe's history! Our Happy Internet Cafe..."

Chen Guo really did start talking. After a few words, Ye Xiu laughed inwardly. This Chen Guo was great. She didn't have any intentions of persuading the other side. Happy Internet Cafe's history? Was there a need? Not at all! Happy Internet Cafe's history would have absolutely no impact on the other side's decision towards Team Happy. Almost half an hour had passed since she started talking, and Chen Guo was at Happy Internet Cafe's third year, when she was six!

Boss Chen wasn't at the level where her words were sharp enough to leave the other side speechless, but her ability to tell a long-winded story wasn't weak. It wasn't easy for someone to remember all those small details so clearly and then say it to Xia Zhongtian in a serious tone.

Was this requesting a sponsorship?

Of course not!

This was entirely to annoy Xia Zhongtian. Using rambling to waste Xiao Zongtinan's time as revenge for making her and Ye Xiu wait the entire morning.

This method was kind of stupid. She was harming herself, wasting her own voice. But did it cause any real damage to the other side?

It did...

Ye Xiu knew very clearly. He could easily tell by listening. He didn't even need to look. During this half hour, Xia Zhongtian was still playing Glory, most likely PKing in the Arena. However, his playing was a mess. For someone who loved Glory for so many years, even if he wasn't at a pro level, he should at least be somewhat skilled. His movements should at least have some sort of rhythm and strategy to them. However Xia Zhongtian didn't have any at all. It was a complete mess. It was as if he didn't know what he was doing at all. He clearly wasn't focused because of a certain person rambling nonsense the entire time. 　　

He obviously didn't want to hear it, but when her voice drilled into his ears, his brain couldn't help but listen to the contents. Once he started listening, his attention became split, messing up his playing. He played match after match. During these past thirty minutes, Xia Zhongtian played at a speed of one match every three minutes and lost every single one of them. He gave an irritated and furious glare at Chen Guo, but he didn't say anything to stop her. It seemed like he was planning on competing with Chen Guo. As a result, he pulled out his ace and turned up the sound.

This ace was too powerful for Chen Guo. She couldn't do anything about it and stopped talking.

Xia Zhongtian was delighted. In reality, his earphones didn't have sound. This was his office, after all. Even though he was the manager, he couldn't play games too openly. Even if it was just for a few minutes, he had to turn down the sound. He needed to listen for any matters that he needed to deal with even during break time. As a result, when Xia Zhongtian played Glory in his office, he never played with sound. Because of this, he dared to play games during work time. It never hindered his work, so no one could say anything about it. Of course, Ch'ien Tea Green was his Xia family's business. This point alone was more important than his work not being hindered by him playing games.

Putting on these headphones was enough for this woman to shut up. Xia Zhongtian felt a feeling of victory from his trick succeeding. As for Chen Guo, after being hit by this blow, she felt a bit dispirited. She looked around and discovered that Ye Xiu had left the room already. Chen Guo immediately got up. Xia Zhongtian saw that she was about to leave and pretended not to see as if she were just air. Chen Guo only just opened the door when she saw that Ye Xiu was right outside the door playing Glory at Secretary Wang's desk.

"You!" Chen Guo felt helpless, "Where is she?"

"She went out for lunch! I asked her if I could use her computer to play some Glory. She said I could." Ye Xiu. The boss liked the game so much, so the secretary couldn't help but follow along. It wasn't just her. Everyone in the external affairs office followed along. If you looked around, you would see Glory card readers at every desk.

"We're done here, let's go!" Chen Guo said.

"What's wrong? You ran out of things to say?" Ye Xiu asked with a grin.

"That guy's put on his headphones." Chen Guo said.

"It looks like it's my time to shine!" Ye Xiu said.

"What do you mean?" Chen Guo was startled. When she looked at Ye Xiu's screen, his character had squeezed into the Arena. He was only spectating though. At this moment, an open spot appeared, and Ye Xiu quickly took it.

"Who's this guy?" Chen Guo pointed at Ye Xiu's opponent on the screen.

Ye Xiu pointed inside the room.

"That's... that's too evil!!" Chen Guo cried out. At the same time, she started thinking. Were those two here to get a sponsor or were these two here to bully each other?

Chapter 1070: Off to a Bad Start

Xia Zhongtian was one of Excellent Era's sponsors, and he himself also played Glory. His character obviously wasn't any sort of secret to Excellent Era's people, so it was no secret to the former captain of Excellent Era, Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu took the secretary's computer and logged in with a random account card before searching for Xia Zhongtian's character in the arena, easily finding his room. The moment the Xia Zhongtian's opponent left the room, he resolutely placed his own character in the arena.

Which smurf was Ye Xiu using? Chen Guo didn't bother checking because it wouldn't affect the result. No matter what class he used, it would all just be bullying noobs for Ye Xiu, no? In that moment, Chen Guo began to feel sorry for the person inside the room. Compared to her own rambling, this was probably a far harsher attack. Chen Guo could guess that Ye Xiu wouldn't go too easy on him.

As expected, Chen Guo had just reached this conclusion when a round had been finished. Chen Guo glanced at the time. Thirty seconds? Or was it even less?

In the blink of an eye, the second round began. Chen Guo couldn't even bear to watch the process. It was like watching an adult hit a kid. Anyone with a conscience wouldn't be able to admire the process. They would only find it cruel and inhumane.

　

The second round quickly ended, and then the third began...

Chen Guo felt like she could hear the frustrated breaths through the door.

Xia Zhongtian had been a Glory fan for so long already, so even if he had no talent whatsoever, his skill wouldn't be too bad. In the online game, he had probably never lost so badly. As a sponsor, he might have fought a pro level match before, but being a sponsor meant that Excellent Era's players would take it easy on him.

However… Ye Xiu was merciless this time!

In the time that these thoughts had taken place, Xia Zhongtian had lost his sixth match already.

　　

Chen Guo's rambling had distracted him, causing him to lose a match in three minutes. Now that Ye Xiu had personally gotten onto the field, Xia Zhongtian managed to lose six matches in three minutes. From this, it could be seen that there was definitely a reasoning behind the saying that one shouldn't make empty promises, but act on them.

　　

Five minutes went by rapidly and Xia Zhongtian had already lost ten matches.

Five minutes, ten matches lost.

Chen Guo, as a fellow Glory gamer, could easily imagine Xia Zhongtian's current state of mind. But this guy was rather stubborn too. He had been beaten so badly, and there was an obvious disparity in skill, but he still refused to give up, unwilling to leave the room and fighting match after match.

Another five minutes passed...

The phone on the secretary's desk rang with a ringtone dedicated specifically for the boss. Ye Xiu picked the call up casually. "What?"

"How come my lunch isn't here yet!" Xia Zhongtian didn't seem to realize that the person picking up didn't have his secretary's voice at all.

"You've lost so many times and you can still eat?" Ye Xiu asked.

Silence fell. Then, Chen Guo heard the sound of a chair moving. Looking into the room, she saw that Xia Zhongtian had finally stood up, walking around his wide desk and out of the room.

"It was you just now?" Xia Zhongtian came out of the room and saw Ye Xiu where his secretary should've been. Glory was running on the computer. Even though he hadn't seen Ye Xiu's character, he wasn't dumb. It wasn't hard to guess.

Ye Xiu smiled, but didn't say anything.

"My skill level is that bad?" Xia Zhongtian looked incredulous.

"It's not that bad," Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo and Xia Zhongtian were both struck speechless. What this person was implying was obviously that he was too strong. That was just too arrogant. However, no one could retort to his arrogance. This was Ye Xiu, a God at the peak of Glory. If he were humble and said something like he wasn't so good, wasn't so powerful, then that would be equal to slapping the faces of all Glory players. If you weren't powerful, then what would we all be?

　

"Mr. Xia, do you want to continue?" Ye Xiu asked.

"No need," Xia Zhongtian replied. He wasn't a masochist.

"How about our discussions?" Ye Xiu asked.

"There's no need for that either…" Xia Zhongtian looked at Chen Guo with a hint of anxiousness. It seemed like Chen Guo's scolding of him just now did have its impact.

"Well, since your lunch still hasn't arrived, how about we all sit and talk it out?" Ye Xiu suggested.

"Is there a need? I feel that you know that I will never sponsor Happy. I find it strange that you would come." Xia Zhongtian said.

"As Xia Zhongtian, you definitely couldn't, but as the head of Ch'ien Tea Green's Marketing Department, I feel like this is quite a good chance," Ye Xiu said.

Xia Zhongtian paused for a moment, digesting that.

Xia Zhongtian not sponsoring Happy was because he personally couldn't accept it. However, from a business perspective, with the amount of attention Happy was receiving recently, they were a great sponsorship choice. Especially for Ch'ien Tea Green.

This was because the relationship between Excellent Era and their other sponsors was purely about business. They gave a sponsorship and naturally hoped that Excellent Era would do their best to promote their products. However, Ch'ien Tea Green was different. Since their sponsorship was more of Xia Zhongtian's personal desire, the company didn't sponsor them much, and they didn't require much from Excellent Era either. Even the most loyal local fans of Excellent Era probably didn't know that that their local famed company Ch'ien Tea Green was one of the sponsors of the team they loved.

The sponsorship given by Ch'ien Tea Green was frankly like an expenditure a rich young master had made on a whim. The money had been spent and he was satisfied. He had never hoped to profit from it. This sponsorship hadn't gained any influence so it was perfectly alright for Ch'ien Tea Green to turn around and sponsor Happy instead. They weren't like the other main sponsors of Excellent Era who had to carefully consider things if they wanted to sponsor Happy.

Xia Zhongtian was the head of external affairs so he had a professional eye for these things. It was just that when it came to Glory, to Excellent Era, he liked to act on his emotions. With Ye Xiu's reminder, he realized that, from business perspective, the current Happy truly was a good sponsorship choice. If he wrote up a feasible and professional report, the board might even accept it.

　

In that instant, Xia Zhongtian began to consider this from a professional perspective. However, as he began to think of the practical execution, he remembered how Excellent Era was facing disbandment, and that all this was the personal handiwork of the very team in front of him, lead by the man in front of him. Xia Zhongtian's rationality immediately burned away.

"I refuse," he said without a hint of emotion. He wanted Happy's people to feel frustrated. Although I can't influence much, at the very least, you won't be able to get a sponsorship from me. This was the only thing I can make you do in punishment for your deeds. That was what Xia Zhongtian thought.

　

"I see, what a shame. You've missed a good opportunity." Ye Xiu said.

"Don't worry, Ch'ien Tea Green has plenty of marketing channels," Xia Zhongtian replied aloofly.

"Oh, then how do you plan to end your sponsorship with Excellent Era?" Ye Xiu asked.

"You actually have the audacity to ask that?" Xia Zhongtian's cold demeanor melted immediately, replaced by the flames of anger. In his heart, it didn't matter what had brought Excellent Era to where they were now along the way, but Ye Xiu and Happy had given Excellent Era the final blow. This blow was the reason he couldn't forgive Ye Xiu and Happy. Even though he had gleaned the intricacies of these events from news reports, this would only fill him with disdain for Tao Xuan, but it wouldn't influence his hatred of Ye Xiu and Happy for their finishing blow.

"That's what competition is. You give and you gain. Why wouldn't I have the audacity?" Ye Xiu asked.

Xia Zhongtian didn't know how to reply. In reality, that wasn't what he wanted to express. The reason he didn't like Ye Xiu and Happy was just because they had given Excellent Era its finishing blow. In regards to how Ye Xiu used to be a member of Excellent Era and got kicked out before striking back, he didn't really feel anything. That meant, for him, in this victory and defeat, Ye Xiu was just like any other player. They won and Excellent Era fell, so he hated them, that was how simple it was.

For Ye Xiu's victory, only the competition mattered.

　

For Xia Zhongtian's hate, it was in reality only about the competition as well.

"Excellent Era needs help. Perhaps you could find a chance," Ye Xiu said.

"Me?" The topic brought up, Xia Zhongtian still seemed bitter. "I hope so, too, but unfortunately I don't have that ability."

"You will. You just need the right opportunity," Ye Xiu said.

"What do you mean?" Xia Zhongtian was taken aback.

"Excellent Era is currently dismantling and selling parts of its assets." What Ye Xiu said was the nightmare of any Excellent Era fan. "I hope that it's most important part won't be dismantled."

"Let's go!" Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

"Oh…" Chen Guo made a sound of agreement but felt that it was quite a shame. There had been a moment where Chen Guo saw that Xia Zhongtian had been seriously and rationally considering sponsoring Happy. She had held a flicker of hope, but unfortunately, Xia Zhongtian still refused in the end. As expected of a huge Excellent Era fan. In the end, he couldn't get over the fact that Happy had struck down Excellent Era. Chen Guo couldn't argue against this because Xia Zhongtian cared solely about the competition and the results. He made this decision because of the outcome. Unless they changed the outcome of that match, they wouldn't be able to change his mind, and unfortunately that was impossible.

"We're off to a bad start…" After leaving Ch'ien Tea Green, Chen Guo, who had kept on speaking for a full half hour, was melting under the sun. She bought two drinks from a vending machine and threw one bottle to Ye Xiu before rapidly downing half of her own bottle. Then she took a look at the packaging, Ch'ien Tea Green.

Ye Xiu didn't seem affected and twisted the bottle open to drink. "Don't worry about it. There's no reason for us to lack sponsors, it's just that you chose an impossible mission from the get go. It's just looking to fail!"

"That brat, Little Chang, I'll show him!" Chen Guo's aggro switched targets and she immediately took out her phone to dial Chang Xian. Speaking of, although they had been firmly rejected by Xia Zhongtian, she still couldn't bring herself to hate him.

In the end, it was all because of his love for the game. He was no different from Chen Guo, Ye Xiu and everyone else who loved Glory.

Chapter 1071: Tyranny’s Rookie

Chen Guo said she was going to scold Chang Xian, but she was just saying it. Chang Xian had good intentions, although it was rather depressing that his help ended up doing no good. Chen Guo and Ye Xiu had wasted time and effort going there to not get a sponsor, but they didn't lose anything either, so it wasn't too bad.

So in the call, Chen Guo still expressed her gratitude before giving a simple explanation of why they couldn't get the sponsorship from Ch'ien Tea Green. Then, she asked if Chang Xian had any other recommendations.

Cao Guangcheng, who was listening in, knew that Happy had wasted their time on this and basked in secret delight. He had been Excellent Era's team reporter for all these years, so he naturally knew what the deal with Ch'ien Tea Green was and what kind of person Xia Zhongtian was. He knew from the beginning that Happy wouldn't get anything from Xia Zhongtian. From the phone call, it sounded as if Xia Zhongtian had asked them to visit. This was unexpected. He had thought it would be pretty good if Happy just got no response. He hadn't thought Xia Zhongtian would have called them to visit. He definitely managed to mess with Happy.

Cao Guangcheng found it unfortunate that he couldn't have witnessed it in person. He could only imagine it himself to cheer himself up. He had no idea that although Ye Xiu and Chen Guo had been stood up at their scheduled appointment, in return, they had also bullied Xia Zhongtian for a good while.

Chang Xian wasn't an idiot either. He didn't know about the situation regarding Ch'ien Tea Green, but Cao Guangcheng had followed Excellent Era for so long, so how could he have been ignorant to this? Chang Xian had realized that this was Cao Guangcheng's little trick. But even if he knew, he couldn't do anything about it. Nothing would be gained by arguing about it. Except that this time, he wouldn't ask this senior. After agreeing to Chen Guo's request, he prepared to take a look over things himself.

With what had occured, Chang Xian realized that it wouldn't be easy for Happy to take Excellent Era's sponsors. However, Chang Xian was clever. If it wasn't convenient for Excellent Era's sponsors to sponsor Happy because of Happy defeating Excellent Era, then what about these sponsors' competitors? If they sponsored Happy, wouldn't that be a win-win situation?

Competition was omnipresent, even in business. Chang Xian decided to bring his thoughts in a different direction and went to look for the competitors of Excellent Era's sponsors. However, this was outside of Chang Xian's area of control. This information wasn't something that Chang Xian had at hand, so it would be slower. Yet he hadn't even managed to do anything before Happy received their first phone call that expressed interest in sponsoring them.

　　而这电话的来处,则正好证明了常先思路的正确性.

This phone call also managed to justify the logic in Chang Xian's thought process.

Feike.

This was a well-known computer peripheral brand with their keyboards and mouse being the most famous. These two things were doubtlessly the sharpest tool for esports athletes. With how the Glory Alliance flourished, it would be strange if they didn't sponsor anyone. In reality, Feike was already sponsoring a team in the Alliance.

Tyranny!

The team Feike was currently sponsoring was Team Tyranny, who many thought would win the championships. In addition, Feike was the archrival of a peripheral device company sponsoring Excellent Era, Speed Serpent. Speed Serpent chose Excellent Era and Feike chose Tyranny. The sponsors were archenemies as well. What Feike was thinking of when they chose to sponsor Happy was clear as day.

Feike's headquarters weren't in City H. After getting in contact through the call, Feike and Happy had two video meetings to negotiate the sponsorship. Although Happy was a hot topic right now, their fame and influence was nothing compared to Tyranny and Feike's contract for Happy showed their caution. The contract would be a year long for 1,500,000 RMB along with the request that their sponsorship would be put above all others.

The year length of the contract was clearly a representation of Feike's wait-and-see attitude to Happy's continued survival in the Alliance. The request to be considered above all other sponsors showed that they actually had quite a bit of optimism towards this. As for the one and a half million, it wasn't much if you considered the entirety of the Glory circle, but for a team that had just arrived in the Alliance, it was a considerable amount. This was all thanks to how Happy managed to defeat Excellent Era and gain public attention. Otherwise, for other teams that had managed to fight their way back into the Alliance, it wasn't unheard of for them to be completely ignored.

After negotiating back and forth for a while, the sponsorship money was eventually raised to 1,800,000 RMB. The other requirements didn't change. Both sides were very satisfied with this contract. Then, the time came to officially sign the contract. Although this was a small contract, Feike wanted to use Happy's current popularity to hold a press conference for the contract signing. However, the playoffs were still ongoing, and the Glory circle was focused on the competition, so this sort of promotional activity had to be delayed.

　

After completing the contract with Feike, the business doors to Happy were completely opened. They received more and more calls inquiring about sponsorship. Chang Xian had managed to compile a list of worthwhile sponsors, but by then, Chen Guo was already too busy to initiate any attacks. Just the sponsors that were calling was already making her more than busy. Some were sincere, but some were there to try and profit in the chaos. Some even tried to bully Happy through Happy's lack of experience by directly tricking or scamming them. Some even had no idea what was happening and just called to be a part of the action. Chen Guo was finally finding the feel of running a pro team and being the boss. She hadn't really done much in the past.

At the same time, the playoffs were already at the semifinals. Tyranny versus Tiny Herb, Samsara versus Wind Howl.

The first match was Team Tiny Herb's home game against Team Tyranny.

Team Tiny Herb had gone through a lot of changes this year. The All-Star level account Flying Drops had been sold to Samsara and Tiny Herb's lineup lost a Grappler. The original player of Flying Drops, Li Yihui, had also left the team in summer. Xu Bin, the Grind King from 301 Degrees had taken over the retired Deng Fusheng's Knight, Angelica, and managed to become an All-Star with his excellent performances. Then, prodigy Gao Yingjie had debuted this season, becoming a part of the Witch Duo with his captain, Wang Jiexi. There was also the hand speed expert, Liu Xiaobie, who had grown into a very dependable player. He had been mere steps away from becoming an All-Star this season. Team Tiny Herb was almost had a four All-Star lineup.

As for Tyranny, it wasn't just four All-Stars, but four top Gods of their classes. The only one who was in a little awkward of a position was Lin Jingyan. The other three still counted as the top of their respective classes.

With this lineup, curiosity towards the person in the other position of their starting lineup was aroused.

Since the team competition needed five people to fight at once, who would be the fifth person who stood beside the four gods?

In the summer transfer window, since they were bringing in powerful aces and changing up their lineup, a lot of Tyranny's players and accounts had left. From that time on, everyone had been wondering who would appear beside these four gods, but the one who appeared was a person that no one was familiar with.

Qin Muyun.

Before this season, no one had ever heard this name. He was such a plain and obscure player, yet he had become the last puzzle piece in Tyranny's starting lineup.

Qin Muyun had come from Tyranny's training camp. He hadn't had any sort of fame before this and he was already 21 when he became a part of Tyranny's starting lineup.

This debuting age was rather late. Compared to Lu Hanwen who wasn't even of age yet, he should've been a senior, but now, they were rookies of the same generation.

Qin Muyun had a Sharpshooter character and in this position, Tyranny originally had Wang Chixuan. Wang Chixuan wasn't a God, but he was still a very good player. However, Tyranny still decided to pick Qin Muyun from the training camp, while Wang Chixuan left in the summer transfer window.

What was special about this Qin Muyun? What allowed him to squeeze out this skilled, experienced Wang Chixuan, who was also familiar with the team, making him a core member of the team that stood next to these four Gods?

Everyone held high expectations for Qin Muyun, but soon enough, they were all disappointed.

Qin Muyun gave no striking performances on the field, and the data from each match seemed to point out that he was normal. He was just a very average player.

Soon enough, no one paid him any attention any longer. Rookie? There were more striking rookies this season. Wasn't Team Blue Rain's 14 year old Lu Hanwen a riot right now?

Thus, if you asked who Qin Muyun was, most players would probably shake their heads in confusion.

This was the media, the public's attitude.

However, pro teams wouldn't do this. They wouldn't underestimate any opponents, especially in the playoffs, especially a core member of a team like Tyranny.

Qin Muyun's data was very average, but don't forget who he's standing next to.

Apart from Zhang Xinjie, who was a Cleric, Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan weren't just normal All-Star players. In their old teams, they were all core DPSers. Next to people like that, what sort of data are you expecting a rookie to the pro league to have?

The media and the players didn't think Qin Muyun important, but Tiny Herb wouldn't do that. A slight mistake might mean that their journey this year would be over.

Thus, against Qin Muyun, Tiny Herb put equal attention in research on him as the four Gods.

Often, in the data for this season, the reports concerning Qin Muyun always started with: this player's data is average but he hasn't met the Rookie's Block.

That's right, he hadn't met the Rookie's Block.

In all nine seasons, only two players had never met the Rookie's Block: Wang Jiexi and Sun Xiang.

Now, a third had appeared, but compared to the previous two, he had very average performances. His lack of Rookie's Block might be because of some objective reasons like, with Tyranny's lineup, the four Gods took too much attention from players and attacks.

Tiny Herb wouldn't reject this sort of possibility, and in reality, they hoped that this was the reason. Otherwise, if it was because Qin Muyun had some sort of hidden talent, then that might become the biggest variable in the match.

The unknown was always the scariest.

Chapter 1072: God of Healing

The public paid great attention to Tyranny and Tiny Herb's opening match. Happy Internet Cafe also continued its tradition of streaming the matches. However, it was no longer convenient for Ye Xiu and the others to watch in the Internet cafe with everyone else. After the Challenger League, they could all be considered famous. Although they couldn't be compared to Gods, getting surrounded on their home turf wouldn't be anything surprising. Thus, Happy stayed at home, using their projector to watch the first match of the semifinals.

By then, the group arena had finished and Team Tiny Herb won 5 to 4. It could be seen how intense the match was just from the results. Each team had fought to their last person.

The players took a break and the broadcast replayed a few spectacular moments from the group arena. Then, it was time for the team competition.

Tiny Herb's starting lineup consisted of Wang Jiexi and Gao Yingjie's Witches, Vaccaria and Kind Tree, Xu Bin's Knight Angelica, Liu Xiaobie's Blade Master, Flying Swords, and Yuan Boqing's Cleric, Aweto.

The player list wasn't anything surprising. This was Tiny Herb's typical starting lineup this season. However, those familiar with Tiny Herb would discuss these characters..

"They're using a Cleric!" There were plenty of voices discussing this.

This was because Team Tiny Herb had two healers, not just one. One was the Cleric in the lineup this time, Aweto, and the other was the character that had made great contributions to Tiny Herb's two championships, Paladin Wind Guard.

During Tiny Herb's two champion seasons, they had a player with the title God of Healing, Fang Shiqian. This player was a dual healer expert, and was immensely skilled in both healer classes. Using a different healer class depending on the circumstances and needs was a large part of Tiny Herb's strategy back then. A Cleric's attack support and a Paladin's defense, Fang Shiqian was able to flawlessly utilize both a more offensive-oriented Cleric and a more defensive-oriented Paladin.

However, in the two matches that brought them their championships as well as when Fang Shiqian was voted into the All-Stars, he had always appeared as Wind Guard's player. So, those who only looked at the data might forget his true identity. However, those who were familiar with Tiny Herb would never forget this point.

Tiny Herb had continued with this style even today. It was just a shame that a player like Fang Shiqian, who could reach the top in both classes, was a rare case. The successor Tiny Herb had found, Yuan Boqing, could also play both classes, but he couldn't reach Fang Shiqian's level. He had trained hard for two whole seasons, but had yet to make any breakthroughs. It always felt like the heart of their adaptable strategy wasn't always quite there. Was there really a value to this strategy anymore? This question had been subject to much debate.

Apart from the five starting players, the sixth player was Zhou Yebai's Ghostblade, Rangoon Creeper. When Qiao Yifan had still been present, Rangoon Creeper was still a pure Phantom Demon, but in accordance to the needs of the team this season, Rangoon Creeper had his skill points reset and became a Hybrid Sword and Phantom Ghostblade. Zhou Yebai seemed to be performing better with the Hybrid Ghostblade, too.

As for Tyranny, the starting five consisted of Han Wenqing's Striker, Desert Dust, Lin Jingyan's Brawler, Dark Thunder, Zhang Jiale's Spitfire, Hundred Dazzling Blossoms, Qin Muyun's Sharpshooter, Negative Nine Degrees, and Zhang Xinjie's Cleric Immovable Rock. Their sixth player was Bai Yanfei's Elementalist, Rota.

Neither lineup held any surprises; they were both using the same lineup they had stayed with throughout the regular season. In the regular season, each team had one victory against the other, both having won their home games. However, the playoffs used a headcount point system, so some went back and took a look at the detailed scoring in the team competitions for the two matches and found that the headcount for the two matches were completely the same as well.

As for the data on their matches prior to that, there was little use in looking that far back because both teams had gone through huge changes in the summer. As for the only matches they had fought this season, the only decisive factors to their victories seemed only to be the home advantage.

This was Tiny Herb's home stadium.

　　

Thus, they had won the group arena by a point, but no one could say how large the home advantage was just yet.

Next up was the team competition. Although the heart of Tiny Herb's Healer Switching Strategy was no longer present, the chosen healer class would still, to some extent, reveal their approach towards the current match.

Clerics focused on offense, Paladin focused on defense, so with the Cleric in the lineup this time, Team Tiny Herb was evidently aiming for a more offense-oriented playstyle. As soon as the match started, they pressed forward.

However, in Tyranny's lineup, Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale, Lin Jingyan and Zhang Xinjie hadall had quite a bit of experience fighting against Fang Shiqian. There was no one more familiar with this strategy of Tiny Herb's than them. Having experienced fighting Fang Shiqian and then experiencing Yuan Boqing, the four felt that it was shame that they evidently weren't on the same level.

Fang Shiqian's title was God of Healing, but in reality, his skill often made people forget he was a healer. His ability to attack and defend was much more troublesome to deal with.

As for Yuan Boqing, no matter if he used a Cleric or a Paladin, he played well, but the deepest impression that he gave people was of his healing.

This was where he differed from Fang Shiqian and the reason why it didn't feel like there was any value in Tiny Herb's use of this strategy.

Tyranny's veterans knew this very clearly. Against Yuan Boqing, they just had to treat him as a normal healer. They didn't think he'd have the ability to give support like Fang Shiqian could and make things hard for them.

The experience of these veterans helped them make a quick decision.

Experience was a treasure and it was the one treasure these veterans were most proud of.

However, experience could sometimes hinder you too because sometimes experience was outdated. This sort of experience wasn't correct for the present and therefore would cause errors in judgement.

The judgement made by Tyranny's veterans had erred this time.

The support from Yuan Boqing's Cleric was causing them trouble to the point that they were reminded of back when they used to fight against Fang Shiqian.

Had this player managed to grow so much?

The veterans of Tyranny were shocked, seeing the old God of Healing's aura around Yuan Boqing's Aweto.

This was an oversight and this sort of oversight would always have a price.

Tiny Herb won the team competition.

The headcount points weren't important any longer. Having already won the group arena, there was no need to calculate the points to know that Tiny Herb was the victor of the opening match.

Public opinion of Tyranny's chances at the championship title were highest this season, but being defeated by Team Tiny Herb wasn't exactly completely unexpected.

In the post-match press conference, the veterans of Tyranny seemed calm.

"Tiny Herb played well." There would always be words that needed to be said out of courtesy.

"Every person will achieve growth every season. Some are noticed but others are ignored." There was no explicit mention of anyone's name, but in reality, Tyranny was scolding themselves.

The lineup for Tiny Herb's team competition this year truly was full of the air of growth.

Gao Yingjie and Xu Bin were both first-timers in the All-Stars, so that didn't need explanation. Apart from them, Liu Xiaobie was no longer that player who brainlessly used his hand speed. He was only a step away from the All-Stars, too. Amongst this striking growth, Yuan Boqing had been overlooked. Had he managed to master the key to Fang Shiqin's title of God of Healing without notice?

"Everyone performed well this match, but Yuan Boqing's performance was the key to our victory. He performed amazingly with his support, suppressing our opponents. He guided us to victory this time." When Tiny Herb went up for the press conference, captain Wang Jiexi didn't bother hiding his admiration of Yuan Boqing's performance this time.

This was a surge that no one had ever expected before the match.

Everyone was more willing to look at those famous Gods or the players that had striking performances in the past. Qin Muyun was the silently ignored fifth, and Yuan Boqing was often overlooked.

The victory of this match had been decided by this overlooked player. Discussions about him continued throughout the night.

Then, the match on the following day was practically the antonym of Tiny Herb and Tyranny's match.

The one who was key to victory this time was the God that everyone had been paying attention to and eagerly waiting to see.

Zhou Zekai, it was still Zhou Zekai.

This extremely silent and shy player off the field had become an uncounterable presence on the field.

Everyone knew to take him seriously. Everyone was trying to find a way to deal with him. Everyone was making arrangements to counter him, but it was no use. The Zhou Zekai on the field was just ever-triumphant like that. Team Wind Howl had exhibited a fierce momentum in this season. Their ace player Tang Hao was a fearless person who could say "the junior will succeed the senior" in the Rookie Challenge. But they were defeated.

In their home game, Wind Howl was destroyed by Samsara.

　　

There was no need for much tactical analysis. Samsara's victory and Wind Howl's defeat only had one reason.

Uncounterable.

Zhou Zekai was uncounterable.

All the players that wanted to defeat him all ended up defeated by him. Those who wanted to suppress him with tactics would only end up the one being suppressed.

With this sort of defeat, Wind Howl could only accept it.

In the post-match press conference, captain Tang Hao only said one sentence: "Next time, we'll win."

This was determination. This was his attitude.

But, how would they win? No one could tell. Not even his teammates seemed to have much enthusiasm when Tang Hao said that. Did Tang Hao himself even believe what he was saying? People were doubtful.

The mighty Wind Howl had been dealt a direct hit by Samsara.

The team that most people were placing their bets on getting the championship, Tyranny, had been defeated because of an abrupt outbreak from an overlooked player.

The Four Heavenly King's combo wasn't undefeatable.

Zhou Zekai, on the other hand, really didn't seem to have a counter.

Who would the champions be?

Chapter 1073: Veterans and Rookies

T first round of the semifinals had cast a shadow over Team Tyranny, whose chances at the championship seemed to be the highest. Last year's champions, Team Samsara, had managed to take a firm step on their path to defend their championship with their impressive performance.

Soon enough, the second round of matches of the semifinals began and Tyranny and Samsara met Tiny Herb and Wind Howl respectively on their home turfs.

In the group arena, Team Tyranny won 5 to 3.

The veterans wouldn't fall just because of one loss. They had experienced too many victories and defeats, and no matter which one it was, it would become their motivation to go on.

The veterans performed powerfully in the group arena, ending it at their fourth player, Han Wenqing.

Then, in the team competition that followed, Yuan Boqing became a focal point. How would the player who had exhibited the air of the God of Healing last match perform this time?

In this match, Yuan Boqing used the Cleric Aweto once more.

Logically speaking, you would be more cautious and defensive in an away game, which suited a Paladin's style more, but Tiny Herb still chose to use a Cleric.

This was a sort of attitude. It seemed like Tiny Herb didn't want to drag this out to the third round. They wanted to take their final victory in this away game. They would probably fight even more fiercely in the team competition.

That's what everyone thought, but Tyranny didn't seem to think that way.

Was it another oversight?

　

Of course not, they were just continuing at their own pace, completely unaffected by their opponent's changes in tactics.

This time, they would pay more attention to Yuan Boqing's Cleric, but not too much. This was because they knew very clearly that Yuan Boqing wasn't Tiny Herb's core. Even if the actual God of Healing Fang Shiqian was on the field, Team Tiny Herb's core was still forever another.

Wang Jiexi, Vaccaria!

This was Team Tiny Herb's true core. Don't even dream of the veterans of Tyranny overlooking this order of importance.

At the beginning of the match, Tema Tyranny immediately launched a fierce assault. Under the cover of Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossom Style, Han Wenqing's Desert Dust darted into the enemy's formation.

Zhang Jiale managed to integrate himself into Tyranny extremely quickly, extremely smoothly. Some people said that this might have been because Tyranny's captain, Han Wenqing, had a very similar style to Zhang Jiale's old partner, Sun Zheping, so Zhang Jiale easily found a place on the field.

Then, whenever there would be the slightest opening, another figure would appear to patch it up.

Dark Thunder, Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder. Speaking of fame, Lin Jingyan was the one with the least fame in Tyranny's four Gods. Speaking of ability, he was also the one whose ability was slipping the most clearly, having already been surpassed by his junior. No longer being the tactical core, he had much more room and choice in his play. When there was Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossom Style to provide cover, he would hide within and throw a few sneak attacks. When Han Wenqing's Desert Dust couldn't come over, he could turn into an strong DPSer. The Brawler class was one that was suited to multiple styles and it's potential was fully unleashed under the hands of an old veteranlike Lin Jingyan.

Team Tyranny launched a powerful offense. They would no longer overlook any player in Tiny Herb, but they wouldn't cast away their own style aside either. They had to keep the tempo at their pace, otherwise they would be led around by the nose. Team Tyranny held the initiative from the very beginning, accumulating advantages and walking towards victory step by step. As for their Master Tactician, Zhang Xinjie carefully watched over the entire battlefield. He was like a machine, always making sure to minimize possible mistakes. This sort of healer was the most secure shield at your back.

Victory!

Tyranny eventually managed to earn back a victory on their home turf.

Yuan Boqing, who had been the center of focus before the match, had performed well as well. It was just that, this time, he wasn't a surprise for Tyranny anymore. To a group of people who had experience fighting Fang Shiqian, Quan Boqing wasn't an uncounterable presence for them.

　

In the post-match press conference, the words of Tiny Herb's captain, Wang Jiexi, were very cliche, but were also an accurate depiction of the match. "We played well, but our opponents did better."

Just like when the two teams fought in the regular season, neither side committed any serious mistakes that had clearly affected the victory of the match. Everyone had performed well, they exchanged blows, slowly accumulating their advantage until, in the end, Tiny Herb fell and Tyranny still stood.

Tiny Herb and Tyranny had fought to a tie, 1 to 1, and needed to use the third and last match to decide their victory. It would be held on Tyranny's turf, but they wouldn't have the right to choose the map.

In the other match of the second round of the semifinals, Samsara fought their home game against Wind Howl.

Wind Howl, who had lost their home game, was obviously not in the right headspace for this match. Although their captain Tang Hao had expressed a determined attitude after the last match, the fact that Team Wind Howl lacked playoffs experience was clear in this match. They weren't like Tyranny's veterans who could face a loss with such ease, their mindsets remaining unaffected. The young members of Wind Howl had been obviously over cautious and hesitant. Their uncertainty in tactical decisions were extremely apparent.

The Wind Howl of the regular season pressed forward with determination They were fearless, and their spirit was indomitable. However, in the playoffs, they began to become afraid. This was because the rules of the playoffs were different, A single loss might cut of their future path and turn all their efforts to dust. Now, they were standing at such a crossroads. Victory meant that they might be able to survive, but failure meant that everything would end there.

　

This sort of pressure wasn't something that was present in the regular season. They had managed a smooth journey in the first round of the playoffs, crushing Misty Rain in two rounds and entering the semifinals. That was all until they had lost their home game to Samsara in the first round of the semifinals. Team Wind Howl had suddenly fallen into a dire situation.

The pressure they were under caused the members of Wind Howl to panic. Even though they had a veteran like Fang Rui, he couldn't save the whole team. Fang Rui wasn't the head of this team, and his dirty playstyle wasn't one that gave him any advantage in boosting everyone's morale.

The second round ended in Team Wind Howl's defeat. Team Samsara walked towards the finals with their heads high and shoulders back, and Wind Howl? They had caught everyone's attention during this season, yet ended on such a pathetic note. All the players who hated Tang Hao's attitude were delighted.

However, Wind Howl was young, no matter if it was Tang Hao or Zhao Yuzhe, they still had plenty of time to fight for what they wanted. It all depended on if they could learn something from their defeat or not.

After two rounds of the semifinals, Samsara had managed to get into the finals, while Tiny Herb and Tyranny would have to duke it out in a third round.

　

After three days, the final match between the two began on Tyranny's turf and a foreign map. The two had been careful from the group arena, eventually fighting to each of their last members again. In the end, it was Tiny Herb that won 5 to 4, taking the lead.

Entering the team competition with a lead of 1 point was still some form of an advantage. However, in the team competition, Tiny Herb, who had the lead, seemed to be even more cautious than Tyranny.

On a foreign map, the two sides didn't rush to fight. The characters of both team were scattered across the map, but within supporting distance. It seemed that they were trying to get a hold of the terrain before striking.

After two minutes, the two sides still hadn't met, but they had swapped places. Tiny Herb's characters were all in Tyranny's half of the map while Tyranny's characters had all come to the side of the map Tiny Herb started on. Both sides continued to scout out the map.

The first contact between the two sides finally occurred then.

It only occurred, but it didn't erupt because the contact they had was rather shameless. Team Tyranny's Lin Jingyan had seen Tiny Herb's Aweto as he wandered across the map and dexterously hid his character, Dark Thunder. He didn't immediately find a chance to attack and carefully began to tail the other instead. At the same time, he kept up a string of messages to the team chat, reporting on what was occurring. Team Tyranny began to make a tactical movement. All the characters closed in on Aweto's position.

However, the audience could see with their omniscient view that even if Tyranny successfully trapped Aweto, they would only be able to steal the initiative. It wouldn't be so easily to take out Aweto in one wave. This was because Tiny Herb's characters weren't scattered at random. They were all within supporting distance. If anyone sent out a message for help. Other characters would be there to support them within seconds.

However, Team Tyranny's members weren't impatient either. Their characters arrived at the appointed positions one by one, but no one rushed forwards to attack. Even when all five had arrived, they were still adjusting their positions.

Tiny Herb's possible support was all within their expectations! Their current arrangement was made to restrict this sort of support. With these veterans, they would still pry out openings even if there were none. Now that this chance had appeared in front of them, they had to take hold of it firmly. Everything had to be prepared before they struck.

　

These adjustments without any sort of direct clash was boring to watch. However, any spectator with a bare minimum knowledge in Glory would feel the tension in this situation.

Was it time to strike?

They could strike, right?

Are they still not going to strike?

Countless spectators felt that the time was ripe again and again, but reality told them, again and again, that these veterans of Tyranny were far calmer than they. With these three veterans and the careful and precise Master Tactician Zhang Xinjie, did Team Tyranny intend to make a flawless arrangement?

There was no such thing as a flawless arrangement on the battlefield. What Zhang Xinjie hoped to do was simply minimize the chances of an accident occurring.

"Forward!" The order appeared into the chat.

Bang, the sound of a sniper rifle split the air. Qin Muyun had been aiming for a while now, and finally shot upon receiving this order.

With that gunshot, he was exposed. However, once the battle started, everyone would be exposed. Tyranny's arrangements were made to deal with what would happen after they were exposed. The five characters had already charged forth as one.

Chapter 1074: Tyranny’s Tempo

The spectators could see everything far more clearly than any of the players.

The ten characters had originally been scattered around the map, but after the gunshot, all of them suddenly headed towards the same location. In the blink of an eye, blossoms sprouted all around the map as battles formed. Only now did spectators realize Team Tyranny's intentions. Team Tyranny didn't seem to be targeting Team Tiny Herb's Cleric, Aweto. Their aim was to cut off Aweto's connection with everyone else. Battles had bloomed all over the map. Yuan Boqing suddenly discovered that there was nothing for him to do. Tyranny had led all of the conflicts away from him.

Where do I go?

For an instant, Yuan Boqing was faced with this question. There were sounds of battle all around him. Which location should he go assist?　

Fortunately, an order quickly came from the team chat. It wasn't just him. All of Team Tiny Herb was heading towards a single rendezvous point. Since Tyranny had started these waves of attacks, there was no need to question who held the initiative at the moment. Tiny Herb clearly didn't want to start a fight with Tyranny under these circumstances. If they did, they would only fall into Tyranny's tempo.

First, group up. Then, counterattack!

Wang Jiexi's decision was clear and precise, but it wasn't anything surprising.

This type of response was completely within Tyranny's plans. In a map with lots of dips and slopes like this one, a player's line of sight would often be blocked. No one could see the entire situation with just a glance. The only ones who could were the spectators, who possessed an omniscient view of the map.

The spectators could see that Tiny Herb's attempt to convene together would be obstructed because of this. Tyranny cut off Tiny Herb's characters from each other. They didn't immediately choose a main target to attack. They made adjustments according to the situation.

Team Tyranny moved quickly. The communication going on in their team chat was also very rapid. They used concise but comprehensive words to communicate. Only the most coordinated teammates could instantly understand the meanings behind their short messages. As for the spectators, they could only see a bunch of letters and numbers being spewed out. They had no idea what anyone in Tyranny was saying.

However, they could still see the results of their communication.

In the end, Team Tiny Herb's players were successfully partitioned off from each other. Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree and Liu Xiaobie's Flying Sword were cut out and pushed towards a location that Tyranny wanted them to be at.

"Attack!"

Another order. This time, Tyranny was truly attacking now.　

Dazzling Hundred Blossom's attacks instantly swallowed up that location. Zhang Jiale never attacked solely to damage the target. Oftentimes, he would provide cover for others. The brilliant lights only hit the ground, but who would be coming out from the light? Would it be Han Wenqing's Desert Dust? Would it be Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder? Or would it be no one?

No matter what the choice was, the opposing players needed to be on guard. The purpose of Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossoms Style was to confuse the opponents and have them question what decision to make. This time, under the cover of the Hundred Blossoms Style, Han Wenqing's Desert Dust shot out.

Liu Xiaobie reacted extremely quickly. Flying Sword brandished his sword and welcomed Desert Dust. Without any hesitation, he unleashed his explosive hand speed.

Against a waning old general at the end of his career, explosive hand speed was a smart way to match his biggest strength against his opponent's biggest weakness. Liu Xiaobie knew what the current situation was, so he wasn't polite at all.

The crowd exclaimed in surprise at Liu Xiaobie's explosiveness. The screen displayed a number. Liu Xiaobie's APM had surpassed 300.

In Glory, each player could only control one character. It wasn't like RTSes, where there was a lot of room to get to a high APM.

300 APM. In Glory, this was already an unimaginable number. For many, it wasn't a question of whether they could move their hands fast enough, but rather what to do with each action. And right now, Liu Xiaobie's 300 APM was just a starting point. It was still going up.

Shadow Steps!

The moment Flying Sword clashed with Desert Dust, seven shadows split up. With the level cap increasing along with Liu Xiaobie's frightening hand speed, what players could only dream of had been achieved in just an instant. Each and every shadow seemed real. Which one was real? Which one was fake? Perhaps not even an experienced God like Han Wenqing could distinguish them in a short amount of time.

As a result, he simply didn't bother trying.

Playing rock-paper-scissors with his opponent wasn't his style. He was always simple and direct. Seven shadows? Desert Dust charged past them directly towards Gao Yingjie's Kind Tree.

Liu Xiaobie immediately had Flying Sword turn around and chased after him with a sword slash. But when he turned around, a Brick flew out from the cover of Dazzling Hundred Blossom's light cover. In the next moment, the Hundred Blossoms Style stopped being just a simple cover and swallowed up Flying Sword. The viewers could see Flying Sword's health rapidly dropping. Liu Xiaobie and his explosive hand speed had been denied by these two seniors simply and easily.

As for Liu Xiaobie, after being engulfed by the Hundred Blossoms Style, the damage was secondary. More importantly, he felt like he couldn't see anything. Slowly, he started getting used to it and saw Dark Thunder. When Liu Xiaobie saw an enemy, he got ready to rush forward. Suddenly, a white light blazed around his body. A Sacred Fire had been cast beneath his feet.

Dazzling Hundred Blossom's interference must be stopped!

Liu Xiaobie was still clear-headed. Tyranny was a formidable opponent that they had already fought two matches against in the playoffs. At this point, both sides had a good grasp of each other's methods. Hundred Blossoms Style must be cut off from the source. If not, they would be harrassed endlessly. It would be delusional to think that this cover was also a cover for him. That type of Hundred Blossom Style would just be a fake. The Hundred Blossoms Style from Zhang Jiale was absolutely a targeted one. It wasn't just cycling through different skills to produce a dazzling effect. Whatever attack came out and wherever that attack hit had careful thinking behind it. As a result, those who were locked down by a true Hundred Blossom Style would be the only ones locked down. Only Tyranny's players and the spectators would be able to clearly see the situation when a true Hundred Blossom Style was unleashed.

Liu Xiaobie determined Dazzling Hundred Blossom's position. He ignored his silenced skills and rushed over. Zhang Jiale obviously wasn't going to let him come close. He attacked while retreating, maintaining the distance between the two of them. Several seconds soon passed, and the silence on Flying Sword wore off. Liu Xiaobie sprinted forward and activated Triple Slash. Sword light flashed in a straight line along with a handful of sand towards it.

Liu Xiaobie's hand speed really was fast. Without any delay, he was able to tilt his Flying Sword's head a bit. However, a Brick immediately followed and hit the back of his head.

Liu Xiaobie wanted to cry. This Lin Jingyan hadn't been so dirty back when he played on Wind Howl. But after coming to Tyranny, his style had changed a lot.

After being put into a Dizzy state, how could Flying Sword be in a good spot? A new wave of attacks suddenly washed over him. His teammate, Gao Yingjie, had noticed that the situation wasn't looking good a long time ago. He had been trying to come over to rescue him, but escaping from Han Wenqing couldn't be accomplished with just a sweep of his broom.

Tiny Herb's other three members had convened without a hitch. But then, they immediately received messages from Liu Xiaobie and Gao Yingjie. And at this moment, the three could still hear sounds of gunfire nearby. Tyranny's fifth player, Qin Muyun, was a Sharpshooter. He deceitfully misled Tiny Herb. By the time Tiny Herb reacted, the team had already been split into two.

The three immediately went to rescue their teammates. Qin Muyun obviously couldn't stop them alone. He could only hinder them a bit. But by the time the three rushed over, Liu Xiaobie's Flying Sword was on the brink of death. Yuan Boqing hastily had his Aweto go over to save him, but to his surprise, Dazzling Hundred Blossom's attacks instantly enshrouded them. With his sight blocked, Yuan Boqing was unable to find Flying Sword's location.　

On the other hand, Liu Xiaobie's vision suddenly became clear. His spirit rose. Even though he didn't have much health left, he still went after Zhang Xinjie's Cleric, Immovable Rock.　　

Bang!

A gunshot.

Tiny Herb's three players arrived. Tyranny's Qin Muyun naturally returned to his team as well. When he returned, he saw an opening and accurately shot Flying Sword's head with a Thunder Snipe. Thunder Snipe's hidden effect: headshots dealt double damage. A spurt of blood flew out from Flying Sword's head. This attack looked as if it actually blew up his head as Flying Sword fell. In the team competition, Team Tyranny won the first point.

Killing Flying Sword gave Tyranny a numbers advantage for a short period of time. They didn't waste it and immediately began attacking.

With an advantage already established, these old generals definitely wouldn't let it go to waste. In this instant, they seemed to have forgotten their age. Just like Liu Xiaobie, they disregarded everything else and burst out with explosive hand speed. On the screen, the statistics showed that the APM from the players on the two teams rose and rose. The intensity of the battle could be seen just from these statistics. Team Tiny Herb's captain Wang Jiexi had broken through to the 350-400 APM range. His Magician style was originally a style that required a lot of actions.

Tiny Herb was able to get their sixth player into the battle intact, but intact was just in terms of the number of their players. Tyranny still dealt Tiny Herb a huge amount of damage during this time. Tyranny's old generals knew how to utilize their numbers advantage. Even though they weren't able to kill off anyone in Tiny Herb, their advantage only increased with this wave of attacks.

Five versus five. Tyranny slowed down their tempo. Competing hand speeds wasn't their strong point. Seizing an opening to do a single wave of attacks was fine, but if they tried to keep up that hand speed, these old generals would be dying.

The advantage had been established. As a result, Tyranny did not try to end it in one go and instead slowed down to play the long game with Tiny Herb. As the two went back and forth, many viewers discovered that Team Tyranny's Qin Muyun received a very pitiful amount of healing. It was as if he was being intentionally cast away.

This type of slip-up wouldn't happen to someone like Zhang Xinjie. This was a tactical decision. Those with a certain amount of Glory knowledge could determine that Team Tyranny was trying to switch out their player. Even though Team Tyranny had slowed down, they did their utmost to maintain their advantage.

Surely and steadily, Qin Muyun successfully swapped out with their sixth player Bai Yanfei. The healing saved by not healing Qin Muyun was effectively distributed to the other four, so their conditions were very good. The full health and full mana sixth player on Tyranny swapped with their dead Sharpshooter, Negative Nine Degrees, and Tyranny's advantage moved one step further.

In the end, Tyranny didn't let their advantage go. In the team competition, Tyranny beat Tiny Herb 6 to 3, winning the semifinals 10 to 8 and progressing to the finals.

Chapter 1075: A Samsara You Shouldn’t Underestimate

"Congrats to Tyranny, I wish them luck!"

In the post-match press conference, Tiny Herb's captain, Wang Jiexi, put a full stop to Tiny Herb's journey this season with a well wish for their opponent. Even though they failed to reach the end this season, everyone had seen Tiny Herb's future. Xu Bin, Liu Xiaobie, Gao Yingjie, all of Tiny Herb's players had talent; they were all young, with much room to grow. Even Yuan Boqing, who had been rather overlooked, had shown everyone something amazing in the match. There was also their captain, Wang Jiexi. Even though he wouldn't be able to stay in his peak state for too much longer, he had valuable experience that he could use to help his team. He would always be Tiny Herb's pilar.

　

As for Tyranny?

"Next up, the finals!"

Captain Han Wenqing's brief but clear words showed everyone the team's determination. Why these veterans all got together and what this was all for was clear as day. Now, they had come this far. Only two victories stood between them and the championship. Even the opponent they had just beaten had sincerely wished them well.

The announcement regarding the finals quickly spread. This was the annual crème de la crème match in the entire Glory circle. It was just a shame that Samsara and Tyranny didn't have anything between them to really talk about. The players of the two teams didn't have any particularly striking past clashes and relationships that could be discussed either.

This was purely a fight to be the champions. On one side was the veterans who had allied together to achieve their long-awaited dream. On the other side, it was the defending champions who wanted to build a new dynasty.

Tyranny was very focused on performing as a whole, while Samsara was always known as a one-man team. This seemed to also be a clash of two kinds of ideals in Glory. Who would be the champions?

With the finals being promoted everywhere, there would obviously be public polls in regards to who would win. In the end, Team Tyranny held a whooping 72.65 percent, far ahead of Samsara.

　

However, over at Happy, Ye Xiu couldn't give an answer to Chen Guo's question of "who do you think will win?"

"They both have a chance. It wouldn't be surprising for either of them to win" was how Ye Xiu answered.

This was the most rational answer.

Although Team Tyranny had won an extreme high percentage of votes in the public poll, most of the votes were an emotional decision. Team Tyranny's veterans didn't have many more chances. Their fight, backs to the water, was a moving tale for people. In addition, Tyranny was filled with widely renown names. On paper, their lineup couldn't be more magnificent.

The 72.65 percent vote was more of a hope and support. The gap between Samsara and Tyranny's combative ability wasn't nearly as absurd as the poll made it out to be.

One man team?

This mocking title was a underestimation of Samsara's abilities. However, out of the in the pro scene, how many people would actually agree with this phrase?

In their eyes, the idea of a one man team was no more than a joke.

Samsara definitely wasn't a one man team. It was just because Zhou Zekai was too strong, too striking, too eye-catching, that there would be the illusion of a one man team. Team Samsara was also a very talented team. Their entire team could keep up with Zhou Zekai's pace, and that was already the best proof.

Although they sometimes relied on Zhou Zekai's forceful momentum to take the upper hand, seeming like they had no strategy, in reality, this forcefulness was a unique strategy of Samsara's, a strategy that only they - having the uncounterable Zhou Zekai - could use, a strategy that many teams wished they could use too.

The only people who underestimated Team Samsara because of the saying "one man team" were all clueless outsiders. This sort of mistake would never happen in Team Tyranny. They would carefully gauge Samsara's strength.

The uncounterable Zhou Zekai. That was what everyone would think of when Samsara was mentioned. But apart from that? Had anyone realized that, out of the semifinalists, Samsara's lineup was the most stable?

The other three teams had all gone through massive changes in the summer. Only Samsara kept their original lineup, a lineup that stayed the same for three whole years. This sort of stability was something the other semifinalist didn't have.

Apart from that, Samsara's skill point advantage was extremely apparent in the last playoffs. After this season, it was no longer a secret. But, even if it wasn't a secret, what could they do about it? You could only keep in mind and beware of this sort of solid advantage, but you would never be able to get rid of it.

When people thought of Zhou Zekai the moment Samsara was mentioned, they hadn't noticed that they had covered up a lot of other terrifying aspects about Samsara with the Zhou Zekai Halo. Jiang Botao, ranked five in the All-Stars, seemed to be just a random passerby under the Zhou Halo, never mind the thirteenth ranked Lu Boyuan.

On Samsara's side, they also had three All-Star players, and they were all in their peak years of their career. Tyranny's four All-Stars was a number advantage, but if you considered their age and state, was this four against three any significant advantage?

"How it will end up will be decided by the match." That was the judgement Ye Xiu gave in the end. By then, Tyranny and Samsara's players were already standing on the stage.

　

The first round of the finals would be held in City S, Samsara's home turf. There wasn't a single empty seat in the stadium. In the group arena that had just finished, Samsara took a lead of 5 to 4. It wasn't a big advantage, but the venue exploded with excitement from it. The fans filled the stadium, raising their self-made flags and signs, eagerly anticipating their team's second championship. The lineups for the team competition were already being broadcasted through the PA system.

Team Samsara: Zhou Zekai's Sharpshooter, Cloud Piercer; Jiang Botao's Spellblade, Empty Waves; Lu Boyuan's Grappler, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain; Wu Qi's Assassin, Cruel Silence; Fang Minghua's Cleric, Laughing Song; Du Ming's Blade Master, Moon Luring Frost.

A lineup that had stayed the same for three years, the lineup that had taken last year's championship. When they came out, the entire venue erupted with thunderous cheers.

　

Tyranny didn't give everyone any surprises either. The four gods would obviously be fighting. Their fifth player was still the ever lowkey Qin Muyun and his Sharpshooter, Negative Nine Degrees. The sixth player was Bai Yanfei and his Elementalist, Rota. This was also the lineup they had stayed with throughout the playoffs.

The players entered their competition booths and, soon enough, the match that would decide the finals began.

As the home team, Samsara had taken the initiative ever since the group arena, and the team competition was no different. They had only just loaded when the entire team flew towards the center of the map, as if not wanting to waste a single second.

However, the visiting team, Tyranny, also showed a vigor that didn't lose to the home team. As soon as they were loaded, they also sped straight for the center of the map.

"Wow, this… both sides seem very impatient!!"

The commentators for the broadcast were also very surprised at the scene before them. In the finals, the final battleground that a year of hard work had taken them to, even the most fierce and eager teams would gain a hint of caution. This was because the results of this match were too important. Most teams would first consider how to establish a secure advantage and then carefully execute their plans for victory. However, right now, Samsara and Tyranny were both charging forward boldly, seeming like they wanted to end this battle as soon as possible. They were treating the saying "the nameless finals" as a joke**.

Clash!

An intense clash!

The gunners of each team fired the moment they got into shooting range. However, on one side, it was the Great Gunner of Glory, while on the other side, it was a barely known rookie. The disparity between them was large enough that even the commentators didn't have the heart to call it a face off. However, soon after, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms' Hundred Blossom Style covered the area with flashing lights. Tyranny had began their breakthrough into Samsara's formation under the cover of these explosions.

Team Samsara didn't show any form of weakness, Jiang Botao's Empty Waves immediately set down two Wave Formations, creating a hard to penetrate barrier, but the light and shadows of Hundred Blossoms Style immediately came down on them.

They wanted to brute force their way through?

　

Tyranny's unyielding momentum was rather unexpected for Samsara. Although the Wave Formations of Spellblades didn't have all sorts of status inducing attacks, they had far higher damage output than Ghost Boundaries. Charging through the Wave Formations, they wanted to launch an offense regardless of the damage they had to take.

However, this adhered to Team Tyranny's usual attitude!

Didn't this team always charge forth no matter what obstacles there were? Just two Wave Formations wouldn't scare them.

Then, what about two more?

Jiang Botao wasn't stingy with his skills at all, immediately sending out two more Wave Formations.

Light, darkness, ice and fire.

Wave Formations of the four great elements overlapped and shone, clashing with the Hundred Blossom lights and creating chaos. Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloudy Mountains and Wu Qi's Cruel Silence were hidden outside the Wave Formations, waiting to ambush whoever charged out.

Who would have expected that no one jumped out of the flashing lights and, instead, the flashing lights moved forward.

The lights of the Hundred Blossoms Style were all Spitfire skills, and all dealt damage. Lu Boyuan and Wu Qi had to back away. However, after that, the two took a side each simultaneously, going around the Hundred Blossom Style's light cover to get to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. No one expected that the two would be welcomed with two powerful skills upon going around.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Tyrannical Chain Punch!

The moment those two characters went around the light cover, the two Fighter class characters of Tyranny charged forth. Desert Dust punched and kicked, forcing Cruel Silence into a retreat. As for the Grappler, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain,s who was good at grab skills, he had been pressed into the ground and beaten by Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder.

The two characters weren't hiding within the lights?

Then what about Dazzling Hundred Blossoms?

The Hundred Blossom Style lights were still advancing, but there was no sign of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. There was only one possibility; the one advancing under the cover of the lights was Dazzling Hundred Blossoms himself.

"Be careful!!" The two hastily sent the message.

Misjudging Dazzling Hundred Blossom's positioning meant that they had misjudged the area Hundred Blossoms Style could affect. So in the next moment, the lights of Hundred Blossoms seemed to have teleported, suddenly appearing farther away and directly onto Samsara's Cleric, Laughing Song. But this time, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms wasn't providing cover for anyone or hindering visibility. He had launched a fierce offensive on Samsara's Cleric. Team Tyranny's opening was shocking. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had covered for himself and charged into shooting range before directly unleashing a strong assault on the opponent's Cleric.

"We have to win!!!" Zhang Jiale roared. The light cover left Dazzling Hundred Blossoms right before he darted past Empty Waves, shooting at Laughing Song as he ran.

Chapter 1076: Samsara’s Weakness

Laughing Song took heavy damage.

Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms wasn't someone who only knew how to protect his teammates through a light screen. After Sun Zheping retired, he had to be the main attacker and a support for his teammates. He had put Team Hundred Blossoms on his back and had carried them forward. Now, he had reliable teammates helping restrict the opponents, allowing Zhang Jiale to concentrate on attacking and dealing serious damage to his target.

No one would have imagined that Samsara would be torn apart and be forced to sell their healer as soon as the match started. Jiang Botao's Empty Waves immediately went back to rescue their healer. However, those who were following Samsara this match, whether it was the viewers or the cameraman, couldn't help but look for for a certain player.

Where's Zhou Zekai?

Where's his Cloud Piercer?

Zhou Zekai was obviously still alive. His Cloud Piercer had decisively turned back. Rescuing their healer was obviously Samsara's biggest priority at the moment. But under the explosiveness of the Hundred Blossoms Style, Zhou Zekai's long-ranged attacks were significantly weakened. He was unable to clearly make out his target's location. He could only rely on his intuition and instinct to attack. In comparison, Jiang Botao's Empty Waves was closer. Moreover, for Spellblades, whether it was their magic wave swords or magic wave formations, all of them were ranged AoE attacks. Even if he didn't know his target's exact location, he could still throw out his skill in the general direction.

The moment Empty Waves turned around, Jiang Botao saw something flicker from below him. He immediately looked down and saw that a Grenade had rolled to his feet.

Jiang Botao hastily leaped backwards. As Empty Waves was pushed back by the shockwave from the Grenade, sounds of gunfire could be heard. Bullets rained down on him.

Negative Nine Degrees?

When did he get here?　　

Jiang Botao was surprised. A strange feeling arose in his heart.　　

He suddenly realized that after Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees shot two times when the two sides collided, he had no impression of what Negative Nine Degrees had done since then. This type of invisibility shouldn't exist in the finals. In the finals, everyone was fighting with all they had. How could there be a cheerleader among them?

But the moment he tried to rescue their healer, Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees suddenly appeared. And Jiang Botao didn't seem to know when he got into such a perfect position.

A rain of gunfire forced Jiang Botao back. After Desert Dust and Dark Thunder tossed aside the two characters that they had been pinning down, they rushed towards this location. Zhang Jiale's attacks were just the prelude. Next was the follow up. Tyranny seemed to be planning on directly sending off Samsara's healer in one go.

How could Samsara let Tyranny do as they pleased!

Jiang Botao's Empty Waves slashed with an Earthquake Sword, blocking off these two characters.

Even though Spellblades wore high defence plate armor and were Swordsman, extremely close-combat wasn't their strong point. When Jiang Botao saw Desert Dust close in, he instinctively stepped back twice. However, Desert Dust's charge had been a bluff. As soon as Empty Waves retreated, Desert Dust seized this opening to directly pass him. Lin Jingyan didn't fall behind. His Dark Thunder ran even more smoothly than Desert Dust.

I was tricked!

Han Wenqing's bluff didn't only trick Jiang Botao. Most of the viewers were astonished when they saw Desert Dust's bluff. This wasn't how the champion of Tyranny played.

For the championship title, how much had Tyranny's players sacrificed?

Zhang Jiale carried the burden of a blackened name. Lin Jingyan abandoned his position as the core of a team. Even Han Wenqing had let go of his courageous and stubborn style that had never changed since the start of his career…...

All of them had changed. The only thing that hadn't changed was their desire to be champions!

"Forward!!!"

The two Fighter classes entered the fray. Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms suddenly turned. A light flashed from his gun and flew towards Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer. Team Tyranny's coordination was loose yet tight, completely controlling the pace of the battle.

Tyranny fought ferociously. However, their fighting was not at all reckless.

Rapidly closing in for a melee battle seemed a bit impatient for an away team. However, Team Tyranny's speed wasn't just fast. It was a speed that reached the pinnacle. The two sides quickly entered a chaotic brawl. What was Samsara's home game advantage? It was their familiarity and utilization of the map. But by rapidly forcing the two sides to fight an intense battle, Samsara wasn't given any time to utilize the map and utilize their tactics. Samsara could only rely on their instinct and intuition to counter. This was the importance of having the initiative. In this match, Team Tyranny gave every team a thorough lesson on how to quickly and tyrannically seize the initiative.

Four minutes and forty seven seconds into the match, the home team's Cleric, Laughing Song, was killed. No one could have expected this result. Healers were too crucial in a team competition. They were absolutely the most protected team members. In a high level match, attacking the healer was an extremely important goal. However, the strategies for that were usually to restrict the healer. It was very rare for a healer to be directly taken out in one go.

But in the finals, in this match that represented the pinnacle of Glory, Team Tyranny achieved it in 4 minutes 47 seconds. Was this a record? Data needed to be pulled up to check. However, Samsara's home stadium was already in complete silence. Everyone in the crowd was dumbstruck. Everyone knew what it meant to have the healer taken away. If this wasn't an important match, people could understand if the team typed GG and then forfeited. However, this was the finals. It was the final stage after one year of struggles. No one would choose to give up so easily.

Without a healer, it could be said that Samsara had less burden on them. At least, they didn't have to constantly need to defend a key character. When Laughing Song fell, Samsara immediately let loose a fierce counterattack. No one held back. Samsara quickly obtained solid results. One of Tyranny's players fell, Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees.

But a strange feeling once again arose in Jiang Botao's heart.

When Negative Nine Degrees was there, it was like he couldn't feel his existence. Now that Negative Nine Degrees was truly gone, he felt like nothing seemed to have really changed. But they had killed an enemy player! How could such an important breakthrough not have any impact?

This feeling made him feel too uneasy.

Jiang Botao tried hard to calm himself and examine the situation carefully. They had no healer, so they needed to end things quickly. However, ending things quickly required a plan to succeed. What? He's already attacking!

Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer didn't seem to have any intentions of resetting the tempo. He continued to launch a frenzy of attacks so much so that Jiang Botao felt like it was a bit excessive. However, in the next second, he no longer thought that. When he examined the situation again, he realized that Team Tyranny had pulled back into a fully defensive position.

Team Samsara needed to be fast, but Team Tyranny wouldn't let them. Zhou Zekai had seen through this point, so instead of resetting, he continued to increase the speed to break Tyranny's tempo.

Can it be done? Zhou Zekai's charge through the enemy lines had opened up the battle countless times, but this time, against the steady defense from Tyranny's four Gods, while Zhou Zekai's assault was as fierce as ever, it was unable to open up the situation. Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossom Style was a huge hindrance to a Sharpshooter, who needed absolute precision to attack. Rush in and fight with Gun Fu? It wasn't like Zhou Zekai had never done that before. However, Tyranny had the number one close combat fighter Han Wenqing and his King of Fighting, Desert Dust. Employing Gun Fu to compete with Han Wenqin was definitely not a smart idea.

"Team Samsara's weakness has been exposed..." Ye Xiu suddenly said. He had been quietly watching the match the entire time.

"What is it?" Chen Guo immediately asked.

"They lack an attacker that can charge forward and break open the situation." Ye Xiu said.

"Uh, don't they have Lu Boyuan, Wu Qi, and Du Ming?" Chen Guo asked.　　

"Grappers don't have very good movement skills. However, they need to get close to display their combat power. Just trying to close in is difficult enough already."

As Ye Xiu explained, Chen Guo looked at the match again. She discovered that Lu Boyuan's Chaotic Cloud Mountain was having a rough time. Grappler wore leather armor. Their movement speed was considered fast, but trying to break through with just movement speed alone would be extremely difficult.

"As for Assassins, I don't think I'll need to talk too much about them? They're not a class that charges into battle." Ye Xiu said.

Wu Qi's Assassin, Cruel Silence, seemed to be in an even rougher spot than Chaotic Cloudy Mountains. He was searching for an opening. However, Tyranny wasn't giving him any. As a result, it just looked like he was doing nothing, circling around the battle.

"As for Du Ming….. His skill isn't quite there." For Du Ming, his class wasn't the big issue, but Du Ming himself was a bit of a problem. Ye Xiu was quite polite in his evaluation. Getting rid of "quite" would probably have been more accurate. Starting from when he closed in on Tyranny, Du Ming's Blade Master seemed to be in a panic. After closing in, he was hit by a Brick from Lin Jingyan and then a punch from Han Wenqing. If his ability to escape wasn't good, he might have been dragged directly into Team Tyranny.

Team Tyranny calmly played the long game with Samsara. Samsara tried again and again to break through, but they were unable to shake Tyranny's defense. When Tyranny's sixth player, Bai Yanfei, and his Elementalist arrived, Tyranny's defense became even more solid. In the end, Samsara had no other choice but to attempt a suicide charge and find victory within chaos. However, Tyranny stood firm. Finally, the match ended with Tyranny winning 6 to 2 in the team competition. Tyranny turned around their loss in the group arena and won the away game.

Champions?

Tyranny won their away game. Next, they would have the home game advantage. This type of situation was too advantageous for them. Many media sources were already declaring Tyranny as the champions. The question mark after the word champions was an attempt to hide that.　

Who would have thought that three days later, in Team Tyranny's home game in City B, it was Samsara that won 11 to 7, overturning Tyranny's home game.

Chapter 1077: Tyranny in Danger

The away game victory finally caused everyone to notice Samsara's consistency.

This was a team that had worked together for three years. They supported each other, depended on each other. The members of the team had a deep trust in each other and worked very well as a unit. They had the same conviction, the same confidence. Their loss in their home game didn't cause them to lose faith. In the their away game, they were powerful in how united they were, standing firm and fighting steadily, not at all affected by their loss in the first round. After two hours of competing, they had eventually taken down Tyranny.

In this match, Samsara had displayed a tenacity and patience that didn't lose to the veterans. No matter if it was as an individual or as a team, every little thing was executed at its best.

A faultless performance. A flawless victory.

During the second day, the media's headlines all discussed how to describe Samsara's performance this round. This time, they had shown everyone that Samsara definitely wasn't a one man team, but a unit. A unit that operated close to flawlessly. The reason that the power of this unit was magnified was because they were influenced by the previous match.

The hindrance of Team Tyranny's Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossoms Style on Zhou Zekai was exceptionally striking. Ranged combat meant he couldn't shoot accurately, but close combat meant he had to face a master of melee like Han Wenqing. Zhou Zekai, known as uncounterable, might not have fallen to a disadvantage in a direct face off, but he had still been suppressed.

　

Samsara had realized that this was where the problem lay, and thus focused more on operating as a team. The presence of the other members of the team suddenly became much more striking. In this match, Zhou Zekai uncharacteristically didn't give an explosive performance, but everyone witnessed Samsara's power as a team that didn't lose to any other team in the Alliance.

After two matches, the two teams were tied. The victory would be decided in the last match. Three days later, it would be at Tyranny's home turf, but with random maps.

Who would win?

　

With the battle having reached this point, theoretical analysis was meaningless. The two teams were continuously rewriting what everyone knew about them, breaking through their limits and improving themselves each time. Everything would be decided on the field.

　　

The tickets for the final match in three days were nigh impossible to obtain. The match started exactly at 8 PM, and the group arena came first as usual.

The previous two group arenas were all won by Samsara and the results were both 5 to 4. Although Tyranny's veterans had a lot of experience and honed awareness, Samsara was a very mature team by now. The members of the team were all skilled and everyone had a lot of match experience. For the old veterans, this was the hardest sort of opponent to deal with. However, the difference of a single point didn't have much influence on the team competition. Under the new rules, the group arena was already being considered a starter to the real match. They wouldn't be too relaxed, but not too nervous either.

But the situation that had remained stable for two rounds ended in this round. The winner of the group arena was still Samsara, but this time, they had won 5 to 3, ending the group arena at their fourth player.

A 2 point deficit caused some commotion in the venue as Tyranny's fans began to become anxious.

Looking at the overall situation, Samsara hadn't gotten any overwhelmning lead in any of the face offs. Samsara's 5 to 4 victory was slowly accumulated through each fight. It was this sort of situation that made people feel insecure. This meant that the entire team had fallen to a disadvantage. What was wrong with Tyranny?

The audience didn't know, they just hoped that the team could adjust and end up one step short of success. As for the Samsara fans in the venue, they were excited. This sort of beginning gave them the hope for victory.

　　

After the break between the two sections, the team competition began. The lineups for the teams didn't have any sort of change from the previous two matches. The map was unfamiliar, except for the fact that the two teams would spawn in opposing corners. After the characters loaded, Team Tyranny's characters charged forward at once, not bothering to look at their surroundings.

The stadium fell into a stunned silence before it exploded with cheering. Didn't this scene happen in the away game that Tyranny won beautifully? Not hesitating, aiming for a direct frontal assault, and keeping the match at their pace? Tyranny's fans hoped for this scene to repeat itself and cheered for their team.

On the other hand, Ye Xiu frowned immediately upon seeing this.

"Is something wrong?" Chen Guo had developed the habit of keeping an eye on Ye Xiu's reactions during a match, getting Ye Xiu to give a few words of explanation whenever there was a chance.

"They're too impatient," Ye Xiu said.

"Ah? Didn't they play this way in the first match?" Chen Guo said.

"That's different. In the first match, Samsara had the map advantage. Tyranny's playstyle was unexpected, eventually managing to negate their advantage and suppress Samsara's momentum, controlling the pace of the match. However, this map is unfamiliar to both sides and doesn't give an advantage to either side. Tyranny's current playstyle won't give them any benefits." Ye Xiu said.

"They can't help it," Wei Chen suddenly said, "Tyranny's stamina can't keep up."

Stamina!

No one would know better than Wei Chen as to how this affected a player's state. The long team competition in the Challenger League had given him too much strain and then his performance after that had clearly slipped. Although the veterans of Tyranny were much younger than Wei Chen, how could the intensity of the Challenger League compare to the intensity of the playoffs?

Not only were the playoffs more intense, the matches were spaced close together. The regular season was one match per week, but the playoffs had one match every three or four days. The playoffs were using the new rules too, so there was a large chance that three matches would have to be fought. Team Tyranny had fought two three-match battles in a row to enter the finals. As for Team Samsara, they had two two-match battles to decide the victor.

Samsara had fought two fewer games than Tyranny. That meant they had a week to rest. Especially since, before the finals, Samsara had already rested for three days when Tyranny was fighting their third game against Tiny Herb. They hadn't even rested for three days before having to rush to City S to fight the well-rested Samsara.

Tyranny had managed to take that game down in one, but after returning to their home turf, they were defeated by Samsara after two hours of ceaseless fighting. Tyranny's stamina was probably already running low by the second game. After the exhaustion from a season of battles, then the successive intense battles of the playoffs, age was mercilessly dragging these tenacious veterans down.

However, they didn't back down at all and wouldn't surrender. They knew that stalling wouldn't be good, so they fought in the last game with the same attitude and style from the first game despite knowing that they wouldn't gain the same sort of advantage. Falling behind in the group arena might've been a way of preserving their stamina. They had to make sure that they had as much energy as possible for the team competition.

Now it was time for their final battle. Maybe they were all exhausted, but their willpower pulled them through every action.

Charge! Team Tyranny charged.

As for Samsara? Samsara was displaying a completely different attitude to Tyranny. As soon as the match began, they didn't charge. It was obvious that they were trying to avoid a direct confrontation. Team Samsara's entire team moved tactically, swerving to Tyranny's flank. Team Tyranny had fiercely charged forth, but met no one.

Those who realized the problem probably felt a chill in their hearts by now. For such a key battle, every detail would be carefully considered. Samsara's tactical decision at the beginning probably wasn't a coincidence. They had already realized that Tyranny's stamina was failing. Having fought them on the field, Samsara was better able to sense Team Tyranny's worsening state, maybe even better than Tyranny themselves.

Thus, they weren't impatient for this match. They would slowly drag this out into an endurance match with Tyranny.

The battle eventually turned this guess into reality. Samsara avoided a direct confrontation with Tyranny, continuously feinting to harass and wear Tyranny down with a top ranged attacker like Zhou Zekai and a mid-ranged AoE cannon like Jiang Botao's Empty Waves. In addition, there was Wu Qi, who would unleash a torrent of attacks whenever there was the slightest opening, as well as Lu Boyuan who was great at single-target control; whenever the Grappler caught a target, he would throw the target away from the team... Samsara's lineup was great at harassment. Team Tyranny had Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossom Style for cover, but the Hundred Blossom Style was exhausting for both the player and the character. So it would only be used at crucial times, not thrown out like free candy.

Tyranny had managed to brute force their way at Samsara a few times, but despite getting an upper hand several times, they never managed to deal a critical blow to Samsara. Even worse, they still hadn't managed to make any changes to the situation at hand. If they didn't have problems with stamina, they could continue to go back and forth like this and keep the upper hand. However, everyone who could tell that this problem existed knew that with every advantage they managed to gain on the field, their situation worsened.

Their focus was weakening, their reactions slowing, their mechanics stiffening… Willpower would help them endure, but only endure. You couldn't win a match by just enduring. They needed to perform at their peak if they wanted to beat the powerful Samsara.

However, they couldn't do that anymore now. When another wave of harassment came, Team Tyranny was visibly a beat too slow, and this opening was immediately captured by Zhou Zekai. He, who hadn't performed explosively in the finals at all yet, finally gave the decisive blow in the final game. Cloud Piercer shot wildly, suddenly exploding into action and completely messed up Tyranny's formation. The other characters swarmed forth, taking this chance to storm Tyranny with their whole team. This time, Samsara didn't back away, fighting to the end. As for Tyranny, the veterans had long since reached their limit. Though they were still doing their best, their declining play caused them to expose many openings.

In the team competition, Team Samsara won by a huge lead: 6 to 1. The final score of this match was 11 to 4. Team Samsara once again won the championships and became the second team to defend their title after Team Excellent Era. And all of this took place at Tyranny's home stadium. The venue was silent.

Chapter 1078: The Same As Always

It's… over?

Zhang Jiale's hands still remained on his keyboard and mouse. In fact, five minutes had past since his Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fell.

The first to fall from Team Tyranny was Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder, then it was Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. He hovered in midair as a ghost as he continued to watch as Team Samsara pursued his team relentlessly.

Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees fell.

Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock fell.

Only Han Wenqing's Desert Dust and Bai Yanfei's Rota were left. The two didn't give up and used up all their strength to take away Wu Qi's Cruel Silence from Samsara. The three then fell down together.

Glory!

Like in the online arena, this word also appeared after the end of the team competition. However, the glory didn't belong to him because he had lost again…...

How many times have I lost?

Zhang Jiale was unwilling to think about it.

He had given up everything. He had endured criticism from his fans and the torture in his heart.

Just once. Just once is enough.

He kept telling himself that. However, he was once again one step away. He just needed that one step, that one win. He had won countless times in his career. Why did he always fall here?

Zhang Jiale couldn't believe it. He didn't know what to do, and even forgot what he should be doing at this moment. It was until someone started knocking from outside the player booths did he suddenly snap out of it.

Han Wenqing, Tyranny's core who didn't know the word cower.

Zhang Xinjie, the Master Tactician who never made a mistake.

There was also Lin Jingyan, who was let go of by his team and found himself a new place in Tyranny. He was also an old player who started in the second season like him.

Also, Qin Muyun and Bai Yanfei…...

All of his teammates were standing outside. Everyone looked pained after losing the match. They all tried their best to hide it, but he could see through it. Lin Jingyan even managed to squeeze out a smile. It was probably the most unsightly smile Zhang Jiale had ever seen in his life.

"What a shame..." Lin Jingyan even managed to speak. Even though he was upset, everyone in Tyranny knew that Zhang Jiale was suffering more than any one of them.

This was because he carried such a heavy burden yet still fell at this same step again.

Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie had at least won the championships once.

As for Lin Jingyan, it was the first time he had fought in the finals. He felt that he had already gained a lot by coming this far. Although he felt very regretful for their final loss, at least his mental burden wasn't as great as Zhang Jiale's.

Only Zhang Jiale…...

"I..." Zhang Jiale wanted to speak, but stopped.

"Don't tell me you're going to retire again?" Lin Jingyan spoke.

"That's no good."

"It's still too early for that."

"Right, we still have opportunities."

"Next season is going to arrive in the blink of an eye."

"Yeah, it already feels like it's tomorrow."

"I can't wait for it."

"I..." Zhang Jiale opened his mouth to speak again. Everyone shut their mouths and looked at him.

"I wanted to say that I'm fine." Zhang Jiale said.

Everyone looked at one another. When the match had finished, everyone apart from Zhang Jiale had walked out from the player booths and showed no signs of activity. At that moment, they even predicted the worst situation that could happen. It wasn't until Zhang Jiale walked out did everyone feel a bit relieved. Everyone started to comfort him, but he said he was fine.

It's true, I'm fine. Zhang Jiale looked around him. It seemed as if everyone in the stadium was watching him as well. But he was fine. Even though he had carried a heavy burden, it all came from his own choice. Sun Zheping told him to clean up all those distracting thoughts in his mind. Zhang Jiale tried to do that, but he realised that he couldn't do so. Perhaps, only people like Sun Zheping were capable of doing that, right? In the end, Zhang Jiale wrapped up all those distracting thoughts and carried it on his shoulder. This was his method; he wasn't able to give up, but neither would he be weak. He would carry those things clearly on his back! As for now, he merely had another package to carry on his shoulders.

"Yeah, I'm fine. How about you guys. Are you guys alright?" Zhang Jiale even managed to ask everyone in return.

Everyone looked at one another once again.

"Since everyone's fine, let's go." Han Wenqing waved and turned around with no hesitation. The six members of Tyranny walked down the stadium with their heads held high. Applause started to ring in the stadium. Even though the fans felt disappointed in the loss, they had seen how the team performed. From beginning to end, they didn't see the team weaken or see them give up. They continued to fight and struggle. Their performance was worthy of the applause, so they didn't need to feel ashamed for their loss.

The applause grew louder, and the six from Tyranny motioned towards the audience by waving their hands. Despite losing in the match, they wouldn't fall. No matter what burden they carried, that wouldn't ever happen.

The audience was clapping, so the workers on site put down whatever they were doing to clap as well. Even members of Samsara, who won the championships, stood on the side and clapped. It was not for themselves, but for Tyranny. Despite losing the match, they won respect from every single person.

An award ceremony was held on the stage for Samsara. Like last year, the team collected the trophy and didn't really celebrate. However, they were the second team to win the championships twice in a row after Excellent Era, so they might just create a new dynasty. This was a fact no one would ignore.

In the press conference after the match, Team Tyranny went first. All six members that appeared in the team match sat on stage. They gazed at the reporters below them and realised that every one of them seemed to look more solemn than them.

"Can we start?" In the end, it was the team captain, Han Wenqing, who asked first.

"Uh, it was a very regretful loss. Do you have anything to say?" A reporter seized the opportunity to ask.

"It was regretful indeed, but there's no other way because there can only be one champion." Han Wenqing spoke.

"What are your thoughts on how each team performed?" Someone asked. By losing the competition with a clear gap in the scores, Tyranny's performance needed to be deeply looked into. However, their situation was different from their first match. By the time the finals had reached this point, everyone had thought about the problem of Tyranny's players running out of stamina. The reporters were clear about this, otherwise, the team wouldn't receive such applause from losing, and their questions wouldn't be so courteous.

"Both sides worked very hard. I think no matter who won, both teams would have been worthy of the title." Han Wenqing said.

"As for the coming year, does Tyranny or the players of Tyranny have any plans or intentions?" The reporter asked. Here, the reporter purposefully emphasised "the players of Tyranny". All the reporters peeked intentionally or unintentionally towards Zhang Jiale. It was like how all the players of Tyranny cared about him when they lost. The reporters knew that Zhang Jiale would be the one who was impacted the most by this loss.

"The same as always." In the end, Han Wenqing replied in such a brief manner.

However, the reporters cared too much about this matter, and no longer cared if they were being cruel. One of them finally named specifically in his question. "I would like to ask for Zhang Jiale's personal opinion, would you like to say something?"

"Me?" Zhang Jiale looked at the reporters below when he was named. He even gave a laugh as he said, "Aren't I already used to this?"

The reporters were startled.

This was a self deprecating joke, but no one was able to laugh.

Did he make this kind of joke because he had lost heart?

However, then they heard Zhang Jiale continue to speak. "As for the future, it's what our captain said: the same as always."

"Mm, nicely summarised. The same as always." Lin Jingyan nodded.

The reporters originally wanted to ask Lin Jingyan as well, but when he showed the same attitude, they fully understood. Even though this was a painful loss, it wouldn't be able to strike down any of them. In the upcoming matches, they would still see these unyielding old generals continue to struggle and strive for the glory that they had been pursuing for all these years.

The reporters had nothing left to ask about the finals The other members in Tyranny weren't old players that were about to retire. Taking Zhang Xinjie for example, he was part of the Golden Generation and was still at the peak of his career. This was why everyone's sorrowful emotions weren't targeted as deeply towards them.

"Uh, next season, Ye Xiu and his Team Happy will be in the Alliance. With how the league is usually arranged, it's very likely for them to be matched with Tyranny in the first round. Do you have anything to say to him? You guys are old acquaintances after all!" The reporters started to ask questions outside of the topic.

Everyone in Happy was watching the broadcast. They were all in sync as they looked towards Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu drank his tea calmly.

"Too bad... I would definitely be made fun of by that guy." Zhang Jiale muttered.

"Ah? What do you mean?" A reporter asked immediately, but Zhang Jiale chose to stay quiet.

"I hope he can focus on the matches, so he won't bring trouble to everyone online." Lin Jingyan said.

"Hm, what do you mean by that?" The reporter immediately asked again, but Lin Jingyan also chose to stay quiet.

Everyone looked at Han Wenqing.

"Beat him. The same as always." Han Wenqing said.

The same as always again. The problem is that you haven't beaten him that many times in the past! Isn't saying "the same as always" a bit inappropriate? The reporters criticised silently. Most of the information they got from Han Wenqing would include this motto.

In the end, all the reporters looked hopefully towards Zhang Xinjie, hoping to get some hot topics out of him.

"Time's up." Zhang Xinjie looked at the time. "We should finish!"

"Ah ah ah... Vice-captain Zhang, could you talk a bit more about Ye Xiu?" The reporters wailed with grief. Unfortunately, the time was up, and Zhang Xinjie cared more about the time than Ye Xiu. Team Tyranny's players got up one by one and left the press conference.

Chapter 1079: Happy, Champions?

After Team Tyranny, the reporters interviewed Team Samsara. Defending their championship title was obviously an incredible achievement. As soon as Team Samsara went up on stage, they were met with fervent congratulations from the crowd. But after contrasting this excitement with the disappointment from Tyranny's old generals, some of the crowd felt sad, especially the old reporters that had followed Glory for so many years. Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale. Their work always revolved around these few players. How could they not have a bit of emotional investment into them?

The clash between the new and old was difficult to avoid. The joy and elation flowing from Samsara's side made it seem like it was the coming of a new era for both Glory and the news scene. As for them? Would they be like the old generals of the pro scene and gradually fade away?

Definitely not! Everything must continue on like in the past.

The old reporters suddenly felt a wave of empathy surging inside them. Immediately afterwards, the incisive questions flew towards Samsara.

"First of all, congratulations Team Samsara for defending your title. What I want to ask is whether or not the war of attrition employed to win the third match was chosen because you saw that the old Team Tyranny players lacked the stamina and energy to maintain their peak conditions?"

"Yes." Zhou Zekai said.

"In the second match, we realized that Team Tyranny didn't seem to be too good at long wars of attrition. This is why we decided to employ this type of strategy in the third match." Jiang Botao immediately added. For touchy subjects like this, who knew how the reporters would spin these types of one-word answers from Zhou Zekai.

Not good at long wars of attrition…... Jiang Botao summed it up with what seemed to be a good explanation, but the crucial question about Team Tyranny's stamina issues was dodged. How could the reporters let him get by so easily?

"Then why do you think Tyranny isn't good at long wars of attrition?" A reporter asked despite already knowing the answer. He had already made his decision. If Samsara dared to act stupid answering this question, he wouldn't let these shams go no matter what.

"Uh, during this period of one month, Tyranny played nine intense matches for the playoffs. This must have been very exhausting. Their stamina issues in the later stages were the key to our Samsara's victory."

In the end, Samsara gave a clear reply to this question.

"Oh, then let's say if Tyranny had only played four matches before the finals like Samsara and had enough time to fully recover, would that have made any impact on the results?"

"The match would have definitely been more difficult." Jiang Botao replied.　　

"Then, do you think Samsara would have still won the finals?" This reporter's questions were becoming more and more harsh. He was practically implying that Samsara had won with an unfair advantage.

"Competition is filled with countless variables. This is why we keep playing on stage. If you could accurately deduce the outcome of a match, then what's the point in competing? From an objective perspective, I'm not able to answer your question. However, from Samsara's position, I believe that Samsara would have won no matter who our opponents had been!"

Jiang Botao's reply was powerful and resonating. This reporter was clearly unable to counter it because he also knew that there was no such thing as having an unfair advantage. Every element was a part of a victory. If not, when a powerhouse beat teams due to having better players and better characters, wouldn't that also be considered as having an unfair advantage?

"Captain Zhou, is that what you think too?" Unable to make a counter argument, the reporter immediately switched targets. He also knew that once he switched to Zhou Zekai, this interview topic would stop here.

"Yes." Zhou Zekai's reply didn't disappoint him.

"I have no other questions." This reporter immediately followed.

Afterwards, there were no more questions with malicious intentions. Once the unoriginal questions like what are your thoughts on the victory, the reporters once again switched topics and gave a similar question to what they asked Tyranny: "Next season, Ye Xiu and his Team Happy will be in the pro scene. What are Samsara's thoughts about them? Do you think Happy can succeed?"

When everyone in Happy heard the first part of the question, they were almost about to look at Ye Xiu to see his reaction. But in the end, the reporter asked about Team Happy as a whole. This was different from Tyranny. The reporter had considered that Samsara was a part of a different generation than Ye Xiu. Samsara wasn't like Tyranny, who had players that had old relationships with him. As a result, the reporter didn't concentrate on Ye Xiu.

"That depends on how you define successful." Jiang Botao said.

"It seems like they intend on becoming the champions." The reporter said with uncertainty.

Pfft!!!

This time, quite a few people at the scene laughed. Samsara's players were sitting on stage and knew that the camera was on them, so they were able to maintain their composure. However, expressions of astonishment could clearly be seen on all of them. The reporters weren't like them. After laughing, no one waited for Samsara to reply. The reporters crowded around that poor reporter: "Where'd you hear that from?" The press conference erupted into an uproar.

"I heard a player from Heavenly Swords inadvertently leak it!!" When that reporter saw how everyone wanted to gnaw at him, he immediately confessed.

"How could someone from Heavenly Swords know?" Someone asked.

"After the Challenger League finals, Happy stayed over at City B. They have a good relationship with Heavenly Swords and are constantly in touch with one another." That reporter immediately replied.

"Is what that person said reliable? Or was it just a joke?" As soon as someone heard it was a private exchange, he didn't believe it.

"I don't know either!" That reporter said bitterly. He had just overheard it while passing by. He couldn't confirm it either, so he didn't know if it was the truth or a joke.

"It was probably a joke. It has to be." The reporters gradually calmed down.

"What are Samsara's thoughts on this?" A reporter suddenly remembered who the main characters were and promptly threw the question over to Samsara.　　

Jiang Botao stared blankly. He felt like if he had to answer, he would probably say that he felt like it was a joke. Even though Happy beat Excellent Era, miracles couldn't keep happening over and over again, no? Happy's strength was still rather limited. Saying that Happy wanted to win the championships was too much. But if he actually said that it was a joke, it would be hard to avoid people from thinking that Samsara held contempt for Happy. But if he said that it was probably the truth, then.... it would be hard to avoid people from thinking that he was just saying fake words!

This is a difficult question to answer!

Jiang Botao, who had been very adept at answering questions the entire time, was actually stumped. After a long while, he finally replied: "It doesn't matter what Happy's goal is. Samsara will always try our hardest and beat our opponents."

The question was dodged with an ambiguous answer. However, the question had been a joke itself, so the reporter let it go. Soon afterwards, the press conference for Samsara concluded. After the crowd dispersed, quite a few reporters became reinvigorated and started opening up their address books to confirm what exactly had been said.

The broadcast for the finals had ended. Everyone in Happy was still stunned from the commotion from that question. Not long afterwards, Chen Guo's cell phone rang. Chen Guo took out her cell phone. The call was from Lou Guanning. After picking it up, Chen Guo was able to get a profound understanding of how terrifying reporters could be. Didn't the press conference just end? The reporters interested in this question had already found ways to ask Heavenly Swords. One of those reporters had found a way to directly contact Heavenly Sword's boss, Lou Guanning. As a result, Lou Guanning quickly called Chen Guo, asking how he should answer.

"How should he answer?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

"Of course I was serious." Ye Xiu said.

"He was serious." Chen Guo replied to Lou Guanning.

"Haha, how fun!" Lou Guanning seemed to be looking forward to the exposure and hung up the phone with a laugh.

"You're not staying low-profile at all!" Chen Guo held her cell phone and sighed. Starting from when the Challenger League first started, Happy had been quite high-profile. As soon as they began, they came out saying that they would topple Excellent Era and received quite a bit of ridicule for it. Now that they had actually done it, who knew where those haters went. But now, Chen Guo knew that when news came out with Happy's statement that their goal was to win the championships, these haters would probably come out again. The confidence from those haters would probably be even higher, no?

"It doesn't matter." Ye Xiu said nonchalantly, "In any case, no matter what happens, we have to strive for victory."

"For this goal, everyone is going to need to work even harder!!" Chen Guo encouraged the team.

"Of course!" Steamed Bun replied excitedly. Tang Rou smiled, showing her ambitiousness. The one who couldn't stay calm was the one who was usually the calmest, Qiao Yifan.

Become the champions? Their next goal was actually going to be the top of Glory. Qiao Yifan felt like he was going dizzy. But when he saw his teammates, he knew that they weren't joking. Happy was going to be rushing for the championship title? This was all going too quickly!　　

"Okay, it's getting late. Everyone should get ready to go to bed!" Chen Guo looked at the time and called out. Happy had a fairly strict work and rest schedule now. No one would be allowed to live a disorderly lifestyle like before. The memory of Ye Xiu sleeping for a very long time due to exhaustion was something still fresh in her mind. Next up, they would be preparing for the Pro League. Everyone in Happy needed to be in their best state the entire time. A disciplined sleep schedule was essential.

The next day, the various esports media put the finals as the lead story.

Samsara defends their title. A tragic conclusion for Tyranny. But between these two teams, another team had squeezed its way in.

Happy, Champions???

The title of the story added in three question marks. The article itself was filled with incredulity. You could say that maybe Happy didn't understand their situation. But Happy had Ye Xiu; how could he not have a good grasp of his team? You could say that he was being serious... maybe after Happy beat Excellent Era, even Ye Xiu was so excited that he couldn't tell east from west anymore?

The mainstream media reports were already polite about it. But in other places, articles with titles like "This Century's Biggest Joke" quickly popped up. The various teams also soon received inquiries from the media asking about their thoughts on this matter, making all the teams feel gloomy. During this period of time, how many questions relating to Happy had they answered? What's up with this team!

Chapter 1080: Splitting Rewards

Aiming to be champions?

Happy's statement was dismissed with a laugh by the pro teams.

If it wasn't that Happy had Ye Xiu, the pro teams would probably think that these guys were having delusions of grandeur after their unexpected victory against Excellent Era. However, since Ye Xiu was present, they wouldn't be so childish.

"It's joke, right?"

"They're probably doing this to get more publicity."

"They don't really need to keep coming up with these things. They already have a strong enough presence."

The teams all said different things, but their tone was generally full of ridicule. Aim to be champions? The majority of the teams in the Alliance wouldn't dare say this. Happy really was daring!

Happy was flourishing. After obtaining a sponsorship from Feike, Happy managed to x obtain another two more sponsors. These were all from sponsors who had always taken an interest in the Glory Alliance and didn't mind giving a share to Happy. However, they were like Feike, already sponsoring other teams in the Alliance. They invested in Happy, wanting to watch how things went.

With these three contracts, Happy had already received nearly 5,000,000 RMB in sponsorship money. For a grassroots team, this was a very solid support. After that, the prize money for winning the Challenger League, their share of TV broadcasting revenue, their share of ticket revenue, etc. all arrived. With the amount of attention that the Challenger League received, no matter if it was the TV broadcast or the venue tickets, the revenue gained was far greater than previous years. The Alliance was very sincere and generous with their competitions. The teams didn't just get prize money, but also shares of all sorts of profits. Many other competitions would just deal with this through just the prize money.

Just winning the Challenger League was worth 5,000,000 RMB. Considering the influence of the Challenger League, this was no small amount. The Alliance had clearly considered how the winner would be entering the pro league the following season. This money was also a source of support for the team. With the prize money on top of their shares for everything else, Team Happy had managed to earn over 10,000,000 RMB through just the Challenger League alone. This showed Chen Guo exactly how financially powerful the Glory scene was now. Of course, due to the special circumstances of this year's Challenger League, the shares of profit were naturally higher than previous years.

With over 10,000,000 RMB for funds, Chen Guo felt much more secure. Although the 18,000,000 RMB earned with the materials from selling the skill point guide could have been invested into the team by Wei Chen, this was just too much. If they really invested it all into the team, Chen Guo felt that her title as the boss would be more of a title than actual reality. But now that the team had managed to earn some money on their own, Chen Guo felt much better about using it.

As soon as the money arrived, Chen Guo didn't hesitate to take out the 5,000,000 RMB in prize money and divide it up between the members of Happy. Even though Happy's players had never seemed to care much about this sort of thing, they couldn't just go with the flow and continue like this. In the past, they didn't have the funds, so they just got by like that. Now that they had gained a significant amount of profit, it definitely had to be shared.

The division of this money was very overwhelming. Luo Ji and An Wenyi were both just university students. Suddenly gaining several hundred thousand made them at a loss as to what to do with it.

As for Ye Xiu, the bank card he was given was immediately thrown into the drawer, becoming a member of his large pile of Glory smurfs.

Wei Chen? He was a person with 18,000,000 RMB in his hands. After obtaining the several hundred thousand, he simply nodded, saying nonchalantly, "Mm, not bad." Chen Guo wanted to hit him for that.

Tang Rou smiled, thanking Chen Guo as she accepted the bank card, not at all intending to decline it. However, Chen Guo knew that she had even more of a right than Wei Chen to act nonchalant. Chen Guo looked down on Wei Chen for his response. Then, that night, after everyone had gone to bed, Chen Guo realized that Tang Ruo had forgotten her card on the table and nearly cried. With a weak password like 123456, anyone could just take the card and the money. My lady, you were never this careless with Soft Mist's account card!

Steamed Bun, having been a bouncer before for an Internet cafe, had very little wealth. He was delighted with the sum of several hundred thousand, and emotionally exclaimed that he had truly found a good boss, his future was really bright!

Wu Chen and Qiao Yifan came from pro teams. Wu Chen was even the ace of his team. Although his team had been rather weak and their income couldn't compare to the Gods, getting several hundred thousand a year wasn't hard. Qiao Yifan was a rookie, so he wouldn't have that high of an income, but since he was a part of a powerhouse team, he had a good understanding of their scene. This prize money was nothing unexpected for him.

Chen Guo had been a little hesitant when giving Mo Fan his share. Mo Fan rarely went on the field and Chen Guo had split the prize money evenly, not bothering with taking contribution into account. In these beginning stages, the team was still growing in many ways and Chen Guo felt that this sort of thing was far too troublesome to deal with. Plus, Ye Xiu, who had made the greatest contributions, had agreed with her decision wholeheartedly. Then what was there to worry about? It was those like Luo Ji and Wu Chen, who hadn't had much play time, that felt a little bad about getting the same as everyone else, but they still ended up accepting the money under Chen Guo's resolute attitude. Chen Guo's hesitation towards Mo Fan was because she wasn't sure about him. In truth, it was because they didn't interact and therefore, she had no idea what that guy was thinking. She didn't know if he was planning on staying with Happy on their journey.

But on the other hand, Mo Fan had stayed with them throughout this year. It had nothing to do with what he would do in the future. Although he had made limited contributions, he shouldn't be left out if everyone got it. Therefore, Mo Fan ended up with an equal share. After hearing the amount, he had uncharacteristically shown a hint of shock. It seemed like he didn't come from a wealthy background either.

There was another, who was resolute in declining this money.

Sun Zheping. Chen Guo called him about transferring his share of the money over, but Sun Zheping, who had already left Happy, simply laughed and told her not to bother before directly hanging up.

That was too generous, wasn't it?

　

Chen Guo didn't want to give up, but then Ye Xiu had said, "There's no need. He isn't someone who will change his mind."

Chen Guo, holding the final card, didn't really know what to say. Ye Xiu glanced at her. "Did you forget your own share?"

"Ah?" Chen Guo was stunned for a moment. She really hadn't thought about herself. Even if she did, she wouldn't think she deserved a share.

"Just take it as leftovers. For the capitalist." Ye Xiu said.

"Hey hey, who're you calling a capitalist?" Chen Guo objected.

Happy was dividing up their small reward while over with the Alliance, the champions had been decided and were receiving all their large rewards. The Alliance Championship prize money was, considering the influence of the Glory Alliance, a very small amount, only 10,000,000, twice as much as the Challenger League. Apart from that, there were rewards for regular season rankings, but the amount was even less substantial. Twenty teams, a total of 16,800,000. With the money split according to ranking, the highest ranked team only received 1,600,000. The last ranked team received a measly 80,000.

It was obvious that the Alliance no longer depended on prize money to sustain itself. 10,000,000 RMB in prize money? That definitely wasn't the reason any team fought so hard.

What everyone sought was the glory that the championship trophy represented, What teams depended on for survival were things such as broadcasting profits, sponsorships, ticket fees, and similar forms of revenue. And these forms of revenue were affected by the influence the team had. As for the most direct way of increasing their influence, it was winning the championships. Happy's Challenger League championship victory had brought them all sorts of income. In reality, this was a perfect example of the current system.

The season came to a close with the champions decided. However, because of this year's update, there had been a break in the middle of the season, so once the championships ended, July soon arrived. The players of the pro teams began their holiday, but the summer transfer window opened and the managers of the clubs began to get busy.

Over with Happy, the press conference Feike had wanted to hold, but never had the chance to, finally occurred, officially declaring their sponsorship of Happy. Even though they weren't giving much funds, with Happy's current popularity, they managed to do something big with very little cost. Feike was very satisfied with their investment. In this press conference, Happy had taken the chance to announce Su Mucheng's free transfer. This wasn't unexpected for anyone, but, following that, the announcement that Dancing Rain was coming to Happy with Su Mucheng was big news.

Dancing Rain was an All-Star level account. A grassroots like Happy somehow had the courage to obtain it. It looked like their goal to win the championships wasn't a joke.

Su Mucheng was free transfering, so naturally there was no transfer fee. But the media was enthusiastically discussing Dancing Rain's transfer fee. However, in the contract for Dancing Rain's transfer, the transfer fee had an NDA protecting it. Tao Xuan had obviously not wanted the special price for Dancing Rain to affect the sale of Excellent Era. If everyone thought that Excellent Era was doing a huge clearance sale and came with offers of just a few hundred thousand, Tao Xuan would probably die crying.

With Su Mucheng and Dancing Rain, Team Happy suddenly seemed far stronger. Counting Ye Xiu, Happy was a team with two All-Star level players! Not even half the teams of the Alliance had such a lineup!

What moves would Happy make next? The day the summer transfer window opened, Happy had unexpectedly become the main show. The media was making all sorts of guesses. Excellent Era was also a hot topic. The transfer window was open and Team Excellent Era had quite a lot of characters and players. After so long, the transfers should have come to the end of their negotiations. Where would they all go?

As for the Golden Generation that everyone had once been clustered around, they weren't much of a topic anymore these days. This year was the second year where the Golden Generation would have to renew their contracts, so everyone had been attentively waiting to see if any would leave their teams. But in the first half of this year, all the teams had declared that the players of the Golden Generation wouldn't be leaving their teams, apart from Su Mucheng and Xiao Shiqin who were unknowns back then.

Now, Su Mucheng had joined Happy. What about Xiao Shiqin? Where would he go? As someone who could also free transfer, he had a lot of choices.

But before any news about Xiao Shiqin came out, Excellent Era's first bomb, since the news that it was being sold, fell.

Sun Xiang, One Autumn Leaf. The two were transfering to Team Samsara for 28,000,000 RMB.

Chapter 1081: The 28,000,000 Transfer

Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf.

If Excellent Era were still a powerhouse in the Alliance, this would have been a very cheap price for Samsara. No character in the Alliance could compare to the Battle God, One

Autumn Leaf. Even if his three-peat had been achieved a long time ago, characters

didn't age. The legend of the Battle God's era would forever be etched onto

him. Along with his former owner Ye Xiu being excessively low-profile, all of the

people's hopes went onto the Battle God's shoulders. No other Glory character

could compare in this manner.

28,000,000. If Excellent Era hadn't fallen so far, this price might not even be enough to buy One Autumn Leaf alone. Even if his prowess wasn't that much greater than the other God-level characters, One Autumn Leaf had always been the symbol of Glory's king. If you asked any Glory player which character was number one, everyone would answer One Autumn Leaf. There was no other answer. Even though Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer had won two championships in a row, he didn't have the same legacy as One Autumn Leaf. In the past two three years, he was the most popular among the new generation of players. However, even greater achievements had been accomplished by another in the past. In more people's eyes, number one still belonged to One Autumn Leaf.

But now, Excellent Era had capsized. One Autumn Leaf hadn't stood at the top for a long time. In the end, One Autumn Leaf was abandoned along with the team by Tao Xuan.

20,000,000. This was the price that Ye Xiu had heard from Lou Guanning for One Autumn Leaf's price. Clearly, due to Excellent Era's current situation, One Autumn Leaf's value sunk along with the team. Of course, different teams might get different offers. For example, the price of 20,000,000 given to Heavenly Swords might be different than what Samsara was offered. If the price was also 20,000,000, then Sun Xiang's transfer price would be 8,000,000. Compared to the price that Excellent Era had paid for him, it was higher instead of lower. That didn't make sense. Even though his talent and genius had been recognized by the scene, after Sun Xiang

transferred, Excellent Era had been relegated. Then, after a year through the Challenger League, they ended up losing the finals. Even if these disastrous results weren't because of him, his value would still be greatly affected. Excellent Era was currently on a sale too. His value increasing instead of decreasing wasn't logical.

Neither side revealed how this price had been negotiated. However, from the total price of 28,000,000 and Excellent Era's current situation, Excellent Era had gotten a good price. Or perhaps Samsara hadn't negotiated too hard. It was also possible that there were many others wanting to buy, so with Samsara's ambitions, Samsara didn't negotiate too much and quickly slammed down the hammer.

There were numerous guesses. In the end, most people thought it was because of this type of reason.

After all, whether it was Sun Xiang or One Autumn Leaf, who wouldn't want them? Excellent Era might be in a difficult situation, but those two were very valuable. There was no need to worry that they could not be sold. The buyers had competition, so it was hard to avoid the price not being raised. If you thought about it like that, it was easy to see this current outcome.

But in any case, this wasn't the focus of everyone's concern. Everyone cared more about the result itself: Samsara had taken in Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf.

As the newly championed team, it was somewhat surprising to see them make such a huge move so quickly. Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf joining the Alliance again wasn't an easy decision to make for any team. A core-level God, the number one character, it was a huge transfer that could completely remake a team.

However, Samsara had Zhou Zekai, the indisputable number one player in the Alliance. No one believed that Zhou Zekai would choose to leave the team. Even less people thought that Team Samsara would change their core that had brought them victory all this time.

But now, there were two core players. How was Samsara planning on resolving this issue? It was a different situation than Tyranny. Tyranny's four ace players sounded even more problematic, but in reality, it was different. For one, when Han Wenqing declared something, even the club's boss would retreat. His authority in Tyranny was untouchable. What's more, Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan were at the ends of their career. They came to Tyranny because their desire to be the champions had yet to die. As for their core position, they didn't care anymore. They had been the core for so many years and were done it with long ago. Champions. They wanted to be champions. Zhang Jiale had given up so much for that goal. Who cared about being the core?

Samsara was different. Zhou Zekais brilliance on stage might be spectacular, but he himself was like a piece of wood. He was a reliable ace player, but he definitely wasn't a good leader. Samsara's players were able to faithfully play alongside him, but what about Sun Xiang? He was a very prideful person. His addition to the team would be a huge challenge towards Zhou Zekai's weak leadership. Would Team Samsara stay as harmonious as before? Would they put Sun Xiang as the core and Zhou Zekai as the support? That didn't seem to be possible. For one, a team had to consider the fans. Such an upstage would definitely not go well with them. What's more, Sun Xiang didn't really seem to be much of a leader? And from what they had seen from him so far, if Zhou Zekai's leadership ability tended towards zero, then Sun Xiang's leadership ability was a negative number…..

Samsara was going to be busy this summer!

Everyone in the Glory scene sighed. They clearly thought that the conflicting chemistry between the two would be a difficult problem to resolve. However, in the new Esports Home issue, besides this transfer, there was an article, written by famed author with the penname Cha Xiaoxia, commenting on the transfer.

Cha Xiaoxia felt that although Samsara's championship victory seemed to be a huge victory, a great danger hid beneath it. Tyranny's problem with their old players' stamina had given them an opportunity to win. If Tyranny had been able to keep up their peak form all the way through, it would be hard to say if Samsara would have been able to win. From the first match in the finals, Tyranny had a way to suppress Zhou Zekai and Samsara's tempo. Facing Tyrannny's stable formation, the problem with Samsara's lack of a direct attacker could clearly be seen.

Samsara had been able to win because of the tournament format. That was what Cha Xiaoxia believed. If it had been the previous format, it wouldn't have been as exhausting, and Chao Xiaoxia believed that Tyranny would have most likely won in the end.

Samsara absolutely recognized this issue. So even though they won the championships, Samsara wouldn't be like last year and not make any changes. This was because there was a team that could suppress them.

Next season, Tyranny's old generals would definitely focus on fixing their stamina issue. Samsara couldn't hope for Tyranny to stay the same. Samsara needed to take the initiative to improve. However, improving wasn't something that could be done by fixing up their original foundation. Samsara had reached a bottleneck and needed to break through. As a result, they transferred over Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf.

This might be why Samsara was willing to spend 28,000,000 to quickly complete the transfer despite winning the championships. Cha Xiaoxia wrote. They needed a direct attacker. This type of attacker needed to be able to break through the concrete defense formed by Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Xinjie. Just from that requirement, very few players qualified. This wasn't something that an average pro player could hope to do. The only ones that could shoulder that burden were the Alliance's top attackers and top close combat characters.

Thus, Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf. In addition to Excellent Era's current plight, anyone would make this choice. The key to their breakthrough had been found. However, it came

with a problem. Sun Xiang was certainly a qualified choice, but because of how qualified he was, how to resolve the inner conflicts in the team would be big issue. With how prideful Sun Xiang was, would he be willing to revolve around Zhou Zekai as the core?

Cha Xiaoxia also discussed this question in his article. He was optimistic about Samsara dealing with this problem. First of all, he looked favorably upon Sun Xiang's transformation. Getting relegated from the Alliance, losing the Challenger League, up until now, no God in the Alliance had suffered through such losses. Sun Xiang had once been a very prideful player and he still was in the Challenger League, but after these consecutive failures, shouldn't he turn his head to look at how he fell so far and examine himself?

Sun Xiang's attitude would undoubtedly play a critical role in this problem. If he became more mature after learning from these failures, melding in harmoniously with Samsara wasn't impossible.

In addition, Cha Xiaoxia mentioned the "most underrated player in the Alliance", Jiang Botao.

Samsara's vice-captain Jiang Botao had placed fifth in total votes for All-Stars. This seemed contradictory to "underrated" since he was clearly thought of very highly.

However, Cha Xiaoxia felt like Jiang Botao was thought highly because of Zhou Zekai's halo and the team's identity as champions.There were even people who claimed that even their grandma could pair with Zhou Zekai and win the championships.

That statement was naturally an exaggeration, but the contempt inside it was clear as day. Every player in Samsara had this issue. Whenever Samsara did well, everyone would credit it with Zhou Zekai. As for the others, they were just there to bask in his light.

Cha Xiaoxia didn't think this was the case.　　

Chao Xiaoxia wrote that Jiang Botao was adept at communication. Anyone would feel comfortable interacting with him. He could show consideration for everyone in any scenario, and he wouldn't steal the spotlight either. Outside of the stage, Jiang Botao was this type of person. On stage, he was an expert at connecting everyone together. If he could successfully meld Zhou Zekai into Samsara, he should be able to do the same with Sun Xiang. Jiang Botao was the glue that held the team together.

Chao Xiaoxia straight up gave Jiang Botao a nickname. After excitedly analyzing the transfer and talking about his expectations for the battle of dragons between Tyranny and Samsara next season, he suddenly switched topics: people undoubtedly had high hopes for these two teams, but he felt like there was another team that shouldn't be ignored --- the other champions this year, Team Happy.

"People are treating their declaration to win the championships next season as a joke, but I believe in them. What can I do? I'm already a Team Happy fanboy." Cha Xiaoxia wrote.

Chapter 1082: Excellent Era Tagged Transfers

As an experienced writer, Cha Xiaoxia had quite a lot of influence in the Glory scene and quite a few fans as well. His analysis was accurate and logical, and as soon as his article was out, agreement spread among his readers: that's right, it was exactly as how he said it was. Then, with the last half-joking sentence about being a fanboy, many people began to take Happy more seriously. Happy's true strength immediately became a hot topic online, and many people were all eagerly anticipating an analysis of Happy's strength from Cha Xiaoxia.

Apart from these hot topics, a few less eye-catching transfers were also happening in the background. During this time each year, there would definitely be a few free transfers. With everyone's attention on the Golden Generation, they had overlooked a few others. Among these free transfers, there was actually one rather well-known player.

Liu Hao.

The old Excellent Era vice-captain had come to Thunderclap in exchange for Xiao Shiqin's transfer. In this season, Thunderclap performed rather well, hovering around the playoffs area throughout the entire season. Even though they didn't manage to get into the playoffs in the end, it wasn't someone people would look into. Thunderclap had also viewed Liu Hao as their core during this, although he never managed to do as well as Xiao Shiqin had.

Even so, Liu Hao had refused to renew his year-long contract with Thunderclap. He had never planned to stay in Thunderclap long. He had even planned on leaving during the winter transfer window. Who would have expected that the winter transfer window would coincide with the big update? All the teams in the market became cautious. No one wanted to fortify their strong teams during an uncertain time like just after a big update. As a result, Liu Hao's hopes were crushed.

Now, he was a free player whose contract had expired. As the previous vice-captain of Excellent Era, Liu Hao's ability was quite outstanding. He hadn't managed to be voted into All-Stars, but he hadn't been too far from getting in either. It was just unfortunate that one of his competitors of the same class was Jiang Botao. With Samsara rising through the ranks, Jiang Botao's popularity skyrocketed and unfortunately, Liu Hao found himself squeezed out .

Liu Hao wasn't at all satisfied with this situation, and he looked down on a team like Thunderclap, so he refused the offer to renew his contract. When summer arrived, Liu Hao finally received the offers he was hoping for. Among them, there was finally a powerhouse that he was satisfied with.

Team Wind Howl!

Liu Hao transferred to Wind Howl. This big news in the beginning of July was second only to Sun Xiang and Su Mucheng's transfers. These people were all coincidentally from Excellent Era. Even though Liu Hao had already left Excellent Era for a year, it was clear that his Excellent Era tag was far larger than his Thunderclap one.

In this time, the three transfers had people feeling that it was quite a shame to see how far Excellent Era had fallen. As for Liu Hao joining Wind Howl, people viewed this as a strong addition to a strong team. Ace player Tang Hao, the God of playing dirty Fang Rui, Best Rookie Zhao Yuzhe, and then the addition of Liu Hao. This lineup didn't look extremely spectacular, but it was very solid. With the positions of all the core members on the teams stable, getting a player like Liu Hao, who was just slightly worse than the others, was a good upgrade.

　　

However, Liu Hao's transfer reminded everyone of another person.

Xiao Shiqin. His contract had also expired. Even Liu Hao, who had been traded by Excellent Era for him, had already left, but there was still no news on Xiao Shiqin. Xiao Shiqin would naturally also receive a significant number of offers, and he would definitely have a wider range of choices than Liu Hao. Where would he go?

In the discussions, the powerhouse teams were the most commonly brought up. No matter which one took in Xiao Shiqin, they would gain an incredibly spectacular lineup. The Alliance seemed to be walking towards an era where the greatest players all gravitated towards each other.

But when news of Xiao Shiqin's transfer came out, it made everyone's eyes pop. He had chosen to return to Team Thunderclap.

To become a champion, he had left Thunderclap and came to Excellent Era in pursuit of his future. Then, a year later, Excellent Era hadn't managed to even return to the Alliance and instead was facing disbandment. A few mean and sarcastic fans had already begun bringing up his past choices and mocking him for it. No one had ever guessed that he would return to Thunderclap. Everyone had thought that after Excellent Era's defeat, Xiao Shiqin would work harder to prove that he had made the correct decision in leaving Thunderclap and join a team that was likely to win the championships. However, he returned to Thunderclap instead. This was no different from personally admitting his mistake in leaving. Did Xiao Shiqin not even had the courage to prove himself anymore?

No matter what rumors flew about, all of Team Thunderclap, including most of the fans, warmly welcomed Xiao Shiqin.

"Welcome home!"

The day Xiao Shiqin came back to Club Thunderclap, he saw many fans gathered outside with signs welcoming his arrival. When Xiao Shiqin had chosen to leave, they had accepted his decision, and when Xiao Shiqin was in an awkward situation, they still supported him.

Xiao Shiqin couldn't hold it in anymore, his tears falling onto his glasses. He got out of the car crying and returned to his old club amidst his fans. He had returned home.

Then, Team Thunderclap announced that the club would be taking back the Mechanic account Life Extinguisher, who had left with Xiao Shiqin a year ago, as well as transferring Excellent Era's Cleric, Zhang Jiaxing, over for a club record transaction of 9.5 million.

This was a very low price for an All-Star level account and the main healer of a powerhouse team. However, Life Extinguisher was a character that Thunderclap had brought up. Returning to Thunderclap with Xiao Shiqin didn't seem like a fortification. It was Zhang Jiaxing's arrival that was considered a strong addition to the team. With their original healer having announced their retirement, Zhang Jiaxing's timely arrival was a boost to their strength.

Thunderclap had another player who had been transferred over last year, Elementalist player He Ming. However, his contract was not just a year long like Liu Hao though. He was very anxious seeing Liu Hao leaving, while himself being unable to leave since he couldn't transfer yet. He had been prepared to ask if he could be transferred. But now with Xiao Shiqin's return and Thunderclap's commendable act of managing to snatch Zhang Jiaxing as well, He Ming suddenly felt that Thunderclap might not be so bad. After all, he wasn't as outstanding as Liu Hao. With all the powerhouses having stable lineups, he would have a hard time joining a powerhouse team as a core member. With this, it seemed that staying in Thunderclap, he might at least become the main part of a team that could make the playoffs. There was still hope.

Just as He Ming was feeling satisfied with this future, he received a notice from the club that he wasn't a part of the club's future plans. The club had decided to transfer him, and he could contact possible other teams himself. The club would support him.

He couldn't leave when he wanted to, and he had to leave when he wanted to stay. He Ming was gritting his teeth so hard they might break. Plus, the club had already clearly stated that he couldn't just stay here and refuse to leave either. Pro players needed to compete, and those who weren't a part of the club's future plans naturally wouldn't be asked to do so. Getting an income without needing to compete? This seemed like paradise, but for pro players, this was an act that would destroy their futures. He Ming was a person with some aspirations, so he could only go and find a new team, seeing Thunderclap's attitude.

Samsara, Tyranny, Tiny Herb, Blue Rain? He Ming wanted to go to these teams, but which one would pay him any attention?

In the end, Thunderclap contacted a new club for him. He Ming nearly cried when he was informed of the team. Team Miracle! The team that had only just gotten approval to join the Alliance, the team that would be fighting to stay in the Alliance. He seemed to remember being Excellent Era's sixth player. It didn't make sense that he would fall to a team like this. He Ming wanted to refuse, but after the successive rejections from powerhouse teams, his confidence had taken a hit and he was a little afraid that no team would accept him. Just as he was hesitating, Miracle contacted him with all sorts of promises, such as how Miracle would continue to strengthen itself and definitely wouldn't accept being a team of the lowest tier.

　

He Ming, seeing that no other team seemed to have any visible intentions to take him in, was rather moved by all that Miracle had promised him. He thought to himself, chicken head and phoenix tail. If he couldn't be the tail of a phoenix, it wouldn't be bad being the head of a chicken. At least he could enjoy the feeling of being a core member for once.

　

In the end, He Ming agreed and joined Team Miracle for 2,000,000 RMB. Team Miracle was delighted, mysteriously telling him that there would be a surprise for him.

　

He Ming paused. Surprise? What surprise?

Could it be that Team Miracle was planning on poaching an All-Star level account like Windy Rain for him to use?

Soon enough, the surprise Miracle had planned came.

Excellent Era players Shen Jian and Wang Ze transferred to Team Miracle for a total of 1.725 million.

He Ming wanted to cry. This was the so-called surprise? When the manager of Team Miracle asked him cheerfully, "How does it feel to be reunited with your old pals", he really wanted to kick the guy's face in.

1.725 million. Just the price made He Ming feel embarrassed for Team Miracle. Just the twenty thousand tagging on was enough of a joke, but you even added another five thousand to that! How much did you negotiate to bullshit a five thousand at the end of a transfer worth over a million? He really had been overthinking it wondering if the team had bought Windy Rain! Never mind Windy Rain, it would be good enough if they could even get back their original characters.

But they didn't.

Shen Jian and Wang Ze had already arrived at Miracle and He Ming hadn't caught wind of any news of Miracle purchasing characters.

The three old Excellent Era teammates looked at each other when they met in the practice room that reminded them of a mountain village primary school, speechless and feeling like they wanted to cry.

Chapter 1083: Excellent Era Hasn’t Fallen

The series of transfers at the beginning of July were practically all related to Excellent Era. Now, everyone was thoroughly convinced that the rumors of Excellent Era being put on the market weren't baseless. Even One Autumn Leaf had been renounced, shredding the last sliver of hope for the Excellent Era fans. No matter how much they protested, it would not be able to change Excellent Era's decision.

Who can save Excellent Era?

Questions like this appeared in every corner of the Glory scene. Countless Excellent Era fans were signing a petition, but where were there hopes supposed to be sent to? Every Excellent Era was at a loss. They could only wait there foolishly.

Then, all they saw were players leaving and characters being sold.

Su Mucheng, Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, Zhang Xinjie…....

Dancing Rain, One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher...

After that, Club Excellent Era's training center constantly had people conducting on-site inspections. For Excellent Era, this was their training center, but buildings didn't have life. With just a bit of renovation, this place could become an office, a shopping center, anything people needed.

This portion of the sale seemed to be unrelated to Glory. The team emblem on the club's main entrance had been removed.

Everything related to Glory was being erased. The only thing that had yet to change was Excellent Era's stadium. There were rather limited applications for this type of building. There wasn't much of a market for it, but with Excellent Era gone, the existence of this stadium was meaningless. Perhaps this stadium might turn into a place for sporting events, but the people would no longer be seeing their familiar team and their team's matches.

What would Excellent Era's future be like? A better question might be: did Excellent Era still have a future? No one knew the answer, but what they did know was that things related to Excellent Era were disappearing bit by bit. Their players and characters were being transferred to other teams. Excellent Era's facilities were being renovated. In the game, Guild Excellent Dynasty members discovered that the resources in their guild storage were decreasing day by day. These were all the various materials that Guild Excellent Dynasty had accumulated after many years of work. It was the symbol of Excellent Era's prosperity. And now, these materials were disappearing to who knew where.

The sale of these materials wouldn't be reported in too much detail. From these series of changes going on in Excellent Era, the media had determined that the end of Excellent Era was set in stone.

At this point, Excellent Era's former opponents, even Tyranny's fans, were finally unable to continue mocking them. They wanted to see Excellent Era being beaten by them again and again and hoped to see Excellent Era tumble over and over, but they had never wished for Excellent Era to completely die.

Without Excellent Era, there would be a lot less brilliance.

A sigh of sorrow from a Tyranny fan voiced out the thoughts and feelings of many. But so what? Regret, grievance, sorrow, these emotions wouldn't be able to solve any problems.

At Happy, their second floor renovation was completed and now being used.　

The entire second floor had been divided into five sections: the practice room, strategy meeting room, research and development, Guild Happy, and the lobby. It was small, but complete 1 . All of the core departments necessary in a pro team fit into this small second floor. Of course, if they expanded, they would also need departments such as human resources, financial affairs, external affairs, and so on. But for the current stage that Happy was at, Boss Chen alone would need to burden herself with these matters.

"What do you all think? Pretty nice, no?" Chen Guo excitedly led everyone around to take a look.

"It totally feels like a secret base! It's like Robotech! Come on, don't deny it!" Steamed Bun said.

Everyone laughed.

"Research and development." Guan Rongfei stood outside the R&D room and read the plate on the door. He grabbed the door handle and opened the door.

"Right, this is where you..."

Bang!

Chen Guo introduced the room, while getting ready to let everyone take a look at their R&D department, but Guan Rongfei had already slammed the door closed, cutting off Chen Guo.　

Chen Guo was stunned. Fortunately, she had been in touch with Guan Rongfei for awhile, so she had some understanding of him. After this guy got the data for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, that was the only thing on his mind. Ye Xiu once asked if he could help him compile a practice routine, but this guy was unwilling to do it. It took a lot of effort to get him to agree.

Once he started working, the materials that Happy had accumulated disappeared swiftly. Chen Guo wanted to die. Ye Xiu immediately reminded that guy: this isn't Excellent Era. You can't squander these materials. Please try to be conservative and put more time into solidifying your theories. Don't just immediately start experimenting as soon as a tiny sliver of an idea appears in your mind. After that, his consumption of materials stabilized, but the materials were still disappearing at a heartbreaking rate. This let her understand that to raise a capable research developer, money was secondary. Whether or not you could provide enough resources for that developer was the main issue.

The department under the most pressure was Wu Chen's guild department. These past few days had been sleepless nights. Taking advantage of the enormous amounts of attention towards Happy recently, he was pulling in players to join the guild like crazy, rapidly strengthening the guild. With more guild members, there were more small matters to deal with. Wu Chen didn't have a helper right now, so he had to do everything himself. Chen Guo saw him working and felt bad. A professional team's guild definitely shouldn't managed by a single person, so she talked with Wu Chen and started picking helpers from the guild. Chen Guo also allocated 2 million for Wu Chen to use. Those managing the guild wouldn't be doing it just for love. They needed a contractual obligation to do it too.

Seeing Guan Rongfei shut himself in the R&D room, Wu Chen felt like he couldn't be slow either. He stepped in front of the door marked "Guild Happy" and asked: "I'm here, right?"

"Yeah…" As soon as Chen Guo affirmed it, Wu Chen went inside. Chen Guo stood in the middle of the hallway, stunned. Everyone else was stunned too. But not long afterwards, those two came back.　　

"No Internet?"

"Yeah, people will be coming in the afternoon to hook up the wifi. Let's go along a different route." Chen Guo didn't know whether to laugh or cry. 　

Guang Rongfei and Wu Chen were helpless. They could only follow along with the team again.

"This area is our strategy room. Come come come. Let's all go in and take a look." Chen Guo led everyone into the strategy meeting room.

The meeting room had a rather large window. The room itself was bright and clear. Right when they walked in, they suddenly heard a crash.

"What happened?" Someone said in surprise. Following afterwards, everyone went to the window. The sound had come from outside.

When they got to the window, everyone was silent.

The noise had come from their neighbor across the street. Club Excellent Era's wall had been pushed over. This wasn't a riot. Excellent Era's facilities had clearly been sold already. It was probably the new owner renovating this piece of land.

"Excellent Era... really has disbanded..." Chen Guo felt moved. Her Internet cafe had prospered thanks to Excellent Era. As the Internet cafe across street from Club Excellent Era, Excellent Era fans would naturally have an amicable feeling towards it and happily gathered here to play Glory.

But after establishing Team Happy and challenging Excellent Era, the two had become enemies. Happy's business had been considerably impacted by that. In particular, many familiar faces stopped showing up at Happy. These people had almost been like friends to Chen Guo.

And now, Happy was still here, but Excellent Era was gone. Where did those familiar faces go?

When she finished thinking about all this, Excellent Era's wall had turned into a mess. Before anyone could say anything, an employee from the Internet cafe suddenly called out: "Where's the boss? Someone's looking for her."　　

"Who's looking for me?" Chen Guo said as she walked out.

"He says his surname is Xia. He's waiting downstairs." The employee said.

"Surname Xia?" Chen Guo was surprised. She didn't remember having any friends surnamed Xia.

"I'll go down." Chen Guo called out and then went downstairs with the employee. There were quite a few people standing outside Happy Internet Cafe, looking at the destroyed Excellent Era.

"He's over there." The employee pointed at a figure. Chen Guo went over and was once again stunned. Surname Xia. It was actually Xia Zhongtian.

"Xia... Hi, Mr. Xia." Chen Guo greeted.

Xia Zhongtian turned his head and looked at Chen Guo. He nodded his head: "Hi."

Chen Guo saw that there was a youth standing next to Xia Zhongtian….. Isn't he Excellent Era's Qiu Fei? Chen Guo had already realized something.

"Come in. Let's go up and talk." Chen Guo was certain that he wasn't here just to say hello. He definitely had something to say. After telling them to go up, she told the employee: "Tell Ye Xiu to come over to the lobby."

On the second floor, Ye Xiu was brought over by the employee. Right when he got to the lobby, he saw chen Guo sitting together with Xia Zhongtian and Qiu Fei. He was also surprised.

"Senior." This time, Qiu Fei greeted first.　　

"Hi!" Ye Xiu waved his hand and the four went into the lobby together.

"I'll be taking over Excellent Era." Xiao Zhongtian clearly wasn't someone who liked to mince his words. He immediately went straight to the point.

"Oh, that's great!" Ye Xiu smiled.

"Congratulations." Chen Guo also said. She pointed outside the window: "What are you planning to do there?"

"I'm only taking over Excellent Era. That stuff's not included." Xiao Zhongtian said.　　

"Ah?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"Taking over Excellent Era is a personal matter. With my personal financial resources, I don't have the money to purchase Excellent Era's facilities. I can only guarantee that the name Excellent Era won't disappear." Xia Zhongtian said.

"You've even got a player with a lot of potential!" Ye Xiu smiled at Qiu Fei.

"Qiu Fei almost went to Tiny Herb. Fortunately, I had already talked to Excellent Era and convinced him to stay." Xia Zhongtian said.

"Amazing." Ye Xiu said, "Both of you are amazing."

"Praising us won't do. We'll definitely take revenge on Happy!" Xia Zhongtian said.

"Hm?"

"But this time, I'll have to thank you for your suggestion last time, but Excellent Era won't be owing Happy." Xia Zhongtian said. He took out a document from his briefcase and handed it over.　　

"This is something I've helped you win over. It's a 1.4 million RMB sponsorship by Ch'ien Tea Green. The formalities have already been arranged. All you need to do is sign it." Xia Zhongtian said.

"Arranged?" Ye xiu skimmed through it, "What if we don't want it?"

Xiao Zhongtian's eyes jumped. Chen Guo hastily grabbed it from him: "He's just joking. We want it, we want it." She quickly signed it.

"The contract is only for one year. Next year, whether it's renewed or not will depend on you." Xia Zhongtian said.

"Us? Don't you mean you?" Ye Xiu smiled.

"Me? I'm no longer a part of Ch'ien Tea Green. I'm going to lead Excellent Era and beat your Happy!" Xia Zhongtian said.　　

"You'll be playing on stage?" Ye Xiu asked.

Xiao Zhongtian's eyes jumped again. Unfortunately, he couldn't personally take revenge on Happy. He had been destroyed ten times by Ye Xiu in just five minutes.　　

"Senior, next time, let's meet on stage." Seeing that they were going to be leaving, Qiu Fei called out to Ye Xiu.

"I'll see you onstage." Ye Xiu smiled.

"I'll be going." Xia Zhongtian was already at the door.

"You're going to be leaving already? As a newbie, don't you want to learn from Happy's newly renovated center?" Ye Xiu said.

Xiao Zhongtian glanced at the tiny second floor layout. After a long time, he squeezed out "Not bad" and then left.

Excellent Era hasn't fallen.

Chapter 1084: Change

Someone was finally taking over for Excellent Era.

The news came out on the day that Xia Zhongtian and Qiu Fei came to visit. The fans of Excellent Era, who had fallen into despair, were all suddenly brought back to life. Especially after they heard who had taken over, they were even more excited. Which City H person didn't know Ch'ien Green Tea's influence?

But soon enough, in the press conference Excellent Era held, they found out the truth.

The decision to buy Excellent Era was completely a personal decision made by Xia Zhongtian. It had nothing to do with Ch'ien Green Tea. In addition, Ch'ien Green Tea Didn't intend to sponsor Excellent Era because of their relationship with Xia Zhongtian. The ones that they were sponsoring was Team Happy, who had defeated Excellent Era and joined the Alliance.

What was going on? The excited Excellent Era fans didn't have the calm to try and figure it out. It wasn't as wonderful as they first thought, but Excellent Era still existed and there was nothing that was more of a delight than that. It was just a shame that One Autumn Leaf left them. They hoped that the symbol of Excellent Era would stay with them and fight beside them forever.

But it was all too late for that.

Qiu Fei, Combat Form.

For the press conference, this was the way that the fans saw Excellent Era's future. The Excellent Era of the new season would continue to compete in the Challenger League. This time, they were no longer a powerhouse, no longer an insurmountable presence in the Challenger League. They would fight with their all against every team and keep winning until they eventually reached the end and returned to the alliance to rebuild the glory of Excellent Era.

Long live Excellent Era!

Tonight was the first time in a long time that Excellent Era fans had tasted happiness. Their hopes were not in vain. No matter how small hope was still hope.

Goodbye, powerhouse. New Excellent Era has begun its journey!

The news used headlines like this to report Excellent Era's final transactions. By now, it seemed that all of what made up Excellent Era had been sold.

　

The old Club Excellent Era had been completely reconstructed and New Excellent Era had moved to the place 20 kilometres away next to Stone Road. Everything had become very simple and crude, but everything was still there

As for Happy, they had all settled into their new headquarters. Everyone had started doing what was done on holidays in their own rooms.

"Brother Ye, someone is looking for you." That was when one of the employees of the Internet cafe came up to deliver this message. Since the upper floor was Happy's headquarters now, they naturally wouldn't let just anybody come up.

"Coming," Ye Xiu replied, leaving his computer. After exiting the training room, he took the chance to light a cigarette and took a few quick puffs.

Smoking wasn't allowed in the training room. That was a rule that Chen Guo had took from the other clubs. This made Ye Xiu and Wei Chen extremely uncomfortable. However, the veterans of the team should be role models for the others, so the two had to endure it. What made things even more painful was that there was no point in them being role models because they were the only ones who smoked in the team.

"Who's looking for me?" Ye Xiu took a few steps towards the Internet cafe employee, and by then half his cigarette was already gone.

"He said his surname was Tao." The Internet cafe employee said.

"Surname Tao?" Ye Xiu paused for a moment, looking down. It was Tao Xuan.

"Want to come up and chat?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That's not necessary, I'm about to leave," Tao Xuan replied.

Ye Xiu noticed the luggage beside him. It seemed like he was going somewhere far away.

"You…?"

"After being exhausted for so long, I plan to go and enjoy myself," Tao Xuan said.

"Where?"

"Somewhere out of the country! All these years and I spent most of it locked up indoors. I want to go out of the country and experience what life has to offer," Tao Xuan said.

"Oh? Are you going to check out foreign Glory leagues and their Glory teams?" Ye Xiu asked.

　

Tao Xuan paused for a long while before nodding. "Maybe!"

"I wish you success," Ye Xiu said.

"And I you."

"Goodbye."

　

"Goodbye."

Cigarette burn out.

In the time it took to smoke half a cigarette, Tao Xuan had left. He had come all this way to visit, but left with just a few simple words.

Were they still friends? Ye Xiu didn't know either.

He knew that everyone had their own path. These paths might converge, but they might also diverge. No matter what, you had to walk your own path. He would continue to walk down his. Tao Xuan would too, probably.

Ye Xiu threw the cigarette nub away, returning to the upper floor. He entered the training room and returned to his own seat.

　

"Who was it?" Su Mucheng's current seat was beside his and she asked him nonchalantly.

　

"Tao Xuan," Ye Xiu said.

"Tao Xuan, what did he come here for?"

"He said he's going to visit some other countries," Ye Xiu replied.

"Is it necessary? To hide so far?" Su Mucheng said.

"Is he hiding? Maybe!" Ye Xiu smiled, putting his headphones back on and going back to the game.

"Where did you all go?" Ye Xiu send the message into the guild chat, Guild Happy.

They were still playing in the online game.

Even though they had entered the Alliance and become a pro team, for a grassroots team like Happy, their pro players couldn't leave the grunt work to others. They had to fight in the online game to deal with their lack of resources. All this was like how the Alliance was when it first started. The players of every team spent all of their free time in the game. They trained as they earned materials and equipment. Back then it was common to see all those famous IDs in the game.

　

But now, even if a player wanted to do this, it wouldn't be the same. If the current pro players wanted to play in the online game, they had to use a smurf account. As for their pro accounts, most of them were parked in the Arena.

For Happy, We had to continue working hard in the game. In fact, they had to work even harder because their future opponents would all be at the level of the final boss, Excellent Era, in their last season. They couldn't ensure that their skill would peak each match and they would achieve a miracle every single time. They had to improve, improve continuously. This was like a race. From the very beginning, they were never on the same starting line as their opponents.

Happy was working hard in the online game, but this time, it wasn't just them who was working so hard.

"We prepared for this match for a full year."

That was what Ye Xiu had answered in the first press conference he attended after he won the championship of the Challenger League. The memory was fresh in Xiao Shiqin's mind.

Happy's defeat of Excellent Era was known as a miracle.

However, miracles couldn't lack hard work. Happy had worked hard and accomplished a miracle.

What had Excellent Era been doing in this year?

Excellent Era was also working hard, but all of the hard work was directed towards the Alliance. The only thing that they discussed was what they would do after returning to the Alliance.

They had neglected the Challenger League because they thought that this was something that couldn't go wrong. Even Xiao Shiqin had thought the same way. If he didn't think that way, then he would have never joined Excellent Era.

It wasn't until Ye Xiu and Happy slowly surfaced, that Xiao Shiqin found that even though Excellent Era said that they didn't think Happy was any sort of threat, in their hearts, they were actually terrified of Ye Xiu. It was then that Excellent Era started taking the Challenger League seriously, but this seriousness was only directed at Ye Xiu.

To win the finals, Excellent Era had also worked hard. However, compared to the full year that Happy had spent, Excellent Era hadn't done nearly as much.

Opportunity always smiles on those who are prepared.

This was something that was always said, something that everyone said, but when everyone was prepared, who would opportunity smile upon? It was obviously those who were more prepared. Happy had been more prepared, so they were the ones that were given an opportunity, an opportunity that was called a miracle.

Most people would think that Xiao Shiqin had wasted a year, but Xiao Shiqin thought that he had been taught an important lesson in this year.

Now, he had returned to Thunderclap. He would never again be the person who wasn't prepared enough. He had to be more prepared than anyone. From the very first day, he began to prepare with the entire team.

It had been a year since the big update, but things had yet to stabilize. As the competitions came to a close, the players of the pro teams wouldn't invest so much into the online game. Now the start of the summer holidays, Xiao Shiqin felt that this was the perfect time to fortify his team. To defeat Excellent Era, a team like Happy could prepare for a year. If they, Thunderclap, wanted to do well in the Alliance, then they would have to start early.

Dumb birds fly first. Why had he never thought of that before?

"Captain Xiao, Team Three's four members have arrived at their positions." The voice coming from the game brought Xiao Shiqin back to the present.

"Oh, tell them to make sure to keep hidden. Chengtai, take a team to the right flank; Yanqi, you go with Chengtai."

"Hey, you've only come back for a few days, captain, and you're already chasing me away. I want to stay with captain." Dai Yanqi sulked.

"Don't joke around, hurry up and follow." Xiao Shiqin started to sweat. He hadn't seen her for a year and she had got an even bolder, daring to tease even him. She was Thunderclap's Devil. Who knew what Thunderclap would be like if she ever became the captain?

　

However, Dai Yanqi was merely joking around. Her Elementalist had already begun following Chengtai's team as she spoke.

"Captain Xiao, Captain Xiao!" That was when a character ran over, yelling for him.

"What's wrong?"

"Another guild has arrived." The newcomer said.

"Which one?"

"It's Happy!"

Happy… Just hearing this name would cause Xiao Shiqin's emotions to go haywire, but he soon composed himself. "How many people and how far are they?"

　

"About one team, they'll be here in about 5 minutes," the newcomer said.

That guy would definitely be in Happy's formation. Compared to the Challenger League last season, the Pro League would be even harder. They would definitely start preparing earlier and spend a lot of time in the online game. This was something that he had taken out of their book.

He hadn't thought that they would have the chance to fight again so soon.

"Everyone over here, come with me. Avoid Happy for now." As Xiao Shiqin spoke, he led the team away from their original hiding spot.

"Traps! Don't leave traps, go and dismantle them!" Xiao Shiqin acted as if he were leading a pro match, serious and careful.

Thunderclap's players all felt that after their captain had left for a year and come back, he had changed.

In the past, his arrangements and tactics had given the feeling of doing all you could under heaven's mandate. Now, it felt like he wanted to rebel against fate.

Thunderclap would definitely change because of this!

Chapter 1085: The Rookie That Doesn’t Listen

Under Xiao Shiqin’s careful commands, Thunderclap’s players didn’t leave a trace. Xiao Shiqin and two of his teammates, Fang Xuecai and Zhang Qi, were left behind.

Fang Xuecai was an Assassin. He had joined Thunderclap a year after Xiao Shiqin and was a good friend of his, who had played alongside Xiao Shiqin for many years. Zhang Qi was a rookie that had become a pro player only last year. Xiao Shiqin had already left by the time he joined. This rookie hadn’t been very accepting of Xiao Shiqin’s choice to leave, but all he felt from the other team members was their heartfelt respect for Xiao Shiqin. Once, he inadvertently said something a bit disrespectful and had been admonished by Dai Yanqi, who had acted as if she were his senior, despite only joining the team one year earlier than him. The expression of the other team members were very unfriendly as well.

Zhang Qi felt gloomy. He was just a rookie though. How could he complain? He could only silently endure it. When he heard the news of Team Excellent Era losing, Zhang Qi rejoiced at his misfortune. But then, Xiao Shiqin unexpectedly returned to Team Thunderclap. This made Zhang Qi somewhat spiteful of him. The other team members cheerfully accepted Xiao Shiqin’s return though, making Zhang Qi feel even more disappointed in his team.

No backbone.

The players and the team didn’t have any backbone.

This was the feeling in Zhang Qi’s heart, but he didn’t dare criticize anyone. When he saw how Xiao Shiqin’s return was treated so well, his heart only became more unbalanced.

Soon afterwards, Xiao Shiqin immediately assumed the position of captain. Then, he called for everyone to go into the game and fight bosses for materials.

Is this something a pro player should be doing?

Zhang Qi looked around. No one in the team seemed to object. He didn’t dare break away from the entire team, so he could only go into the game with the team. Now, he was following behind this no-backbone Xiao Shiqin. They were hiding in a bush for who knew what reason.

“They’re here!” Fang Xuecai suddenly whispered.

“Got it.” Xiao Shiqin replied.

Zhang Qi shifted his camera and saw a bunch of Guild Happy characters majestically enter the woodlands on this hillside.

Zhang Qi turned his head and looked at Xiao Shiqin, who wasn’t sitting far away from him. Not only did he look vigilant, he even seemed nervous.

Really? We’re just playing in the game. Zhang Qi thought rather disdainfully.

“Zhang Qi, when you turn your camera, be gentler.” At this moment, Xiao Shiqin’s voice suddenly came in from his headphones.

“Ah?” Zhang Qi stared blankly.

“They’ll notice the rustling of the bush.” Xiao Shiqin said.

“Oh.” Zhang Qi replied. As for his real thoughts: hmph, coward.

Zhang Qi didn’t treat Xiao Shiqin’s warning seriously. He didn’t think that this caution was necessary. After Happy’s people arrived, they rapidly dispersed.

“Take note of each team’s whereabouts.” Xiao Shiqin assigned this role to three players. Zhang Qi checked the direction that he was responsible for.

“Gently, gently!” Xiao Shiqin reminded again.

Annoying!!

Zhang Qi nearly blurted it out, but he was able to stop himself. But under this urge, not only did he not turn gently, he turned even more roughly. Since he had already finished turning, it was too late for Xiao Shiqin to say anything more. Xiao Shiqin furrowed his brow, but didn’t say anything in the end.

Zhang Qi was bored to death as he watched that direction attentively. Guild Happy had two teams coming this way. After coming to a certain distance from them, the two teams split up. One team continued straight at them, while the other team moved diagonally to the left.

What’s there to look at?

Zhang Qi was distracted. Suddenly, he heard Xiao Shiqin shout: “Not good! Run!”

Then, he saw Xiao Shiqin and Fang Xuecai run out from the bushes at the same time. Their movements were extremely fast.

Zhang Qi hadn’t been very focused. He didn’t respect Xiao Shiqin’s orders either. Whenever an order came out, he would always complain in his mind first before doing anything. That was practically a habit now. Now that an order required his immediate action, how could he not be slower than the others?

A Satellite Beam descended from the skies, directly hitting this bush. Xiao Shiqin and Fang Xuecai had promptly escaped to dodge it, but Zhang Qi was hit because of that slight hesitation.

“F*ck!” Zhang Qi cursed as his character started wobbling away. But then the Satellite Beam split into eight smaller pillars. He had taken the Satellite Beam straight to the face and now he was about to be hit twice.

Where’s the attack coming from?

Zhang Qi was too busy to figure out the answer to that question. Escaping was more urgent. He saw a gap between two pillars and rushed towards it.

“Slow down!” Xiao Shiqin shouted.

Only you would slow down!

At a critical moment, Zhang Qi complained even faster. He completely ignored Xiao Shiqin’s warning to slow down. His character continued to sprint. Suddenly, he saw that gap flash and one of the pillars split into two, filling up the gap. His character just happened to be caught by it.

Zhang Qi turned pale with fright, but his character was already in a stunned state from this attack. Light pillar after light pillar smashed into his character. Eight? No, there were clearly twelve of them. The Satellite Beam pillars that initially hit him weren’t two, but three! Two of them had been overlapping, making it difficult for Zhang Qi to distinguish between the two.

But Xiao Shiqin had warned him to slow down. Could he have seen through it?

Zhang Qi felt somewhat ashamed. Let alone anything else, just being hit by every single light pillar from Satellite Beam was shameful enough.

Right when that pillar of light finished sweeping the area, he saw a Battle Mage with a Guild Happy tag charge towards him.

Do these guys think I’m that easy to bully?

I’m not an ordinary player!

Zhang Qi angrily welcomed his opponent, swinging his sword with a Destruction Slash. He was planning on giving this Battle Mage, who didn’t know how high the heavens were, a lesson. But when his sword flashed, that Battle Mage didn’t slow down and nimbly dodged it. The Battle Mage’s spear thrust towards him at the same time. Zhang Qi’s Destruction Slash wasn’t completed yet. However, that Battle Mage’s Dragon Tooth had already arrived.

Zhang Qi was once again alarmed. It was too late to cancel his skill. Dragon Tooth hit, and he was put into a stunned state. The other side used a Sky Strike to knock him into the air and then went behind him, sending him flying away with a Falling Flower Palm.

Bang!

Zhang Qi’s Berserker tumbled in the air. At the very last moment before he was sent flying away from his original location, he saw Xiao Shiqin and Fang Xuecai rush over to try save him. That Battle Mage welcomed them fearlessly.

Zhang Qi’s Berserker fell to the ground. He didn’t forget to Quick Recover at least as his character got up. However, he soon discovered that he was trapped. A whole bunch of characters surrounded him.

“I…”

Zhang Qi was only able to utter a single word when the enemy weapons fell, unleashing all sorts of skills. The wave of focused attacks instantly killed him.

I’m a pro player!

Zhang Qi had wanted to yell that out, but he was instantly killed before he could say anything.

What just happened?

Zhang Qi had trouble regaining his composure. Everything had happened too quickly. A few seconds ago, he had been waiting in a bush, throwing insults at Xiao Shiqin in his head. A few seconds later, he was a corpse lying on the streets.

Are you joking? He had never died so quickly even on the pro stage!

Zhang Qi was stunned.

The ghost world was deathly silent. Everything on the battlefield had nothing to do with him. But Zhang Qi could hear sound — Xiao Shiqin’s voice.

He was giving orders.

He and Fang Xuecai were crossing swords with the other side.

Zhang Qi turned his head to look over. Xiao Shiqin looked focused and also nervous.

What’s there to be nervous about? Those were his thoughts a few seconds ago. Now, the not-nervous him was already dead.

Zhang Qi prepared to revive. Suddenly, a notification flashed: Cleric Haruir has cast Resurrection on you. Do you want to revive or not?

Zhang Qi immediately clicked yes. His character stood up and then pounced forward.

“What are you doing!!” Zhang Jiaxing’s voice came from the practice room.

Zhang Qi was at a complete loss. He discovered that all of his teammates were looking at him as if he were an idiot.

“Wait until the right opportunity to revive…” Zhang Jiaxing mumbled to himself. He was a newcomer, after all. For Thunderclap, he was even newer than Zhang Qi. If this were Excellent Era, he wouldn’t let this matter go with just a word or two. A healer’s status in the team was quite high.

Zhang Qi finally woke up. He actually chose to revive while trapped in the enemy ranks. This decision was extremely stupid. Trying to deny it would be stupid.

“Sorry, my bad.” Zhang Qi said.

“Zhang Qi, pay attention to orders.” Fang Xuecai followed up.

“Okay…..” Zhang Qi replied dumbly.

If he had had listened to orders, would things have turned out differently? Zhang Qi couldn’t help but glance at Xiao Shiqin. He was the same as ever, focused but also nervous.

“Team one, don’t advance. Retreat five coordinates.”

“Team four, take the place of team three.”

“Team five, hold on. Support will be arriving soon. Team six’s healers, support team five.”

Thunderclap’s support hurried over, clashing with Happy. Xiao Shiqin didn’t plan on deciding the winner here though. He noted their goal: to kill the boss, not to win versus any other guild. Fighting Happy was out of helplessness. However, he soon realized that Happy’s offensive wasn’t that fierce. It seemed like they were also clear-headed. They also knew that this battle was pointless.

The leaders of the two sides had a mutual understanding. With neither side suffering too heavy casualties, the troops on both sides started to retreat. Not long afterwards, the battle stopped.

Amidst Happy’s troops, a Battle Mage walked out with a spear on his shoulders: “You’re working hard!”

Xiao Shiqin saw that it was the Battle Mage that sent Zhang Qi’s Berserker flying.

“So it was you.” Xiao Shiqin said.

“Who’d you think it was?” Ye Xiu said.

“Who else could it have been?” Xiao Shiqin said. Apart from Ye Xiu, there was only Tang Rou.

“If it were her, she wouldn’t have been so low-profile.” Ye Xiu smiled.

Xiao Shiqin suddenly thought of Tang Rou’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks. For her Battle Mage, the image of that skill gave the deepest impression. Where was she hiding now though? The previous battle hadn’t been too intense. Xiao Shiqin hadn’t found Happy’s other players yet. As a result, he could only instruct his troops: “When we fight again in a bit, pay attention to that Battle Mage. Kill him in one wave!”

At the same time, in Happy’s troops: “When we fight again in a bit, pay attention to that Mechanic. Kill him in one wave!”

“The boss is here!” At this time, the two sides received the news.

“FIGHT!!” The two leaders gave the order.

Thunderclap immediately focused on that Battle Mage!

Happy immediately focused on that Mechanic!

Chapter 1086: Focus Fire

Dragon Swordsman, the level 75 wild boss of Dragon Highlands, was their target today.

By now the eight level 75 wild bosses had been completely figured out by the players. Out of the eight, there were six that were each experts of single class type. The other two were amalgamations of three different class types. Figuring out the class of a boss wasn't just to make the battle easier, but also to understand the rewards that the boss could drop. The drops from the boss would naturally coincide more with the class of the boss.

Dragon Swordsman was one of the six class type experts. His class type was obviously the Swordsman class, if his name was anything to go by.

There would be events that signalled Dragon Swordsman's respawn, and the guilds that noticed these events would naturally prepare to welcome the boss beforehand. That was what Thunderclap had planned, and also what Happy had planned. It was just unfortunate that they bumped into each other. They exchanged blows, but tried their best to preserve their strength. It hadn't been a minute since the Dragon Swordsman had spawned.

"Attack!"

The two teams simultaneously received the order, but no one charged towards Dragon Swordsman.

All of Thunderclap's players focused on Ye Xiu's Battle Mage without any hesitation. All of Happy's players focused on Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic without hesitation.

Having hundreds of people focus on one target was just in theory. In reality, the DPS methods of healers were limited, the melee classes needed to switch places as they attacked, which had a method to it because they couldn't all attack the same target all at once, and ranged attacks needed space: Gunners needed a path for their bullets while Mages needed a good angle to cast spells from.

The two teams had only just received the order to focus fire and hadn't had the time to arrange a formation for attacking and positioning. This wave of attacks was rather hapdash.

Perhaps it was enough against normal players, but Ye Xiu and Xiao Shiqin were both at the top of the Glory scene, and the top of the top at that.

Battle Mage, Mechanic, the two figures weaved in and out of the attacks, parrying the strikes from melee classes, and dodging the blasts from ranged classes. When they did receive damage, it was only the smallest loss possible at the time.

Both sides were stunned.

The offensive launched by the other side made them feel like they were looking in a mirror. They all turned their views and saw two characters running around desperately.

"One Wave Rush!" Even their yells were exactly the same. The two sides had come across each other, but the battle between them hadn't erupted yet. Both sides were focused on accomplishing their orders and had sort of switched places. After all, Happy's players were in a position where it was easier to hit Ye Xiu's Battle Mage while Thunderclap was in a position closer to Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic.

In that moment, people from the two guilds had mixed together and it was hard to tell who was friend and who was foe. From the overall situation, it looked more like Ye Xiu and Xiao Shiqin were on the same side.

How merciless!

A focused attack like this wasn't easy to deal with, even for a God like Ye Xiu. While parrying, his Battle Mage managed to throw in a few Neutral Chasers and rely on these Chasers to increase movement speed. Ye Xiu's Battle Mage sprinted across the field, quickly looking around, spotting a massive tree root lying across the ground. He charge wildly towards it and jumped over the root, immediately crouching and finding cover against the ranged firepower.

In almost the exact same moment, he saw a Mechanic using accelerator, practically rolling on the ground as he swerved over from the other side of the tree root.

The two characters looked at each other.

"Hahaha…."

The two couldn't help but laugh.

"I'll draw their attention, you all go and steal the boss!"

The team chat of the two guilds once again flashed with the same message at the same time.

Then, Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic flicked his hand and threw a Grenade, while sneakily setting up a Mechanical Seeker. Ye Xiu was even more vicious. His Battle Mage directly activated Dragon Breaks the Ranks and charged at Xiao Shiqin. Grenade? Mechanical Seeker? These skills couldn't stop the momentum of Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Xiao Shiqin quickly jumped back thrice, barely dodging the attack, but Ye Xiu had already completed his attack. Low-leveled skills like Dragon Tooth and Sky Strike flew out. Mechanics did have some close combat ability, but it was nothing compared to Battle Mages.

Ye Xiu naturally didn't want to drag this out either. He hadn't forgotten that Thunderclap's army had their eyes set on him. When Xiao Shiqin swerved around the tree roots from the other side, he had already been prepared to keep fleeing. But, then he saw that the army that had been hunting him down had switched targets.

Ye Xiu was stunned. At the same time, Xiao Shiqin also realised that Happy, who were hunting him down before, had gone elsewhere.

In that moment, next to the tree root, the leaders of both sides stood there alone.

Caw caw!

A crow landed on the tree roots, shuffling its feet for a moment before flying away after losing interest.

"Ha…" Xioa Shiqin said, "They all left…."

"Why aren't you leaving yet?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I want to leave." Xiao Shiqin said. This wasn't a courtesy. The current distance between them meant that Battle Mages had the advantage. Leaving gave Xiao Shiqin the advantage. Pulling away meant that the Mechanic could gain the upper hand.

"Then I'll escort you." Ye Xiu didn't say anymore, striking out.

This time Xiao Shiqin didn't fight for his life, especially the last knockback attack. He just stood there and took it.

With the Mechanic sent flying, Ye Xiu understood what Xiao Shiqin wanted, not bothering to pursue. Instead, he immediately ran towards his own team. Xiao Shiqin did the same. When his Mechanic quick recovered, he immediately got his feet and headed towards Guild Thunderclap.

"What's the situation?" Ye Xiu quickly returned to his team, asking for the current battle situation.

"It's very lively." Wu Chen said. In reality, he was the leader when it came to Happy in the online game. Of course, with Ye Xiu here to help, he would naturally give up command. Any club guild would do the same.

Ye Xiu looked around. As expected, it was very lively.

With Dragon Swordsman's spawn method having warnings, it gave the players plenty of time to prepare. Usually, by the time he spawned, several guilds would have already arrived. It wasn't like other bosses that would usually have been snuck away by one guild and the others who arrived later would chase after it.

Right now, the teams from Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, and Hundred Blossoms had arrived, and their scouts said that Void's people were on their way.

There were only eight level 75 wild bosses in total, and their class characteristics were exceptionally obvious. Each guild would naturally place importance on them in accordance to their own needs.

Dragon Swordsman was a part of the Swordsman class. There was no need to explain Team Blue Rain and their two Blade Masters. Team Tiny Herb had Liu Xiaobie's Blade Master, while Team Hundred Blossoms had Yu Feng's Berserker. As for the rapidly approaching Team Void, the Ghostblade Duo were clearly of the Swordsman class as well!

It wasn't very feasible that one team would have all 24 classes, but having all 6 class types was rather common. However, characters would have different levels of importance within their team. Of the four guilds, Blue Rain, Hundred Blossoms, and Void had Swordsmen as their core classes. As for Tiny Herb, their Swordsman was just a level of importance below that. Then there was Happy who had Qiao Yifan's Ghostblade and Ye Xiu's unspecialized. In comparison, Thunderclap seemed more like a bystander. The Blade Master in their team was Zhang Qi's character, and this rookie hadn't even become a core player yet!

The teams of the guilds had all gathered and Dragon Swordsman seemed like the huge bonfire on Bonfire Night. Currently, no one had gone up to him yet. They were all looking at one another and waiting for the right time to break the stalemate.

"Quick, you go up and light a fire first," Ye Xiu messaged Xiao Shiqin on QQ.

"You first," Xiao Shiqin replied.

"Hurry up! What are you waiting for?!" Ye Xiu and then went and messaged Huang Shaotian.

"Holy f*ck where are you!?" Huang Shaotian immediately replied back. He didn't use many words, but used a bunch of emojis instead, almost 30 of them.

"God Jiexi, hurry up. You guys look like a team of janitors. Hurry up and come out and sweep." Ye Xiu then went to bother Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi.

"There's plenty of time." Wang Jiexi was very calm. Tiny Herb did have quite a few Witches, and they were all holding brooms. Janitors? Wang Jiexi looked around. Come on...

"Comrade Li Xuan, don't blame me for not reminding you. Ghosts Boundaries have to be set early. If you throw down a bunch now, you'll definitely come out on top." Ye Xiu then sent a message to Void's Li Xuan.

"Are you trying to fool ghosts*?" Li Xuan replied.

"I'm not joking."

"But we're not even there yet…"

"Really? Then you don't need to come. It's already finished, seriously. Tiny Herb's janitors are already sweeping up the remains," Ye Xiu said.

"Hahahaha…." Li Xuan sent back.

There was also Hundred Blossoms. Ye Xiu glanced over his QQ friend list, but didn't immediately see anyone. He wasn't very close to Hundred Blossom's Yu Feng.

"Has anyone else not arrived yet!?" Ye Xiu yelled.

"Old Ye, where are you come out come out I hear your voice!" Blade Master stepped out of the crowd on Blue Rain's side, swinging around his sword and showing off.

"It's Huang Shaotian, quick, don't hesitate! Kill him!!" Ye Xiu yelled.

Boom boom boom!!

The guilds really didn't hesitate. They were all throwing attacks at Huang Shaotian's Blade Master, and most of them were ranged attacks. For a moment, it looked like Blue Rain was having a fireworks party.

"Ye Xiu, fuck you! I'm going to kill you!" Huang Shaotian ran around, desperately dodging the attacks. Blue Rain's entire team had to back away as well. All the attacks were focused on Huang Shaotian's Blade Master, but they weren't that accurate, especially not the AoE ones. Amongst these, Tiny Herb's members were the most outrageous. All the witches threw a bunch of Lava Flasks over, covering the ground with lava like a volcanic eruption.

"Shot with Sorrow is Ye Xiu, don't hesitate, focus your fire on that Battle Mage!" That was when yelling erupted from Thunderclap's formation, and it seemed like it wasn't just one person.

"Don't fall for it everyone, I have eight computers and I'm logged onto eight alts. If I die I'll just switch alts, so killing me is a waste of time. Don't fall for the enemy's lies*!" Ye Xiu yelled back.

"Enemy's lies, my ass! We're all enemies, anyways!" Huang Shaotian, having been focus fired, somehow hadn't died and had hidden into some corner, but refused to give up the chance to speak.

In Happy's training room, everyone was glancing at each other. What eight computers? Whenever you open your mouth, all you say is bullshit and you manage to shit it out so fluently too.

"Peace Breaker is Xiao Shiqin, don't hesitate everyone. Focus that Mechanic!" Happy yelled in revenge.

"Don't fall for it everyone, I have ten computers and I'm logged onto ten alts!" Xiao Shiqin yelled back.

"Hahahaha, Xiao Shiqin are you trying to fool Void's Ghostblade Duo*? Your Thunderclap doesn't have enough extra computers for you!" Ye Xiu laughed.

The pro players that had visited Thunderclap before thought for a moment. That was right, Thunderclap's training room didn't have so many free computers, so let's hurry and focus him!

In that moment, there were some attacking Ye Xiu, some attacking Xiao Shiqin, and some continuing to attack Huang Shaotian. Under this situation, pro players were a target.

Chapter 1087: Misdirect

The entire situation was in chaos. The guilds kept switching targets. The players felt as if there were numerous bosses out there. In reality, the real boss, the Dragon Swordsman, was still sitting peacefully in the center of the circle. Although it was chaotic, not a single attack actually hit the boss.

It was clear that there was clear thinking and decision-making behind this madness. They all knew what would truly tip the scales of battle. The couldn't touch the Dragon Swordsman yet. Whoever did would become a target for everyone. With everyone so happily attacking all at once, whoever stood out and became a target would end up as minced meat.

Thus, all the guilds hoped that someone else would make this mistake, but they found that all the other players were just as rational.

Ye Xiu's Battle Mage suddenly darted out from the crowd as if in a panic and came to a position where he stood out a lot.

Killing Gods was something everyone found enjoyable. It was just that after the first wave of attacks, everyone would be making sure to protect their own Gods while they attacked others. As a result, it became more and more difficult to find their target. However, at this moment, Ye Xiu's Battle Mage had exposed himself to the guilds!

Don't hesitate!

Everyone's attacks turned towards him. However, Ye Xiu's Battle Mage was faster than a rabbit, darting off in another direction with a whoosh.

"He's going after the boss!!!" Someone suddenly realized that Ye Xiu's Battle Mage was about to step into the Dragon Swordsman's aggro range.

"Did he get careless?" The pro players of each guild were delighted. Ye Xiu had panicked and made a mistake. With him pulling the boss into this battle, the others didn't even need to discuss with each other. They would definitely all cooperate to kick Happy out of the competition first.

He's in! He really charged in!

The Dragon Swordsman moved. When sensing someone approaching, he would attack immediately. It seemed like Ye Xiu had only just realized this, hastily swerving in a different direction.

He's too late.

As many thought this gleefully, the Dragon Swordsman had started attacking. Then, everyone saw him jump up high with an impressive Collapsing Mountain directed right at Guild Thunderclap.

　

"What the fuck!?" Guild Thunderclap panicked, but Xiao Shiqin had realized something was wrong ever since Ye Xiu swerved towards a different direction.

　

F*ck, this was a misdirection!

Xiao Shiqin felt like crying. Since they were all impatient to kill off Ye Xiu, some of Thunderclap's attacks had hit the Dragon Swordsman when Ye Xiu's Battle Mage had swerved. Even though Ye Xiu's Battle Mage had gotten into the boss's aggro range first, that aggro was nothing compared to the aggro pulled by directly attacking the boss.

As the Dragon Swordsman crashed his way into their formation, the other guilds immediately took the chance to add to their misfortune.

Explaining would do nothing, Xiao Shiqin knew this. Xiao Shiqin wouldn't believe that such an obvious misdirection could be missed by the experts presiding over each guild today. However, these guys would all go with the flow at a time like this. They'd pretend to not understand the reality of the situation and instead cooperate with the boss to send Thunderclap out of the competition as was convenient.

　

Xiao Shiqin felt dejected. Why did Ye Xiu misdirect the boss to Thunderclap and not the other guilds? Why didn't I think of misdirecting the boss before Ye Xiu did?

"Prepare to retreat…" Thunderclap wouldn't be able to endure the combined assault of the boss and the other guilds' harassment, so Xiao Shiqin resolutely gave the order to retreat.

　　

With this chaos, another guild immediately tried to cut in and take over the situation.

"Ghost Boundaries, set!!"

Void would never lack Ghostblades and under the command of the Number One Phantom Demon, Li Xuan, all the Ghostblades charged forth. It didn't matter if they were Sword Demons or Phantom Ghosts, all of them summoned their Ghost Boundaries.

In an instant, phantasmic power spread across the field. Void's Ghostblades must have undergone special training for this. Currently, the Ghost Boundaries covered the field and very few overlapped. A huge area had been locked down all at once.

　

Because of a team's core classes, the guilds would usually have a majority of players playing specific classes. The surplus of a single class was a pain in dungeons, but in PvP, they could also easily find ways to execute unique team attacks using their advantage in numbers of a certain class. For example, the current Void Walk had covered such a large area with Ghost Boundaries. None of the elites in the other guilds could achieve this; they didn't have so many Ghostblades!

　

Although they might not have Ghostblades, they had other classes!

That was when the Witches of Tiny Herb came forth, launching attacks as one. Lava Flasks were thrown everywhere and Magic Rays crisscrossed in a wide net.

"Blade Masters, charge!!!" Blue Brook wouldn't be left in the dust either. With a single command, their most abundant class, the Blade Masters, charged into the fray courageously as a single group, using Triple Slash to dart right in with extreme speed. Their Warlocks, only slightly fewer than their Blade Masters, directly opened up a circle of Death's Doors.

"Hmph, we've been expecting this." Blossom Valley's people entered the battle fearlessly as well. Not only were their Spitfires numerous, but they all liked to imitate their ex-captain, Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossom Style. They might not be as skilled, but the combined chaos of so many people sending out skills created some impressive lighting.

"How chaotic…" Ye Xiu commented from the sidelines. When he had charged up to misdirect the boss, he had given Happy an order. In that instant, not only did Happy abstain from attacking Thunderclap, they retreated even faster than Thunderclap. Thus, as the other four guilds went with the flow and clashed in an intense battle, Happy had pulled out and became spectators.

Ye Xiu looked over the raging battle before glancing at Happy's formation. A new guild like them didn't have such obvious class differences. Though Ye Xiu's unspecialized was a very tempting choice, it was extremely hard to train up an unspecialized in these times. No normal game expert could complete the Heavenly Domain Challenge at level 50. Now, the level limit had gone up by another five levels, so the Heavenly Domain Challenge had become even harder, but unspecialized characters would still have to complete it at level 50. The possibility of being able to train up an unspecialized had dropped again.

The other guilds noticed that Happy had quietly retread, waiting to benefit from the aftermath. They could only grit their teeth though. They couldn't do anything. They had already sent arrows flying, so there was no turning back. It wouldn't be feasible to even try and get everyone to turn their fire on Happy now. After all, they fighting were in groups of hundreds of people, it wasn't so easy to pull back and stop.

　

"Save your strength!" All four guilds had the same thought. With that, defense became the main focus of the battle and the pace of the battle slowed immensely. Seeing this, they realized that this wasn't too bad. If they slowly came to a stop, it wouldn't be impossible to turn their fire on Happy. Should they make a pact? Right now, the different guilds had clashed, they wanted to cooperate with each other, but they were also terrified that someone would only pretend to cooperate and take the chance to strike. This was quite the conflict. Guild wars were even more complicated than pro battles sometimes; at the very least, this sort of chaotic all-out brawl wouldn't happen in a pro match. In a pro match, it was clear who were enemies and who were allies, unlike guild wars where an ally might turn their back on you in the next moment.

These guilds were still debating their next arrangements when a flash of sword energy flew out, parting the crowd. The Dragon Swordsman then charged out of the encirclement.

Everyone was shocked. The Dragon Swordsman wasn't programmed to run away. Could it be… that someone stole the aggro?

Everyone turned to look and saw that, in the direction the Dragon Swordsman was heading, there was a Launcher, cannon shouldered, directing blast after blast at the Dragon Swordsman. It was only until the Dragon Swordsman was almost on top of them that they began to retreat. However, no player's movement speed was good enough to kite a boss, or else they'd be far too easy to kill. A few steps away from the Launcher, the Dragon Swordsman raised his sword and flung out a Spellblade's Ice Wave Sword towards the Launcher. The speed of the skill was enough to get any Spellblade player drooling.

But this Launcher reacted extremely fast. With a jump, twist and blast from the cannon, the character rapidly switched directions, dodging the Ice Wave Sword.

Launcher...

The Number One Launcher of the Alliance had already gone to Happy. Apart from a player at Su Mucheng's skill level, how many people could manage to accurately cause enough damage to steal a boss' aggro under such chaos?

But if you do this, aren't you just pulling even more aggro for Happy?

Thunderclap had only hit the Dragon Swordsman because of Ye Xiu's misdirection, but hadn't managed to pull much aggro. Just Void's Ghost Boundary net was enough to grab the aggro. Even so, at a time like this, no one was willing to take the boss' aggro. They had to control the situation first. They would only start trying to deal the most damage when the situation was stable.

　

The boss' aggro was like a ticking time bomb. No one wanted it. So after Void grabbed the aggro, they quickly misdirected it towards Tiny Herb, who had launched a fierce offensive. Tiny Herb was rather generous, shoving the aggro at Blue Rain. Blue Rain was even worse, dodging it entirely and misdirecting it at Hundred Blossoms. Seeing that this wasn't very good, Hundred Blossoms threw it back to Void.

Going back and forth like this, trying to cheat one another, was because no one wanted to establish a solid hold on the aggro then. That was why Su Mucheng managed to pull the boss away so easily.

　

However, her purposeful stealing of the aggro was very different from the misdirections that had occurred between everyone before. With the boss getting pulled away, it was enough for the guilds to come to a ceasefire and charge over with no need of further prompting.

　

The Dragon Swordsman still wanted to chase after Su Mucheng's Launcher, and naturally, Happy's members would come and help prevent the boss from doing this. The other guilds quickly arrived, ready to send their own attacks. But that was when they saw the positioning of Happy's members. The pro players present were stunned.

This positioning was like a super misdirection formation. If the guilds launched their attack, the Dragon Swordsman would probably immediately turn his attention back to them. Happy had used the fact that none of the guilds wanted the aggro to turn the Dragon Swordsman into a shield for them to use.

However, could this really work? The guilds also had experts here. If they couldn't even deal with this, then they wouldn't be called experts. Immediately, the guilds had their members stop before rapidly rearranging their formation. But that was when Happy's members scattered and the Dragon Swordsman began to charge over like an uncaged tiger.

"What the hell? No one attacked it, did they?" Everyone was shocked. Then, someone noticed what had happened and wanted to cry. When had Su Mucheng gotten behind them? Happy had been using the Dragon Swordsman as a shield and now they were using the other guilds as a shield.

There were many pro players here, but after being played so many times, they had to admit that Ye Xiu's knowledge and decision-making when commanding in these sorts of situations had gone far beyond them due to his full year of experience in the online game.

Chapter 1088: Disparity

A 5v5 confrontation is absolutely not the same thing as a 100v100 battle. Although pro players were admittedly very skilled, much better than the average player, they only had the background of a pro. On the other hand, Ye Xiu's year and a half of madness in the online game, frequently fighting and stealing bosses had greatly increased his skill level in this aspect, revealing a great disparity.

Pro players admittedly had a higher level of tactical understanding, but but on this kind of stage, they weren't necessarily better than the club guild leaders at maintaining balance and control. In situations like these, pro players relied more on their overwhelming ability in order to stop their opponents from seeing their plans to fruition, and using their skill to directly tear their enemies apart. Except now, hidden within the opponent's army was an individual of unparalleled skill in online battles: Ye Xiu. This gap was one that they had no way of closing at the moment.

Dragon SwordsmanKnight directly charged at Su Mucheng's Launcher, charging into a few groups of guild troops. As they charged their hands did not stay still, instead swinging their swords wildly left and right. It was as if these few guilds had drawn the aggro of an OTed boss. What made this more awkward was the fact that, although they had no way of controlling this situation, they also couldn't just sit around and do nothing. Su Mucheng's Launcher was still moving, leading the Dragon Swordsman through the opposing armies to dish out damage and kill.

Focus fire on Su Mucheng?

It wasn't as if they hadn't thought of this, but Launchers possessed the greatest range. It wouldn't be easy to focus fire on her location. Furthermore, with a controller as skilled as Su Mucheng, this wasn't really realistic ...

"Charge at Happy!!" At this moment, no one was sure who suddenly came forth with this idea, directly shouting this out from within the crowd. The people who heard it thought it sounded reasonable. They immediately ignored he Dragon Swordsman and charged towards the players of Guild Happy.

However, Happy's players had long prepared for this. As soon as they saw that several of the guilds were planning to join forces to attack them, they immediately turned and ran without another word. Moreover, they split up as they ran. Their entire army had dispersed at a moment's notice, throwing everything into disorder.

At a time like this, should they chase or not chase? Who should they chase? How far should they chase? All of the pro players once again felt very confused, not knowing what to do. It was the guild leaders of the various guilds who, incomparably experienced when it came to these battles, seeing that Happy appeared to want to lure them away, immediately frantically went to check on the location of the boss.

Because of the careful avoidance of these few guilds, the Dragon Swordsman charged outwards from amidst their troops, continuing to throw himself straight at Su Mucheng's Launcher.

As for Su Mucheng's Launcher? At this moment she had indeed run very far away. Sure enough, she was trying to bring the boss away ...

"Watch the boss! Pull it back!"

Every single one of the large guilds panicked. They hadn't come here to battle with Happy. What was the point of fighting for this long if the boss was going to be stolen away like this? This was the bad thing about wild bosses; they weren't like normal bosses, which were restricted to a certain area. Those bosses, if brought too far away, would automatically reset and return to their areas. But for wild bosses, the whole map could be seen as their permitted movement area. If you had the capability to continuously drag the boss around without being hacked to death, then you could take it to travel the entire world. 1 **

Once the various guilds noticed that Happy was trying to steal Dragon Swordsman, how could they just ignore it? Outputting damage to pull back the aggro wasn't something that could be done in just the blink of an eye. At a time like this, they obviously had to rely on Knights' aggro skills to forcefully control the boss. For a moment, Knights charged forward from every guild, all using Provoke against the Dragon Swordsman.

The effects of Provoke could override another instance of the same skill. All of these players fired off this skill at once, and for a moment, no one could tell whose skill had ultimately taken effect. In short, Dragon Swordsman charged back like a fiend. Every guild hastily adjusted their Knights' rhythm, methodologically trying to establish control. Seeing that her purpose had not been achieved, Su Mucheng once again fired back, bombing indiscriminately from afar. But if one was truly talking about generating aggro without taking damage output into account, then Knights were the one class that generated the most aggro. With the addition of specialized aggo control skills, their advantage in this respect was unparalleled among the classes.

Although a vast majority of the Knight players present could in no way compete with Su Mucheng, let's not forget that there were also pro players present! Currently, Xu Bin was the Number One Knight player in the Alliance, and so naturally he was also the one who stood out most among the Knights. Ultimately, it was him who pulled the aggro of Dragon Swordsman.

…

Thus, Dragon Swordsman target became Herb Garden. This wasn't a situation that Tiny Herb wanted to see. Fortunately, the aggro currently on Xu Bin was only because of a CC skill, so it wasn't stable.

Should they release it once again? Xu Bin was at a loss. They had pulled it back, but now they wanted both to release it and to not release it. This kind of back and forth, what did it mean? He couldn't seem to figure it out himself.

Kill Su Mucheng first?

Someone had thought of this, but when they took a look at the situation again, Su Mucheng fired a few shots and then started running as if she had given up. However, Xu Bin, who was keeping the boss's aggro under control, was very clear that the boss's aggro was still on Su Mucheng's Launcher. If he released the boss, the boss would immediately run in that direction. However, if he didn't and established the aggro, wouldn't Herb Garden become the target of everyone?

At this time Xu Bin felt embarrassed, not knowing how to proceed.

"Release!" In the end, it was still Wang Jiexi who made the decision. Not releasing would be unfortunate for their Herb Garden, but releasing the boss would at least bring misfortune to all of the other guilds too.

Xu Bin released the boss, and the Dragon Swordsman charged out. All the surrounding Knights all stood stupidly, not knowing how to proceed. For now, none of them wanted the aggro of the boss, yet they also couldn't just let Happy lead it away. They couldn't block, but they also couldn't not block. Then, what should they do?

"Follow the boss, and push Happy away!" Finally, someone came out with a suggestion. The Dragon Swordsman was currently chasing after Su Mucheng. There was no way her Launcher could single-handedly lead the boss along forever; the other side would definitely need to send people to block the Dragon Swordsman in order to buy her some time. Couldn't they then just chase after the boss, while also seizing the chance to roll over Happy?

As a result, they all swarmed, charging forward. On Happy's side, everyone also swarmed, helping Su Mucheng buy time. They actually managed to utilize the strength of the entire guild.

Both sides thoroughly collided at last. At this moment, Herb Garden, Blue Brook Guild, Blossom Valley, and Void Walk felt that they had a common enemy, surprisingly banding together to fight against Happy. Happy's players were put on defense, yet they were still unable to withstand the combined offensive of these four guilds. When it came to the strength of normal players, they were inferior to these professional guilds.

"Not good!"

As a result, these guilds bullied Happy with glee, only to suddenly discover that even as Happy's players risked everything in order to defend their position, the Dragon Swordsman had already been led even further away. Already, they had lost sight of Su Mucheng's Launcher. The Dragon Swordsman's silhouette also disappeared behind the mountainside in the blink of an eye.

Within the four guilds, normal players and pros alike broke into chaos. How could they continue to pay attention to the players from Happy in front of them? So this giant crowd was just a distraction after all. Now, Dragon Swordsman had completely escaped from their frame of view. What corner would he be dragged off to now, to be secretly killed?

Several hundred people hurried chased over, only to realize that the mountain was far too tall, and the earth far too vast. It was as if the Dragon Swordsman had never spawned at all. Where would they even begin to search? The various guilds scattered their troops, dispatching them to go search. As for the pro players, they all seemed a bit lost. They couldn't figure out how Happy had led the Dragon Swordsman away, just like that ...

This would need a thorough tactical analysis.

.

The pro players naturally pondered the problem from their customary point of view. Just like when they carefully reviewed their opponents strategies after a match, they felt that the situation that had just come to pass should also be analyzed thus.

The online game was extremely easy for pro players since they didn't have any opponents at their level. However, when an opponent at a high skill level appeared, then the game became quite a bit more complicated than even normal pro matches.

None of the players that had been sent out to search for the Dragon Swordsman had brought back any news, right up until the point where the system announced that the Dragon Swordsman had been slain by Guild Happy. As for where this had occurred, and who had participated, the club guilds surprisingly had no clue.

Everyone present was dejected, gloomily going through the motions of cleaning up in the aftermath. Those who could respawn did so, and any dropped equipment was picked up. In this process, it was difficult to avoid altercations with the other guilds. Still, no large scale confrontations occurred. These players all had habits acquired through years of works, and they normally wouldn't argue over such small issues. The aftermath of a boss being stolen felt like the aftermath of a professional match, continuing to fight seemed completely pointless. After all, they were all guilds that had grown so large. Killing each other wasn't going to destroy a guild. For example, after Samsara's championship victory last year, Blue Brook Guild and Guild Samsara had engaged in a brutal conflict, the fires of war spreading throughout the world of Glory from guild members to wild fans alike. The result? It could only be said that both sides had suffered. After all, this was an online game, a character that died could respawn in the blink of an eye. It was true that equipment could drop, but it could also be picked up, turning into a back and forth cycle of you drop I pick and vice versa. Ultimately, which side profited? Neither, because in the end both sides would suffer losses. Only some lucky passerbyers stood to gain.

Thus, these kinds of battles were something the guild managers tried to avoid at all costs. It was only after important competitions, when the fans felt the need to vent, that the guilds felt compelled to stand firmly beside them. Even though they knew very well that this was not the sensible thing to do, they didn't really have a choice. They could only think of it as a tax of sorts to the fans.

But now, they had simply lost a wild boss, and their feelings were unlikely to be that strong. The various players all felt a bit like they couldn't really compete against Ye Xiu, yet the guild leaders were all desensitized at this point. Bringing in the cream of the crop to compete against Ye Xiu, and still losing the wild boss to Happy? Wasn't this just another day in Glory?

Except ... their guild had now brought pro players into the game as well. How come Happy could still so easily carry out their plans? This question was one that the various players from the club guilds couldn't really find an answer to. In their eyes, pro players were in a completely different league. Whether they hadn't played the online game for a long time, or had only played a little, Ye Xiu's presence for the past year and a half was a very valid reason for their failures. But they had completely neglected this battle ... just when would they win?

Chapter 1089: Dragon Spine Marrow

"What dropped?"

An elite member from Happy's guild gave the last hit to kill the boss, Dragon Swordsman. At this moment, he was standing around the Dragon Swordsman's corpse, looking nervously and expectantly at the materials scattered all over the ground.

Guan Rongfei's addition to the team put Happy's equipment development in the right track. Although he wanted to focus more on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, after being in this line of work for so many years, he was still very clear on what his responsibilities were. All of Happy's Silver equipment would be developed by him alone.

Guan Rongfei had already come up with several ideas based on Happy's current materials. And Happy's vast amounts of Level 75 uncommon materials broadened his horizons. Happy couldn't compare with Excellent Era in terms of Level 70 and below materials. Happy couldn't compare with other club guilds in terms of Level 75 normal materials either. However, for Level 75 uncommon materials, Happy instantly stood out. In the Level 75 update, Happy had established their position in the Heavenly Domain wild bosses battlefield. Their allies, Heavenly Justice, Radiant, Parade, and Conquering Clouds, had considerably fatter guild storages as well. And once Wu Chen joined and the guild had gradually grown, the guild drew less and less from the other four guilds, focusing on enriching their own guild's storage.

For the other guilds, their materials were like a pyramid, the more high-end the material the fewer there was. But for Happy, it couldn't be said that it was completely the opposite, but at least relatively speaking, their guild storage outdid the other club guilds.

A professional like Guan Rongfei knew very clearly what this implied. This meant that although the overall number of Silver equipment possessed by Happy might not be able to catch up to the powerhouses in a short amount of time, Happy might not lose to any other guild in terms of Level 75 Silver equipment. Don't look at how the other guilds already had Level 75 Silver equipment, while Happy had none. That was only because Happy didn't have many Level 70 Silver equipment. Happy also didn't have a professional like Guan Rongfei working for them.

Wei Chen and Ye Xiu. Wei Chen's knowledge was mostly limited to his Warlock class. Most of it was through experience. He lacked the theoretical foundation, so it was difficult for him to deduce many things from one case. As for Ye Xiu, his knowledge base was broader than Wei Chen's, but his time was limited. Just a single Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was already making his head dizzy. He also needed to study strategies, watch over the growth of his players, and deal with in-game matters. He really couldn't handle everything. As a result, for their Level 75 Silver equipment, Ye Xiu just didn't bother spending any of his time and efforts into this area.

But with Guan Rongfei here, Ye Xiu was now completely free from this area. With a professional like him, the progress towards their equipment sped up considerably. After Guan Rongfei received the information on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, he really wanted to hurry up and upgrade this equipment. He had all sorts of other crazy ideas too.

For this Dragon Swordsman, Guan Rongfei had a clear request.

Dragon Spine Marrow!

This was the name of the material that Guan Rongfei requested. Happy originally had four pieces of this material, but Guan Rongfei had expressed that the amount was far from enough.

"Four isn't enough? How many do you need?" Ye Xiu asked.　

"The umbrella ribs." Guan Rongfei replied.

"Umbrella ribs….." Guan Rongfei's boldness surpassed Ye Xiu's imagination. The umbrella ribs were the frame that supported the umbrella. It required a rather high quantity of materials. This part had always been made using normal materials. However, Guan Rongfei was domineering. This guy actually wanted to use uncommon materials here. Was he planning on using only Level 75 uncommon materials for every part of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella?

"Isn't that too extravagant? Is there a need?" Ye Xiu was a bit doubtful. Uncommon materials were usually used for a few important parts of a Silver equipment. There had never been a case where a Silver equipment was completely made up of only uncommon material.

"It has to be." Guan Rongfei was certain, "The structure of this piece of equipment is extremely complex. It can't compare to other equipment. Along the way, you've probably already noticed that it needed more uncommon materials at higher levels. This is because if the quality of the material isn't raised, getting such a complex structure to improve to a higher level isn't possible."　　

"Are you sure this is the only reason? And not because our Level 75 uncommon material reserves are still good, so you wanted to create a beautiful piece of Silver equipment composed of entirely uncommon materials?" Ye Xiu asked questioningly.

"That's only the third reason." Guan Rongfei said.

Third reason... this guy really had this kind of thought. Ye Xiu really wanted to very politely give this guy a scolding, but Guan Rongfei followed: "There's the second reason: this way is relatively economical."

"Economical?" Ye Xiu felt like he had heard wrong.

"Yes, if you insist on using common materials, that's fine too, but this will undoubtedly require more research into the other options. The amount of materials needed for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella is already several times that of other equipment. The other options make things even more complicated. There are far more types of common material than uncommon material. If the choice of a common material turns out to be a mistake, then the amount of waste produced overall will be many times greater than other equipment." Guan Rongfei spoke frankly and confidently when he talked about equipment. It was a completely different attitude than when he talked about anything else.

Ye Xiu felt like this was very logical. In the end, it was because Level 75 materials had only been around for half a year, not like Level 70 materials that had been studied for three years now. In addition, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was exceptionally complex. An uprecedented upgrade like for this umbrella was much more difficult.　　

However…..

"Is it really necessary to use all uncommon materials?" Ye Xiu said.　　

"I think it's more dependable this way." Guan Rongfei said.

"Are there enough Level 75 materials to upgrade the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella?" Ye Xiu asked. There were currently eight Level 75 wild bosses. No matter how high their efficiency was, their production rate wouldn't be able to compare with Level 70 uncommon materials. There were around twenty Level 70 wild bosses.

"Don't look down on uncommon materials!" Guan Rongfei said solemnly.

"Then I'll listen to you….. What are your thoughts right now?" Ye Xiu asked.

As a result, Ye Xiu received a list of materials that Guan Rongfei needed. Because of their half a year of accumulation, they already met quite a few of the requirements. It was just this Dragon Spine Marrow…...

"12." When Guan Rongfei said he needed 12, it was as if this task was as easy as obtaining 12 lighters.　

"Shouldn't there only be 8 umbrella ribs?" Ye Xiu asked.

"But if it's Dragon Spine Marrow, then I need 12." Guan Rongfei's reply practically said nothing, but Ye Xiu understood that Guan Rongfei meant that this material would be different than past materials, whether that was in length or bulk, which required 12 instead of 8 to accomplish.

"Don't look down on uncommon materials?" Ye Xiu took Guan Rongfei's statement and asked it back to him.　　

"It's worth the money." Guan Rongfei said.

And now, the Dragon Swordsman had finally fallen. As for the Dragon Spine Marrow? Was there any? They were missing 8 pieces still. This boss only spawned once a week and it wasn't guaranteed that they would kill it every time. Even if they did, it wasn't a guaranteed drop…...

How long had it been since Ye Xiu had looked forward to boss drops? This time, he deeply felt it.

Materials were scattered all over the ground. Wu Chen sucked in a deep breath of air and then began picking up the drops. Right now, he was a permanent resident of the game. The others only logged onto alternates and joined when they were needed. More often than not, they were on their mains and practicing in the Arena. Several practice routines had been implemented into the dedicated program that Guan Rongfei had created. Compared to the past, they didn't need to go into the game and look for the correct environment anymore.

Item after item flashed in the team chat every time he picked up a drop.　　

Jade Cloud Sand, Burning Heaven Cloth, Mountain and Sea Ice…..

Drop after drop jumped up in eveyone's eyes. These were all valuable Level 75 uncommon materials, but at this moment, no one cared about them. Finally, everyone saw the three words that they were looking for.

"Dragon Spine Marrow!!" Chen Guo was the first to shout. They were still missing seven.

"Another one!" Chen Guo yelled again.　

A large number of materials usually dropped, so it wasn't rare for several of a single type of material to drop. Everyone wished that all eight Dragon Spine Marrow would drop all at once.

"Three!" Chen Guo called out again, but her shout wasn't as fast as Ye Xiu's click. The moment that she shouted, everyone saw that two Dragon Spine Marrows had popped up on screen. A total of four Dragon Spine Marrows had dropped.

Are there anymore?

Everyone was staring at the ground. There weren't many materials left.　

Wu Chen continued to click rapidly. The numerous materials scattered on the floor were quickly swept clean. Chen Guo's counting hadn't been able to keep up with his speed. After three shouts, she closed her mouth. Everyone was looking at the team chat. Another one and then another one.

"Could all eight actually drop?" Wei Chen was stunned.

Reality wasn't that crazy. In the end, six had dropped.

"D*mn, only six." Ye Xiu sighed.

Everyone was speechless. Due to how often they hunted wild bosses, they had a good understanding of the drop rate of wild bosses. It wasn't rare for two or three of the same materials to drop. Four or five was rather rare, but it seemed to be their first time getting six of the same drop at once. He shouldn't feel sad about that, and there definitely shouldn't have been an "only" attached to it.

Once their harvest ended, Ye Xiu and the others logged off. Wu Chen took the materials along with the other guild members back to the city and continued to do his work.

This summer definitely wouldn't be a relaxing one!

Ye Xiu opened up a file. It contained all of the material needs that Guan Rongfei had requested. Ye Xiu changed Dragon Spine Marrows from 8 to 2. Just this change alone wasn't able to block the dazzling list contained in this file.

Chapter 1090: A Summer Not to be Overlooked

Ye Xiu couldn't help but sigh at the list of materials sent by Guan Rongfei. If this list had been sent to any other club guild, it wouldn't have just been a sigh. A huge storm definitely would have erupted.

Failing to get a wild boss was a common occurrence for any club guild, but frequently losing to a single guild somewhat broke the balance. And this imbalance had lasted for a year and a half already. Happy might not be completely monopolizing all of the wild bosses, but their profits this past year and a half far surpassed any other powerhouse. This was an undeniable reality.

When the clubs did an inventory of their storages at the end of season nine, the guild departments all presented unsatisfactory reports. There were only so many wild bosses. One more wild boss won by that guild was one less wild boss for this guild. And now, Happy had taken so many wild bosses away. With just the remaining wild bosses, how could there be enough for any of them to reach their expected goals?　

The guild departments were embarrassed. Their bosses had unsightly expressions.

However, their bosses couldn't scold them too harshly. It was no secret how powerful Guild Happy was. Guild Happy had a God like Ye Xiu watching over. If their guild leader could beat Ye Xiu, then their guild leader would have been promoted to the team long ago to win the championships.

Their only consolation was that their losses weren't special cases. Their other competitors were also knitting their brows over this issue.

During this year and a half, they had tried all sorts of methods to solve this problem. When the Level 75 update came around, they even had their pro players rush into the game to increase their competitiveness without regard for their pro players' conditions.

The effectiveness of the pro players joining in was very clear, but it wasn't absolute. After the update, it was still Guild Happy that led the pack.

For example, their defeat at the battle for the Dragon Swordsman was not a unique case. It wasn't the first time that Happy had taken down the boss from the hands of other pro players.

It was just that in this battle, there were top tacticians like Yu Wenzhou, Xiao Shiqin, and Wang Jiexi participating. These tacticians had distinctly felt a reality: they couldn't keep up with Ye Xiu's tempo in these in-game battles.

Why is that?

These experts instantly figured it out.　　

Even though they also stood at the top of Glory, they had been separated from the game for a long time. They still held an extremely large advantage when clashing against normal players, but when facing an equally-skilled player like Ye Xiu, this difference only became more obvious.

Although a bit exaggerated, one analogy would be that they were like noobs being beaten by an expert with far more experience than them.

This was certainly an awkward situation. The guild players had in-game experience, but they weren't as skilled as Ye Xiu. The pro players had the skill, but they lacked the experience in large-scale wild boss battles.

This wasn't a minor issue. Happy's dominance was somewhat inevitable.

After the Dragon Swordsman battle, the participating guilds were all deeply reflecting on this issue.

Right now, it was summer break in the league. For the pro players, this break was an official holiday. The clubs didn't have the legal right to demand them to do anything. They also had no obligation to undertake these in-game tasks. Even more importantly, helping out in the game was to improve their team's strength. However, with the summer transfer window open, players might very well switch to another team. Consequently, players without too stable of a position would find it difficult to improve their team's hardware. They would rather improve their own individual skill and improve what could be regarded as their software.

Every player had their own thoughts, but no matter the case, every player was chasing after their dream for glory.　

For Team Thunderclap, their players didn't seem to have any apprehensions about getting transferred away. They didn't even go back home this summer and instead stayed to help out the team.

For Team Tiny Herb and Team Blue Rain, they had talented rookies with lots of room to grow. They didn't want to waste these two months of the summer, so they made training their rookies the name of the game. Both rookies were training intensely and receiving pointers from their respective teammates.

For Team Hundred Blossoms, after rebuilding the team and experiencing a series of trials, they had finally walked out from their lowest point. Even though they had lost in the playoffs to Tyranny, everyone could see the fighting spirit of the new Team Hundred Blossoms. They were filled with ambition towards the new season. The day after being elminated from the playoffs, they had already started preparing for the new season. When Team Tyranny lost to Team Samsara in the finals, Zhang Jiale, who had come out of retirement and joined Team Tyranny, inevitably received hate from a few Team Hundred Blossom fans, but it was less than what people had expected. This was because more fans were invested in the new Team Hundred Blossoms. The fans had walked away from the past, looking forward to the new Team Hundred Blossom's future.

Apart from that, there were other teams too.

For Team Tyranny, the old generals hadn't given up yet. Would season ten be their last chance? No one knew the answer to that. Team Tyranny themselves might not know either, but they would treat it like their last chance and do everything they could because they could already feel that time was mercilessly dragging them from this world little by little. They needed to treasure every minute, every second. They definitely wouldn't let two months of vacation wear away their fighting spirit.

For Team Samsara, while people were still in celebration over the defending champions, the team had snatched Excellent Era's Sun Xiang and Battle God One Autumn Leaf at lightning speed. Their determination for the new season could easily be seen from this. Three consecutive championship victories was the mark of a new dynasty. Team Samsara was walking the road to an even greater glory. This summer, they wouldn't be resting either.

For Team Wind Howl, astonishing everyone became a common occurrence, getting them to third place in the regular season. They had progressed into the semifinals, but were beaten cleanly by Samsara and eliminated from the playoffs. Losing to the eventual champions couldn't be considered shameful, but for these proud and ambitious youths, this season had been like a tiger's head but a snake's tail. A loss was a loss. Even if others sympathized and forgave them, they didn't feel good about it at all. They wanted wins from start to finish.

There was also Misty Rain, Void, 301, Royal Style, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade…..

With Glory's season ten, the Glory competitive scene will have been around for ten years. It would the first complete season with Level 75s. Every team seemed to have a reason for not losing. Every team appeared to be more proactive. Because of their burning fighting spirit, this summer would blaze even more intensely.

Another Level 75 wild boss battle.　　

This was the focal point of the club guilds. It directly affected upgrading their team's Silver equipment to Level 75. If Ye Xiu had a list of materials from Guan Rongfei, how could the other guilds not have their own list?

Barrier Mountains, Shadow Commander Shaan, a boss that mainly dropped Nightwalker class equipment and Nightwalker materials.

Team Blue Rain's Warlock, Swoksaar. Team Blue Rain's Ninja, Dark Forest. Team Wind Howl's Thief, Mysterious Ghost. Team 301's Asssassin, Scene Killer.

These four Nightwalker class All Stars were undoubtedly their team's core. The Shadow Commander Shaan were their biggest priorities. Apart from that, there was Samsara, Void, Thunderclap, and so on.... These teams all had Nightwalker classes as part of their main roster and wouldn't miss this opportunity. As for Happy, they had two Nightwalkers: Wei Chen's Warlock, Windward Formation, and Mo Fan's Ninja, Deception.　　

At a mountain stream in Barrier Mountains, Shadow Commander Shaan spawned. A mantle covered his body. He seemed to blend into the shadows as he walked along the cliff. When the guilds received the news, they quickly crammed into the mountain stream. But when they saw the terrain, their heads immediately started hurting.

To the left and right of the mountain stream were high cliffs. There was no way to arrange any proper formations. The mountain stream itself wasn't wide enough. There was only enough space for one group to fight with the boss, but right now, there were one, two, three, four…...

F*ck, there's more groups than can be counted! Everyone was grumbling to themselves. Their guild leaders all kept silent because they were only the leaders in name. With the pro players watching over them, they tactfully stepped down to give them the authority, especially when the pro player was the captain.

"Captain Yu, this isn't a good place to fight!" At Blue Brook Guild, guild leader Changing Springs was currently discussing the situation with captain Yu Wenzhou.

"Mm..." Yu Wenzhou replied. His left hand was tapping the edge of his keyboard. He was also pondering over their situation.

Huang Shaotian wasn't as quiet. He had dragged along Lu Hanwen, and the two Blade Masters had gone into hiding to who knew here. The only thing that Yu Wenzhou could hear was Huang Shaotian's voice rattling on from outside the game.

"This time, we have to stay calm. We can't reveal our identities so easily. Ye Xiu is a very despicable player. As soon as he finds out it's us, he'll definitely try to kill us as fast as possible. It's just like last time. You know." Huang Shaotian was currently lecturing Lu Hanwen.

"Senior, last time it was just you who revealed yourself, no? Who are you talking about when you say "we"?" Lu Hanwen asked.

"Excuses! If you don't concentrate, he'll easily see through you." Huang Shaotian scolded.

"But….. he doesn't seem to be here? I don't see Guild Happy." Lu Hanwen said.

"Hmph, impossible." Huang Shaotian snorted, "He was just asking me on QQ where I was. He's definitely here. He's just hiding, that's all."

"Oh, I get it." Lu Hanwen nodded his head, "Even if he wasn't originally going to be here, since you replied to him, telling him where you were, he'll definitely be on his way."

"What?" Huang Shaotian stared blankly. Something didn't seem right with this logic?

"Hanwen…... " Huang Shaotian spoke with heartfelt sincerity, "You know, my hands are incomparably fast. They move much faster than my mind. When I play, it's like that. Sometimes, by the time I realize what the problem is, it's like that too."

"I get it. No wonder our captain often stresses that you need to control your hand speed. Lu Hanwen said.　

"Hahaha, that's because he doesn't have this problem!" Huang Shaotian laughed out loud.

"The captain's looking at us." Lu Hanwen had noticed that Yu Wenzhou seemed to be interested in their conversation.

"Shut up! FOCUS! Do you know what focus means, Lu Hanwen!!!!" Huang Shaotian shouted loudly.

Chapter 1091: Before He Arrives

Because of the dangerous terrain, even though the guilds could jump into battle at any moment, for now they could only huddle together. Everyone looked around at each other, secretly preparing their skills and targets. Once their leaders gave the order, they could instantly and accurately launch their attacks.

Yu Wenzhou had also originally wanted to play it safe, but after hearing Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen's conversation, he agreed with Lu Hanwen's judgment. Ye Xiu and his team hadn't heard the news about Shadow Commander Shaan's spawn, they'd only casually asked about Huang Shaotian's location. But now with Huang Shaotian's reply, they were exposed. Aside from a boss spawn, there was no reason for Huang Shaotian to run to Barrier Mountains.

"Team Happy needs many things!" Yu Wenzhou thought to himself. He was very clear about the roster of that grassroots team, and knew that they had two Nightwalker classes, especially Windward Formation, who had history with Blue Rain. Yu Wenzhou's current account Swoksaar was originally that person's account, after all.

But right now, Yu Wenzhou was using an alt anyway, and so he didn't let himself dwell on the past - the thought just crossed his mind briefly, and then he began to ponder how best to combat Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu was undoubtedly the number one enemy. In the current situation, this guy would certainly break the equilibrium, so wouldn't it be safer to sort everything out before he got here?

Just as Yu Wenzhou was about to speak, he heard another voice cutting before him. "I say, to make this easier, how about we negotiate a plan?"

The sound seemed to come from Thunderclap's area. Yu Wenzhou was fairly sure who the speaker was, so he smiled and casually said, "You're in a rush?"

"Before that guy arrives. I'm sure everyone understands what I mean," said Xiao Shiqin.

"Mm… Agreed." From Misty Rain came a woman's voice. Misty Rain's captain, Chu Yunxiu.

"Hmph…" From Wind Howl there was a disdainful cough. Tang Hao knew to whom these people were referring, and was unimpressed by their fear.

"What kind of plan?" Someone asked from 301 Degrees. It was their captain Yang Cong. 301's strength here was slightly weaker compared to the others. If this became a direct battle, they would certainly be disadvantaged, so they were particularly interested in reaching some sort of agreement through negotiation to solve this problem.

Right now, the groups present were Blue Rain, Thunderclap, Misty Rain, Wind Howl, and 301 Degrees, with each team's respective captains present. Tang Hao's scoff wasn't quite an agreement to negotiations, but it at least wasn't a clear refusal, so he was automatically included in the talks.

"Let's each send a representative to 1v1!" Yu Wenzhou was the first to propose a solution.

"Opposed!" Xiao Shiqin immediately objected. 1v1, at first glance, seemed to be fair. But it depended on each side's members, and who they could send up! Blue Rain had Huang Shaotian, an absolute titan at 1v1s; he had a high chance of winning. Thunderclap could put up a fight. Itt wasn't like they'd be instantly crushed by Huang Shaotian, but their chances of winning would definitely be smaller. As for the other teams, they were probably in a similar situation. Yu Wenzhou's suggestion appeared to be fair, but it was definitely biased toward Blue Rain.

"Opposed!" As expected, Misty Rain's Chu Yunxiu also expressed her dissent, following the same train of thought as Xiao Shiqin.

"You want a 1v1, then let's 1v1!" On the other hand, Tang Hao was unafraid and boldly accepted the proposition.

Yang Cong hesitated. When it came to 1v1, his chances of winning were similarly low. But compared to a battle between the full forces of all sides, a 1v1 definitely increased 301's chances of success. Huang Shaotian, Tang Hao, and the others were much bigger players than he was. But in a 1v1, no one would dare say for sure that a win or loss was guaranteed.

"Well, we can't play a group battle, that'd waste too much time." Yu Wenzhou chuckled. Seeing two votes against him, he knew that his suggestion definitely wouldn't be accepted.

"Then to be fast, let's just roll for it!" Xiao Shiqin said.

"Relying on luck to decide? That's absurd! This should be decided by strength." Tang Hao immediately expressed his objection toward this plan.

"Hahaha, I remember hearing that Tang Hao was especially bad at rolling! I heard that he almost always gets less than 50, isn't that right?" From Blue Brook Guild's side came another person's voice. The fact that Huang Shaotian had managed to stay quiet until now was already quite a remarkable feat.

Originally, this was a captain-level conversation, and the other players were careful to maintain silence as they watched. Once Huang Shaotian spoke up, there were suddenly whispers everywhere. It was clear that this was a never-before-heard piece of gossip.

"What kind of skill is rolling?" Tang Hao fumed.

"Haven't you heard that luck is also a part of strength? For example…"

"What about this?" Chu Yunxiu ruthlessly interrupted Huang Shaotian. By the time they waited for that guy to finish, Ye Xiu probably would have already slaughtered his way here.

"Each of us can send out a few people and attack the boss in teams. Whichever team has the highest damage output can have the boss," Chu Yunxiu said.

"Hm, that's not a bad plan." Yu Wenzhou was the first to agree.

"It's alright. That way, I think five people per team would be enough," Xiao Shiqin said.

"Who's controlling the aggro? What about healing?" Tang Hao asked.

"We'll specially designate people to control the aggro and not count that in the damage output. Each side will be responsible for their own healing, and if they cause an OT, then they're disqualified." Chu Yunxiu efficiently laid out the details of her plan.

"Hm, if we do that, then I think sending three people per side would be enough. If there are more, then there'd be too much conflict. We'd get in each other's way," Yu Wenzhou said. If each side sent five people, then that'd be a large 25 person team attacking the boss. If the team was composed of all long-ranged classes, then it'd be a little better, but if there were more close-ranged classes, then that'd require careful coordination of position.

But this was supposed to be a competition. There was no way that someone else would willingly give up their position for you, and so there'd definitely be a lot of clashing. Even if everyone was on the same team and couldn't damage each other, there could still be plenty of intentional interference with other players' attacks.

"Exactly! Competition keep things interesting!" said Chu Yunxiu.

Yu Wenzhou felt a shiver. This woman, she didn't have some deeper plan, did she? At the same time, he saw Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic glance toward his Warlock.

These are in-game characters, we don't need to meet each other's eyes, do we? But it seems like you also have reservations about Chu Yunxiu's plan? Yu Wenzhou quietly thought to himself, but he truly couldn't find any reason to oppose her plan. At least, unlike his proposal of 1v1, the plan didn't obviously favor one side over another.

"Then let's hurry up and begin?" From Wind Howl, players had already jumped forward. Just by looking at their classes, it was clear that they were all members of Wind Howl's professional team.

Once he saw the classes of those characters, Yu Wenzhou suddenly realized what game Chu Yunxiu was playing. Team Misty Rain had many long-ranged attackers! Even if long-ranged attacks could also be blocked, they were still much better off than the close-ranged classes vying for positions near the boss. This was what she had been counting on.

Then what should Blue Brook do? For this battle, they couldn't just rely on the skill of the pro players, they also had to consider which classes would complement each other the best in this situation. Truly a competition of tactics! This was shaping up to be quite interesting.

Yu Wenzhou thought and eventually decided on a suitable team. They didn't all have to be pro players. Here, the class composition mattered more. But just as he was about to call out names, he heard someone in the group shout, "What's that?"

"Where?"

"Above!"

Yu Wenzhou raised his camera and saw the shadow of a character falling from the mountain's cliffside.

"This is…" Yu Wenzhou startled, but there were already others with sharper eyes than his, who could see the ID on top of that shadow's head.

Lord Grim!

An infamous name in their circles, Ye Xiu's unspecialized Lord Grim.

Free-falling at an acceleration at 9.8 m/s, Lord Grim seemed like he was about to crash into the mountain stream, but no one believed that this guy would just slip and fall to his death. At this moment, three shots of gunfire sounded. Lord Grim pulled out his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, sending an Anti-Tank Missile attack toward Shadow Commander Shaan.

The three shots fired one after another, three shots worth of recoil that slowed Lord Grim's body.

And then, the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella opened, and with the Mechanic's skill Rotor Wing, Lord Grim flew back up into the sky.

Not good!

Yu Wenzhou already realized what was going on.

"Quick, pull the aggro!" Yu Wenzhou hurriedly shouted. The others now understood what this was all about. The long-ranged classes launched their attacks, while the Knights immediately came to stabilize the aggro.

But it was too late...

In order not to disturb the boss, the various teams had maintained a considerable distance between themselves and Shadow Commander Shaan. But now Lord Grim suddenly fell from the sky and opened fire. The boss's reaction was of course instantaneous, especially since this was a Level 75 Nightwalker boss. Assassins, Thieves, Ninjas, they were all agile and lightweight classes.

The players couldn't scale the cliffs to the left and right of the mountain stream, but this wasn't an obstacle for this Level 75 boss. With one stride, Shadow Commander Shaan already leapt onto the cliffside, bounding and pedaling upward, instantly leaving behind all the long-ranged attacks of the players. Those clumsy Knights wanted to mock them, but there was no way for them to keep up with Shaan's speed.

But would the boss be pulled away just like that?

Incredulous, everyone looked up at the midair Lord Grim. To fly completely above the top of the cliffs, that simply wasn't possible for a player, was it? Whether an assassin's Air Jump, or a Mechanic's Rotor Wing, or a Witch's Broom Mastery, or a Summoner's Small Flying Dragon summon, or so on, the skills of these classes could help a player achieve heights that other classes wouldn't be able to, but they wouldn't allow a player to fly clear over these cliffs, would they?

It was true, these classes couldn't accomplish it. But Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was an unspecialized! If he used these skills in combination, this height…

Even though most of these skills weren't sub-Level 20 skills, it was no secret that the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella could change forms to allow the usage of higher-level skills.

As expected, after the Rotor Wing, Lord Grim jumped up again in midair, a movement that could only be accomplished with the usage of the skill Air Jump. And then there was another shot, an Aerial Fire that sent his character flying higher. Lord Grim waved his hand, and that Myriad Manifestation Umbrella was in some unknown form and was stuck into the mountain. Lord Grim twisted his body, landing on and jumping off the weapon; with a tug, he pulled the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella back out of the cliffside.

Fuck! This umbrella had ninjato abilities too? Everyone could only look on with dazed expressions...

Chapter 1092: A Hundred Tricks

When Ninjas used ninjatos, they could climb rocks unlike other classes. Thus, in theory, while other classes couldn't jump onto the cliff, Ninjas could use their ninjatos to climb on.

The other classes could only sit there and watch, while the Ninjas from the various guilds rushed out, brandishing their ninjatos in preparation to scale the cliff.

But using a ninjato required technique. Although normal players could perform a few tricks, knowing a few tricks wasn't going to be enough to chase a target. What was needed was speed and efficiency. As a result, everyone watched as the Ninjas rushed forward aggressively, climbed for a bit, and then dropped down like dumplings one by one. The number of players who could stay on the cliff could be counted on one hand.

However, among the Ninjas who could remain on the cliff, there were a few that stood out, especially the fastest one. His movements flowed smooth as water. He was the number one Ninja in Glory, Team Misty Rain's Li Hua, who used the character Dark Forest.

From Li Hua's Ninja, everyone could see hope. Everyone was filled with expectations as they raised their heads high, hoping Li Hua could accomplish something. But soon afterwards, a cold bucket of water splashed on them, extinguishing what little hope they had left.

Someone had attacked down from above the cliff. A Laser Rifle shot over. Even though Li Hua reacted quickly and dodged it, that was just the first test. All sorts of long-ranged attacks rained down the cliff as if they were all trying to outdo each other.

His guild's pro players closed their eyes, unable to keep looking. In this situation, Li Hua being able to smoothly scale the walls was quite good, but wanting him to pursue and attack? Intercept them? Forget about it…..

Yes, forget about it.

After dodging a few waves of attacks, Li Hua let out a sigh and chose to give up and return to the mountain stream along with the few other Ninjas, who were still hanging on.

"Thanks!"

In the global chat, Lord Grim said a single word.　　

"Despicable!"

"Shameless!"

"B*stard!"

"Ruthless!"

"Next time, you'll see!"

After Lord Grim said thanks, replies came one after the other. The reactions and hand speed of the pro players were worthy of their reputation.

The conversation in the global chat caused a commotion for the players. Everyone knew who Lord Grim was, but who were the guys replying back? No one had heard of them, yet they dared to challenge Lord Grim? Did these idiots not know who Lord Grim was?

"F*ck, where'd so many idiots come from?" Someone felt indignant at the injustice and made a remark.　　

"Yeah! Do you guys not know who Lord Grim is?"

"If they knew, they'd probably shit their pants."

"Haha, stupid noobs. They don't even know who Lord Grim is. Go back to school."

Trash talk came one after the other. The normal players might not be able to compare to pro players in fighting, but there was no lack of talented trash talkers. In an instant, words filled the screen. Everyone in the pro teams didn't know whether to laugh or cry and couldn't help but be at a loss for words.

"You guys don't even know the situation and you're bombing the screen. Who doesn't know that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu? You guys need to get your facts straight first. Don't you know how many people you've hurt with that screen bomb? It's best if you don't know. If you guys knew, you'd probably be crying tears!" For the pro players, there was only Huang Shaotian who wouldn't be outdone by the normal players in trash talking. Huang Shaotian's trash talking might not be too sharp and mean, but just the length alone would let him win if you went back and forth with him.

But this wasn't the Glory competition stage. This was the Heavenly Domain. Huang Shaotian wasn't up against five people. He was up against the millions playing the game. As soon as the players saw that someone was actually returning fire, they weren't going to let this rest. For a moment, the global chat had turned into a war. All sorts of players were talking trash about Huang Shaotian's Blade Master.

Huang Shaotian's win condition was by length, but up against the torrent of players, he was defeated in the end. It was a miserable defeat too. Apart from being one against many, the global chat had another big limitation for Huang Shaotian: talking had a cooldown.

"They're pissing me off!"

Because of the cooldown, he could only watch as people talked trash about him. For Huang Shaotian, there was nothing more hellish than this.

"You guys are all talk! 1v1 me! Does anyone dare to? Let's take this to the Arena. Fighting a hundred of you pieces of wood wouldn't be a problem!!!!" When Huang Shaotian realized that trash talking in the global chat was unwise, he tried to shift it to PvP.

How could the players retreat? People immediately replied. Some even ran over to create a room for Huang Shaotian to hurry up and bow down to them.

"That's enough. Do you plan on making next week's headlines?" Seeing that Huang Shaotian was actually intent on going to the Arena and have a bloody battle with these players, Yu Wenzhou finally spoke up.

In the end, Huang Shaotian didn't go to the Arena. The players who had opened up rooms, waiting for him, waited and waited, but didn't see him. How could there not scorching remarks fired at him? Fortunately, everyone in Team Blue Rain, including Huang Shaotian, had already logged off.

Shadow Commander Shaan was taken away by Happy just like this. If the guilds wanted to chase, they would have to go all the way around the cliff. There clearly wasn't enough time, so their only choice was to give up.

Dragon Swordsman, then Shadow Commander Shaan.

Blue Rain and Thunderclap had been thoroughly beaten by Happy two times in a row. The first time, their loss was fine. Ye Xiu had shown that he was more familiar and experienced at large-scale in-game battles than them. But the second time, everyone had clearly gotten there first, but Ye Xiu seemed to have descended from the heavens, relying on his shameless unspecialized class to steal the boss. That made them furious.

Blue Rain, Thunderclap, and the pro players from other teams gave an announcement to their teams: when hunting for wild bosses, the first task is to be on guard against Ye Xiu. The danger from this guy was even scarier than the other guilds combined. It was as if nothing could be done about it. Today's carelessness definitely couldn't happen again.

Soon afterwards, an opportunity to test the guilds had come. Both sides once again met. It was Gray Corner's wild boss, the Brawler Killer Dinglong.

From this boss's name, it sounded like he was a Fighter class, but in reality, he was a Gunner class. This time, there were a lot of guilds that got the news. Samsara and Tyranny. Their guilds unexpectedly didn't get the news for the previous two boss fights. But they weren't going to miss it this time. There was also Blue Rain and Thunderclap. After the two sides met, they remained silent for a long time. For this week's Level 75 wild bosses, these two had done the best in terms of gathering intelligence. Three wild bosses had spawned so far and they hadn't missed any of them. But so what? Despite not missing any of the spawns, the boss didn't go to them in the end. They had busied about for nothing.

This was already the third time, and they didn't want to go back empty-handed again. However, the confrontation this time was going to be more intense than before. Apart from them, there was Hundred Blossoms, Misty Rain, and Void? None of those were cheerleaders.

Fighting for wild bosses was like struggling for the championship title. Each side had a magnificent army with thousands of players, but only one side would win.　　

At the Gray Market, the Brawler Killer Dinglong had spawned. Since this was a street market, it was going to be a street battle. Even though the guilds hadn't acted yet, they had already started sending out people in secret. There were many high points on the streets. For long-ranged classes, getting the high ground was extremely important for displaying their potential. Not long afterwards, the surrounding rooftops, pavilions, anywhere that was higher than the ground, had someone stationed there. The various guilds were all mixed together, looking at one another. No one said a word. They paid attention to the boss's situation, while keeping an eye on the other opposing guilds. As a result, in order to protect their long-ranged DPSers, melee classes began to climb up to the high points to protect their players. The Gray Market was unreasonably rowdy.

"Oh, why are there so many people this time?"

There was no limit to the rowdiness. The guilds were on guard, pondering over how they should fight this battle. At this moment, the evil that needed to be defended against had finally appeared. They hadn't found his character yet, but they could hear his voice.

Happy had come!

This news was like the news of an important person's death. The news was being spread everywere.　

But when they tried looking for Happy, they were all in a daze.　　

It wasn't Happy.

Heavenly Justice, Radiant, Parade, Conquering Clouds... this group….. The guilds weren't strangers to them. In reality, for a long time, Happy hadn't been fighting alone. They would always be bunched together with these guilds, allying together to compete with the big guilds for the bosses.

The previous two times, Happy had operated alone. Now, these four guilds had come together. Happy had already grown to such a level. Did they still need this Alliance?

These guilds alone couldn't compare with the powerhouses, but together, their strength was evident. The pro players from the various guilds were almost about to collapse. This Ye Xiu. When there weren't too many people, he would play tactics with you. When the terrain wasn't easy to fight in, he would play his class against you. This time, there were numerous guilds participating. The competition was intense, so now he was playing the numbers game... no matter what the scenario, he had something prepared for you!

The powerhouses wouldn't be lacking in numbers either, but those responsible for undertaking an important task like fighting for wild bosses couldn't be ordinary fans. The elite players needed to be organized and disciplined. They had to guarantee that they would be ready to form a group at any moment. The guilds had to ensure that there were always two or three groups ready. Normal players might occasionally have some time to spare, and would participate and have some fun, but if you truly wanted to be like these elite players and be ready on call tens of times a week, how many people could endure it?

Normal players played the game for fun. Elite players played the game as if it were work.

As a result, even though powerhouses had many players, for fighting wild bosses, which needed to be done tens of times a week, it wasn't possible to have their entire guild come and fight. The number advantage that Ye Xiu and his allied guilds had was truly troublesome. It wasn't easy to gather more elite helpers to face this type of alliance. For this alliance, if they saw that the situation wasn't looking good, they could just leave. But the guild's elite troops were an official establishment. They couldn't just kick people out. That would damage their image!

Chapter 1093: Diversion

If you counted the five guild alliance, the wild boss of the Gray Corner, Brawler King Dinglong, had attracted twelve guilds. This was discounting those who might have gotten the message and were on their way.

With twelve guilds, there would be at least one elite team from each guild, making it a total of over a thousand characters clustered in this corner of the Grey Corner Blackmarket. There were quite a lot of people, but since it was a market, the terrain was full of stereoscopic buildings. The characters were scattered inside the buildings, outside the buildings, some on higher levels and some on lower ones. Even so, the place was still filled with characters. No space was left for the five guild alliance that had arrived a little late. And what aggro they had! As soon as they arrived, almost all the characters there had turned to look at them, prepared to fight.

"What's this? Did you all form an alliance or something?" Ye Xiu asked loudly.

It would have been better had he not asked, but now that he had, everyone was going with it.

"That's right, we're getting rid of you first!" It wasn't clear who exactly replied, but if they could represent the group to speak up, then they would have to be someone whose opinion was respected in the group.

　

"Tch, do you even know where I am?" Ye Xiu mocked.

　　

Looking around, the crowd realized that they really didn't know. Although pro players were skilled and had good audition skills, everyone was standing in clusters right now. While they could figure out the general area where Ye Xiu's voice was coming from, they couldn't find Ye Xiu's exact location. Ye Xiu wasn't like them, who used their main class on their alts. This guy was an unspecialized now, the combination of all 24 classes. This made his alt account situation rather complicated, too.

"Who cares where you are? If anyone dares come any further, we'll kill them all!" Another unknown person spoke up with a threat this time. However, considering how things were looking right now, it didn't seem like an empty threat. They were very united even if it was forced.

"Alright then, we won't go any further. We'll just stand and watch. You all go ahead," Ye Xiu said.

Over a thousand people simultaneously sent a sweat emoji and the speech bubbles that popped up covered a huge area at once. It was an impressive sight, to say the least.

"Old Ye, you can't just do that!" Someone jumped out of the crowd to speak. Everyone looked over. It was a Spitfire from Tyranny, fiddling with the automatic handgun in his hand.

"Yo, it's you. How have you been? Good?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I'm very well, thank you," Zhang Jiale said.

　

"Did you cry?"

"Fuck off!" Zhang Jiale erupted.

"I told you ages ago. Tyranny isn't good enough. If you want to win the championships, you should've come to Happy," Ye Xiu said.

Boos immediately rose from the crowd. Even though this was God Ye Xiu, who had the most championship titles under his belt, everyone felt that this sort of boast was just crazy.

"Who are you calling not good enough?" A Striker walked out of Tyranny's formation. After talking so much, Ye Xiu's character had been exposed. This time, he was using a Launcher.

"Old Han came too? How lively. I like it. I feel like we pro players should come in game more often when we're free to spar together, improve together, advance together," Ye Xiu said in a serious tone.

"Stop spewing bullshit and disappear already. Or do you want us to send you off?" A Blade Master from Blue Brook also came out. Just from the speed at which he talked, it was doubtlessly Huang Shaotian.

Zhang Jiale, Han Wenqing, Huang Shaotian!

　

The three surrounded Ye Xiu ready to attack. This face off alone was enough to have many people gasping! This was a face off that would only ever be seen in All-Stars! Not only that, the show at All-Stars wasn't as intense or serious as the competition for bosses.

"What are you doing? Trying to bully me with numbers?" Ye Xiu had his character back away as the elite teams of the five guilds behind him stepped forward threateningly.

"Either way, don't even think of causing trouble this time." Thunderclap's Xiao Shiqin had come over as well. Seeing that the situation wasn't bad, what with everyone so aggressively against Ye Xiu's presence, he didn't want to waste the chance to cooperate and kick Ye Xiu out of the competition.

"I'm not causing trouble. Can't I even take a walk here now? What do you want? Are you big guilds clearing the place, having your pro players bully others?" Ye Xiu yelled.

Hearing this, the crowd's fuse was blown. This guy was just being shameless!

"Why are we talking with this guy, just kill him!" Someone yelled.

"Who dares speak to me like that?" Ye Xiu yelled back.

With so many people and so many voices, no one could immediately tell who it was that spoke, but no one cared either. However, with five guild elite teams standing behind him, Han Wenqing and the others didn't dare charge over. Otherwise, that guy would definitely order the five hundred people behind him to drown them in people. Hoping that he would come out and 1v3 them was a naive thought.

As a result, not only was the attention of pro players turned over this way, the elite teams were as well. Everyone began to advance as one. This time, it wasn't just Ye Xiu's character but all of the five guilds behind him who began to retreat.

"What are you doing? You want to fight, huh? You aren't even going after the boss and you want to PK? That's unfair!" Ye Xiu said.

"If you don't want to fight, then leave. We won't let you have this boss."

"You think we're so easy to scare?" Ye Xiu called out.

"If you continue, it won't be good for anyone. Why don't you just take your people and leave?" Yu Wenzhou said from Blue Rain's side.

"Why do we have to go and not you?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Because you have no chance of winning." Yu Wenzhou continued to chat with Ye Xiu patiently.

"Heh, we might not have a chance of winning in a fight, but are we here to fight?" Ye Xiu suddenly laughed.

"Hm?" This reply had Yu Wenzhou lost for words. Then, he looked around, only to see that all the players from the guilds were facing off against the five guild alliance aggressively, cracking their fists and ready to fight at any time.

"Boss!" Yu Wenzhou, who was usually very composed, called out suddenly, his tone a little pained. At the same time, someone at their rear yelled out, "Boss!!!" as well.

That's right, boss!

Everyone's aggro had turned to Ye Xiu and everyone had forgotten that they were here to fight for a wild boss and not for Ye Xiu. Thus, when everyone's attention was elsewhere, a small team appeared at the other end of the Corner. They had no guild tags above their heads, like a normal passing team of players. They suddenly attacked, immediately pulling Brawler King away.

　

Was this a coincidence?

Of course not!

Yu Wenzhou was one hundred percent sure that this was one of Ye Xiu's schemes. This was his plan. He had managed to completely divert their attention.

All the teams hurried to respond, but that small team was definitely prepared and had planned for this. They knew exactly where to drag the boss, darting in and out of the streets of this black market smoothly. It was the elite teams of the guild that were having a lot of trouble. Operating as a whole in places like this made them clumsy.

It was a good thing that every guild had pro players. They didn't have the time to take care of their entire team and all rushed out individually, using their own judgement and methods to search for the boss.

Huang Shaotian, who had been at the frontlines of the face off against Ye Xiu, had managed to get his Blade Master to the frontlines of their hunt for the wild boss in the blink of an eye. With Yu Wenzhou's calm and clear analysis and arrangements, he quickly caught up.

"Where do you think you're going?!!" Huang Shaotian yelled, his Blade Master jumping down from a roof nearby and using Sword Draw midair. A flash of sword energy gathered on his blade and flew out. The attack seemed about to knock down a bunch of people, but then someone in the team suddenly charged out, their spear swinging up and dispersing the light. The Sword Draw had been parried.

Having to parry when only able to see the flash of light caused by the sword energy from the attack and not the blade itself was something you could do if you relied on mechanics alone. Huang Shaotian hadn't expected that his strike would be unsuccessful. Out of Happy's members, only Ye Xiu would be able to this. So who was this person?

Huang Shaotian had no time to wonder. The Battle Mage struck out with his spear once again and Huang Shaotian hurriedly pulled back his sword to guard in midair. He had wanted to use this strike to glide through the air and continue to chase the boss, but he hadn't expected that the other would realize his intentions and switch from a stab to a upwards flick. Huang Shaotian's Blade Master wasn't knocked to one side by this attack and was instead flicked upwards.

"Who are you?" Huang Shaotian was shocked. The Battle Mage's mechanics weren't what was shocking, but rather his understanding of his intentions and judgements. This definitely wasn't something that Happy's rookies could do.

"Who do you think?" The other retorted.

"Holy crap how did you get here weren't you a Launcher how did you become a Battle Mage?" Huang Shaotian yelled in surprise.

"I said, didn't I? I have eight computers open, logged into eight alts. Didn't you believe me?" Ye Xiu said, his spear once again striking towards Huang Shaotian's Blade Master, but this time, he directly used an ultimate, Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. Huang Shaotian's Guard skill was on cooldown, so he couldn't block the attack. Instead, he used a Rising Dragon Slash to pull his character higher in the air and dodge the attack. Then he saw that Ye Xiu's Battle Mage had long since canceled the skill and left him in the air to run back to his team.

"Fuck, don't you dare run!" Huang Shaotian hollered.

"Who's running?" Ye Xiu replied.

Huang Shaotian looked over again. Ye Xiu hadn't run. It was just that his Battle Mage had darted over by a body unit and blocked off Huang Shaotian's path beforehand. He had never planned to leave with his team, but stay and stall Huang Shaotian.

"Fuck!" Huang Shaotian immediately understood his intentions. By the time he was finished with Ye Xiu, who knew where the boss would be?

"Why are you such a slippery bastard?!" Huang Shaotian yelled.

"Hahaha, you should learn from me!" Ye Xiu didn't mind chatting with Huang Shaotian some more.

However, would a thing like speaking interfere with Huang Shaotian's combat ability? Of course not. He kept chattering on and on even as he charged forwards. His intention wasn't to fight Ye Xiu to the death, but to charge past him. But...

Lu Hanwen's Blade Master arrived, Zheng Xuan's Spitfire arrived, and Yu Wenzhou's Warlock also arrived. Huang Shaotian had worked hard to find the boss, so obviously he'd only share his intel with his own people and not the other guilds. The ones who had gotten his memo and came were all Blue Rain's people. Yet when they arrived, they found Huang Shaotian still here facing off against Ye Xiu. Where was the boss? It had left this street ages ago.

"It went that way. Don't worry about me, you just hurry and chase after it," Huang Shaotian called out.

"You think I'm not here or something?"

"Senior, you want to block us four on your own?" Lu Hanwen asked in shock.

"Don't listen to his bullshit! Hurry and give chase, little guy," Huang Shaotian yelled.

"I'm really worried for your IQ. You think you're the only one who knows how to call reinforcements?" As his words fell, Blue Rain's four pros were instantly surrounded.

Chapter 1094: There’s No Harm in Cooperating

Yu Wenzhou looked left and right. They were surrounded by tens of players. With

this sort of encirclement, even if they were able to break away through their

superior skill, they wouldn't be able to pursue the boss anymore.

Yu Wenzhou sighed. This encirclement wasn't really a trap, but rather an opening

from them. He had analyzed which direction the boss could have been pulled away

and then assigned people to chase after the boss. Sure enough, Huang Shaotian

found the boss. In this type of situation, they obviously wouldn't be sharing this

info with the other guilds. Not only would they not be sharing the info, they

had to protect this news from leaking. Thus, Yu Wenzhou didn't immediately

dispatch Blue Brook Guild elite troops to throw themselves at the boss. Such an

obvious movement would definitely attract the attention of others. Yu Wenzhou

didn't want to block Ye Xiu off from the boss, while also bringing along a

bunch of competitors.

　　

As a result, Yu Wenzhou instructed his elite troops to continue spreading out as

if they were still searching for their target in an attempt to mislead the

other guilds. In the meantime, their pro players would get together and go

over. A small-scale movement naturally wouldn't be seen through by others.

Their movements indeed didn't arouse any of the other guilds' suspicions, but Ye Xiu

had dispatched people to surround them, making them appear weak and outnumbered.

"Fighting isn't beneficial to either side. You guys should leave!" Ye Xiu said.

Yu Wenzhou laughed bitterly. Wasn't this what he had said to Ye Xiu a few minutes

ago. This guy was quick to return fire.

"Retreat." Yu Wenzhou immediately ordered.

"What?" Huang Shaotian was shocked.

"Wasting time like this is pointless. It's better to retreat!" Yu Wenzhou said.

Lu Hanwen and Zheng Xuan had started retreating. Even though Huang Shaotian was

unwilling, he respected his captain's authority. After spouting a bunch of

trash talk at Ye Xiu, he retreated helplessly.

"A man who recognizes the facts of a situation is a true hero!" Ye Xiu sighed.

"You flatter me." Yu Wenzhou said.

"If there's ever an opportunity, there's no harm in cooperating together." Ye Xiu

said.

"There will be one." Yu Wenzhou smiled.

Afterwards, some more nonsense was said. Ye Xiu was naturally stalling to give time for his

players to kill the boss. As for Yu Wenzhou, he had already given up. After personally participating in numerous wild boss battles, he now thoroughly recognized just how complicated these battles were. Several guilds, sometimes more than ten, fought against each other in a chaotic war. There was no way to predict anything.

Yu Wenzhou had carefully studied Blue Brook Guild's reports. He clearly saw that no matter which guild it was, their results were very inconsistent, following no patterns. It was possible that one week, one guild would succeed several times, while the next week, the guild failed to get anything. Whether it was Blue Brook Guild or Herb Garden or any other powerhouse, it was the same. Because of how chaotic the wars were, all sorts of impossible to predict events decided

the outcome each time. There was no absolute logic in any of these.

However, when Ye Xiu led Happy, the outcome was more consistent. Compared to the constant ups and downs of the other guilds, their relatively flat and smooth line was astonishing. Without a doubt, Ye Xiu was able to minimize the chaos happening in these battles, which meant that Ye Xiu's way of conducting battles was very valuable as a reference. From what Yu Wenzhou saw, Ye Xiu's tactical skill was certainly one aspect, but more importantly, he was able to accurately grasp the conflicts and balance between the guilds during these boss battles, allowing him to direct the overall direction of the battle. His tactical arrangements didn't stop at just purely

battle aspects such as movements, focusing targets, switching targets.

Doing this wasn't easy. Yu Wenzhou could see the painstaking amount of work that Ye Xiu put into this. It seemed even more difficult than them playing in competitive matches. There was only one match a week, but there were tens of wild boss battles every week. Just how much effort did it take him to do all this homework?

Therefore, when Ye Xiu suggested that they cooperate when an opportunity arose, Yu Wenzhou didn't hesitate to agree. He didn't mind Ye Xiu utilizing their guild's resources because in his eyes, Ye Xiu was a huge resource too.

Yu Wenzhou replied to Ye Xiu and then talked about it with Changing Spring. After all, this was an in-game matter. Technically speaking, the team captain had no such authority in this area. However, pro players had high statuses, especially the captain. Even though they didn't officially have any authority, their words held a lot of weight in anything related to Glory. A more assertive captain would practically be giving orders to the guild leader. Yu Wenzhou was rather polite. When he spoke to Changing Spring, it was more of a suggestion.

After Changing Spring heard Yu Wenzhou's suggestion, he was stunned.

Cooperation. It wasn't like he didn't know how to do that. It was just that the competitions between the guilds, especially the ones between the top guilds like Blue Brook Guild, had a "wolves are here" feeling. No one trusted each other's words. Whenever they cooperated, they would always be on guard for any backstabbing. Once or twice was fine, but if it was frequent, they wouldn't be able to endure this type of provocation. In the end, they might as well just do things alone.

Nothing could be done about it. The competition between the guilds could be considered another battlefield for the teams aiming to be the champions. For them, injuring others was beneficial for themselves. As a result, if they weren't able to get the boss, they didn't mind making things more difficult for their enemies. It wasn't just about strengthening themselves. It was also about finding a way to stop their enemies from growing stronger. In this type of environment, it was hard to have any good relationships with other guilds.

As a result, when Changing Spring hard about Yu Wenzhou's suggestion for a cooperation, he was startled at first. He really wanted to say that cooperating didn't fit this sort of environment. Don't say look at how Happy allied with four other guilds, so we should do the same. The guilds that Happy had allied together with were all bottom-tier cheerleader guilds. The relationship between those guilds weren't as tense. They were never really competitors in these boss battles anyways. It was like giving medicine to a dead horse. They might as well just ally together. Blue Brook Guild wasn't in the same position as them though!

Changing Spring was still pondering over how to explain this to Yu Wenzhou, but then Yu Wenzhou told him who he was planning on cooperating with: Ye Xiu!

Lord Grim!

Changing Spring was more used to calling people by their in-game names. Yu Wenzhou actually wanted to cooperate with that guy! Changing Spring could feel his head going numb.　

This was the first phrase that floated into Changing Spring's mind. That guy was too treacherous. If they cooperated with him, they would be nibbled down to the very bone!

"Ye Xiu! This… isn't this a bit hard?" Changing Spring heard who their collaborator would be. He couldn't even manage to think about how he should words things and immediately expressed his thoughts.

"Hm? What do you mean?" Yu Wenzhou asked.　

"According to our experiences interacting with him, he isn't very trustworthy!" Changing Spring's head shook like a rattle drum."

"Really? His reputation is that poor?" Yu Wenzhou laughed.

"More like there isn't anything good to say about it." Changing Spring grit his teeth.

"As one of his competitors, of course you wouldn't feel anything good from him. Have you ever seriously cooperated with him before?" Yu Wenzhou said.

"This….." Changing Spring hesitated. When Ye Xiu's Lord Grim entered the Heavenly Domain, they were already huge enemies. They had been trying to stop him the entire time. Cooperate? Changing Spring felt his face turn red. In the beginning, he didn't know that this person was God Ye Qiu. Most of their thinking had been on how to recruit him. Recalling how they had actually been thinking about recruiting this God to get him to do labor for the guild, Changing Spring suddenly felt like he had been quite bold too.

"Blue Bridge, when you were in the tenth server, you interacted with him a lot. What are your thoughts?" Changing Spring asked Blue River.　　

"Uh, if it's from a cooperative perspective, I feel like he's reliable….." Blue River couldn't help but think of the tenth server and how the God had been hired by them to do work for the guild. The prices that Ye Xiu gave them made Blue River feel like Ye Xiu was a very understanding person. He wasn't trying to cheat them and it was best not to try cheat him either. Under these conditions, the relationships between the two of them had been quite a happy one. How did they end up trying to kill each other? Blue River carefully recalled. It seemed to be when that guy stopped being up for hire and started doing his own work. Then, that guy monopolized all sorts of records, so the pioneering guilds stopped working with him and wanted to show him their might….

Thinking about this, Blue River realized that the top guilds had tried to suppress a competitor, except it turned out that their competitor was a God. In the end, they were like soldiers abandoning their armor as the furious dragon attacked them.

In this story, what they had viewed as the evil sect wasn't really an evil sect. Weren't they the bunch of bastards trying to bully the weak?

Thinking of this, Blue River suddenly wanted to cry. From his understanding, evil sects always had the advantage at first, but then they would always be destroyed by the righteous sects. When had there ever been a lowly evil sect covered in dirt? That evil sect would be too weak, no?

"Then, are we going to be joining their five guild alliance?" Changing Spring said in a daze.

"That's not necessary. When the battle is in our grasp, we should have full rights to the boss. When the situation is hazier, considering a cooperation with them might give us a chance to turn things around! If you take a look at Happy, that's pretty much what they're doing. If they can take the boss alone, they won't join up with the other guilds and share their spoils." Yu Wenzhou said.

"I understand." Changing Spring nodded his head.

Because Yu Wenzhou had decided to give up, Blue Brook Guild retreated from Gray Corner's Black Market. The other guilds were still looking around. In the end, Xiao Shiqin was able to find traces of the boss, but they were too late. The boss was already about to collapse.

"So you actually found us. Why don't you take a look at the time though?" Ye Xiu welcomed Xiao Shiqin, but he didn't put up his guard. At this point, any guild with a bit of perceptiveness would have left already. Xiao Shiqin was an understanding person, yet he sill insisted on searching for them. Ye Xiu reckoned that he had other motives.

"So you ran here." Xiao Shiqin sighed.

"What? Are you studying my tactics?" Ye Xiu said.

"Haha." Xiao Shiqin laughed, but didn't answer back.

"If there's ever an opportunity, there's no harm in cooperating together." Ye Xiu said.

"That sounds good." Xiao Shiqin said and sent a friend request.

"No need to add me as a friend. If anything comes up, just message me on QQ. This bro's got tens of alternates, how would you know which alt I'm using?" Ye Xiu didn't hesitate to reject it.

Chapter 1095: Immortals Fighting

Another announcement for Happy killing the Level 75 wild boss Brawler Killer Dinglong was issued. Even though the vast majority of players had no way of participating in wild boss battles, that didn't mean they didn't care, especially the veterans. They were fully aware that wild boss battles directly affected a team's strength. It could be considered as the second battlefield for pros outside the league.

And this week, of the Level 75 bosses, Happy had already taken down three of them. Such might made the other guilds feel gloomy, while shocking the rest of the players.

But in reality, this time's Brawler Killer Dinglong didn't solely belong to Happy. Their guild name was the one that appeared on TV, but Heavenly Justice, Parade, Radiant, and Conquering Clouds had participated too. Even though those four guilds had been a part of the backdrop, having a vast number of troops had been extremely crucial. The amount of work that they put in might not be much, but their contributions were essential. Ye Xiu's generous treatment towards his alliance buddies made the four alliance guild leaders feel very embarrassed. They stubbornly insisted that he take a greater share, while they split the rest evenly amongst themselves.

After splitting up the spoils, the four guilds promptly expressed their wishes. The representative for these four guilds was Heavenly Justice's guild leader, Team Heavenly Sword's team captain, and Club Heavenly Sword's boss, Lou Guanning. The holy trinity was too tyrannical. In the Alliance, only Lou Guanning possessed such status.

"God, why didn't you call us for the last two bosses? Don't forget about us!" Lou Guanning said.

"Yeah yeah yeah!" Those three guild leaders immediately added in their voices.　

Happy had enjoyed the last two wild bosses alone, putting these four guilds into a state of panic. As Happy advanced through the Challenger League to beating Excellent Era to win the finals, their popularity had risen to new heights. In the end, they were also able to establish quite a powerful guild. Moreover, new guilds that developed along with the team were the most passionate and energetic. It was easy for guild members to disregard their own gains and losses, putting their efforts into strengthening the team. As a result, the four allied guilds felt like the importance of their alliance was dropping. In fact, Happy had already taken down two wild bosses on their own without their help.

Five guilds cooperating together meant splitting the boss's spoils into five. And now, Happy had just taken down two wild bosses independently, which was equivalent to the five guild alliance taking down ten bosses. This comparison was too daunting. Anyone would know which choice to take. Thus, if Happy truly had the ability and renounced their partnership to take flight alone, the other four guilds wouldn't blame Happy. If they were in Happy's position, they would also make the same choice. In the end, everyone was working together for their own benefit. Joining hands and prospering together didn't exist here because there could only ever be one champion.

Happy taking down two wild bosses on their own worried the four guilds. Lou Guanning had been looking for an opportunity to communicate this with Ye Xiu. Then, after another boss spawned, Ye Xiu called over the alliance to gather. Once this boss was taken care of, the four guilds huddled up and discussed with each other. In the end, they directly raised this issue with Ye Xiu, wanting to see what response Happy would give. Everyone had been working happily together for a long time. No one had been cheated. Suddenly, Happy went out alone without telling them. There were definitely unspoken criticism from them, but the problem was that they had never agreed that if a wild boss came, they must share it. The agreement was just that if the opportunity arose, everyone could work together, that's all.

As a result, the four guilds had no grounds to criticize him, so Lou Guanning asked half-jokingly, hinting to Ye Xiu what their thoughts were.

How could Ye Xiu not understand the meaning behind his words? He laughed: "Is there really a need for me to say it? You all understand. After all, no team ever helps another for the fun of it, no?"

Lou Guanning heard his response and wanted to cry!

He was so direct. It was as if he were stating the obvious, and the four of them asking this question really made them seem foolish and naive. It went without saying. Everyone was fully aware. Not laying it bare could be considered as leaving them some face, but now that they had insisted on an answer, look, look how awkward the atmosphere is.

Fortunately, Lou Guanning and the other guild leaders were familiar with Ye Xiu. They immediately composed themselves and laughed: "You're right! If an opportunity arises in the future, don't forget to call us!"

"Of course." Ye Xiu smiled. In fact, he had called them over to kill Brawler Killer Dinglong for this very reason.

Lou Guanning had nothing else to say. The other three weren't that familiar with Ye Xiu. They might have some other thoughts, but nothing would change because Ye Xiu's words were spot on: in the end, they were still competitors. No team helped another for the fun of it. At least, that was definitely the case for them.

"Then, we'll see each other again if anything comes up. We'll be going first." The three guilds bade farewell.

"Mm mm, see you." Ye Xiu sent off the other guilds. Happy also called it a day. In-game matters continued to be taken care of by Wu Chen and Chen Guo. Ye Xiu and the others followed their usual routine and went on with their practice.

For their current practice, apart from improving their individual skill and teamwork, they also began analyzing their opponents. This work used to be done by Ye Xiu alone, but now he was having the entire team analyze. After all, he couldn't micromanage everything that happened on the battlefield. More often than not, the players needed to make their own decisions. Understanding their opponents was homework that no player could ignore. In the Challenger League, the vast majority of their opponents had nothing worth looking into, but it was different now. For the current Happy, these 19 teams were like towering mountains. There were too too many things to study. What Happy lacked the most wasn't skilled players or materials or equipment, but time.

Even so, they couldn't go too crazy. A healthy schedule was also necessary, especially after last season's finals. The issue of Tyranny's stamina issue had triggered a fervent discussion. Now, no one would ignore the effects of keeping a solid schedule.

Happy needed large amounts of materials, but playing 24/7 to get every single boss was no longer something that the team would do. As a result, the fourth wild boss that spawned this week didn't fall into Happy's hands. Guild Happy had gotten the message and went to participate, without Ye Xiu watching over, their competitiveness instantly fell. This was also one reason why those four guilds in the alliance were gloomy, seeing Happy wanting to fly out alone. Everyone knew the value of having a skilled commander, let alone a top expert like Ye Xiu.

After a chaotic battle, the fourth wild boss this week, Gray Corner's Underground Dark Hand, a Fighter, Gunner, and Nightwalker specialized boss, was snatched by Tyrannical Ambition. No pro players participated in this scuffle. According to the participants in this fight, this time's boss competition gave them an almost serene feeling.

This type of serenity was quite rare. Tomorrow, when the sun came out, the pro players would pour onto the battlefield. The pro players on vacation were more free. At least, they weren't required to practice during vacation. Practice was up to them to decide. Now that they had decided to go into the game and help the guild take wild bosses, why would the club object?

During the day, various battles bloomed where the bosses spawned. At night, the biggest topic in the Glory forums came from an anonymous post: what type of summer is this.

This summer, the number of pro players playing in the game had to be a record. In the early days, Glory was small. The number of pro players back then couldn't compare to the number of pro players today. In this post, the original poster listed all of the pro players that he had seen during this week's wild boss battles. From this, it could be seen that this poster was definitely an elite member of a top guild. An ordinary player wouldn't have had the chance to participate in so many of these battles.

And from how the description in the post was practically incoherent, it was evident that this elite player was on the verge of collapse. Just a while before, these elite players were existences that everyone admired. Even though their roles were like jobs and they were under pressure that many players wouldn't understand, these elite players did it in exchange for glory that ordinary players would never be able to obtain. But everything had changed now. The pro players pouring in made them… or at least, for this poster, it had resulted in a huge psychological blow to him. He didn't know what he could do or what he could achieve. He was the fodder when immortals fought.

The post was pretty much just him crying and complaining the entire time. His choice to go anonymous seemed to be the last shred of clear-headedness in him. Even more pitiful for him, not only did this post not garner any sympathy, it brought laughter from all sorts of players. Seeing these elite players, who usually sat up high looking down on them, being stomped on by even more elite pro players was a form of pleasure to them. As for the pro players, how could they talk bad about them? The pro players were their idols!

In the end, this post became a source of laughter in this scorching summer. It had no impact on the situation. The teams were using this summer to do everything they could to strengthen themselves. They weren't going to change just because of a single guild elite player's complaints.　

None of their plans changed. At this moment, the official Glory company made an announcement. Glory would be releasing a Summer Carnival event.

Event!

The players instantly knew what this meant: plenty of rewards. And the pro teams also woke up. For pro teams, events were also great opportunities to obtain generous rewards. But as per usual, if all they did was participate, the rewards would just be ordinary. The truly high-end rewards came out of intense competition. It was similar to dungeon records and wild boss battles. These types of competitions had always been what the game was about, and every event embodied this style too. Carnival. What type of competition would it be? And this time, there were so many passionate pro players participating. Just how fierce would the competition be?

Chapter 1096: Ghost Parade

Seeing the announcement, everyone naturally clicked on it to check the details and see just how much of a party it would be for it to be called a carnival.

But when they clicked on the page for this carnival, all they saw was a sinister ghost eerily staring back at them. The sound coming from their headphones was also the sound of evil winds. The less courageous players nearly had their hearts leap out of their throats. It was the scorching summer, but what arose from their hearts was a cold chill.

Summer Carnival: Ghost Parade

Scarlet-red words jumped out at them. At this moment, how could any of the players still felt like this was going to be a party? This event was clearly horror-themed.

Looking at the details, the event itself was actually quite simple. It was catching ghosts. It was a different approach to last last year's Christmas event of catching Christmas thieves, but the end result was the same. However, the event rules this time were more detailed and complicated. After all, it didn't coincide with a holiday.

The Ghost Parade would last one week. The system would release a certain amount of ghosts every day. The players just needed to find and kill these ghosts. The ghosts themselves gave experience, gold, materials, equipment, and so on. As for the more high-end rewards, those would be given out the same as always: through the leaderboard.

The leaderboard wasn't as simple as the number of ghosts killed because the ghosts released could grow. As these ghosts killed players, they would grow stronger. Stronger ghosts gave more points. The total points obtained was how the leaderboard calculated rankings.

In the normal servers, there was a clear separation between level ranges. The Heavenly Domain was much simpler since everyone was Level 75. Apart from the points leaderboard, there were other titles that gave out rewards. It was similar to dungeon first clears; only the first player to accomplish the feat was entitled to a reward.

Experienced players understood enough of it with just a few glances. Glory events tended not to be too complicated. Their main feature was competition. Only rewards obtained through competing against others gave the most beautiful rewards. As for the rewards from killing ghosts, those could just be considered as participatory rewards.

Normal players didn't have any hopes of making it to the top of the leaderboard, as per convention, Glory gave out final rewards depending on the player's position on the leaderboard. No matter what ranking you got, there would be an equivalent reward for you, so no matter what, everyone would be trying their hardest. Moving up a few ranks on the leaderboards meant better rewards.

The Ghost Parade would start on 7/7, the second Monday of July. After the update, when the players logged on, the Glory world became similar to the event page, dark and murky. Dense black fog covered the sky. Not a single ray of light shone, yet there was no rain either. The entire world sunk into a fog of gray.

There were no demons yet. The first wave would appear at 7 PM. In the next few days, the other waves would also come out at 7 PM.

In this dark world, the players did their usual work as they waited for 7 PM to come.

At 7 PM, the sound of a bell toll suddenly rang throughout the entire Glory world. No matter what corner of the world you were in, even inside a dungeon, the bell toll resounded in everyone's ears. The bell tolled seven times and the system released five huge scarlet words: Ghost Parade.

"AH!!!!" In a main city somewhere, an ear-piercing scream echoed. A female Blade Master leaped back four times, but still failed to break away from the pursuit of a bunch of round wooden barrels. These wooden barrels had originally just been very ordinary decorations on the streets. The players walked past them everyday. No one really paid any attention to them. At most, a bored player might step on it and jump around.

But when the announcement of the Ghost Parade came out, these wooden barrels seemed to have come alive.

That female Blade Master originally had her back to the wooden barrels on the lookout for these hundred ghosts to appear. How could she have known that there would be movement behind her? When she turned around, she saw these wooden barrels come to life, bending and twisting. A few of the lids on the buckets shook. It was as if these barrels were trying to swallow her.

The female player cried out in fear and hastily retreated. By the time the surrounding players noticed the commotion going on here, they saw a bunch of wooden barrels chasing after that female player. The female player wasn't able to escape. Her Blade Master was instantly swallowed up by the barrels. Then, the barrels dispersed. A beauty had passed away. Only a belt was left. Equipment actually dropped!

The players were shocked!

This barrel ghost killed someone in an instant. These ghosts weren't as simple as people had thought.

Without a clear grasp of the situation, the surrounding players didn't dare rashly advance. However, the wooden barrels took the initiative. The ghost chose another player on the streets and charged over. There were barrels rolling on the ground and barrels jumping into the air. One of the barrels had even leaped several meters into the air, crashing down like the fall of Mt. Tai.

"What's going on!!" The targeted player cried out and wanted to escape too, but these barrels had surrounded him, trapping him in the center. Following afterwards, the barrels converged and the player died.

The players on the street were struck dumb. They had been waiting for the ghosts to spawn, waiting to fight for every second, but then a bunch of dirty wooden barrels popped up and killed two people in just this short amount of time.

"It looks pretty strong. Ah?" A player said to his friend next to him, but he didn't hear a reply. When he turned his head, his friend, who had clearly been by his side just before, had disappeared wordlessly.

"Water Mountain?" The player called out. No reply came. There was no sign of his friend anywhere either. Just when he was about to pull up his friends list and message him, he suddenly heard something rattling from behind him. He turned around to look and saw the willow tree next to him reaching out with its tentacle-like branches to catch him. At this moment, the player saw a silver badge hanging on one of the tree branches. It was his friend's equipment.

The player instantly realized what had happened, but there was no time for him to scream. The willow branches climbed onto his shoulders and strangled him. His screen turned black. He couldn't see anything.

Health…...

The only thing that this player could see was his health falling rapidly. This type of damage was enough to put this willow tree ghost at the level of a dungeon boss! Was this an opponent a player could solo? Dungeons were always played with a team.

The player fell into despair. He was ready to meet up with his friend. Suddenly, he heard several snaps. He could suddenly see again. Countless sword light linked together, cutting the willow tree ghost's branches into bits and pieces.

The player couldn't bother with thinking too much. He immediately struggled free and jumped back. Then, he saw that player also jump back. Those were clearly a Blade Master's slashes, but then a fireball suddenly shot out from his fingers.

Fireball?

The player stared foolishly. Even if this was a low-leveled Elementalist skill, it shouldn't be coming out from a Blade Master's hands!

However, in the next moment, when he saw that person's ID, he immediately understood. Lord Grim.　　

Lord Grim!

God Ye Xiu's unspecialized - Lord Grim!　　

The player was stunned. This character hadn't been around for very long, but he had already turned into a legend in the game. The player had heard from his friends from the tenth server about how Lord Grim had dyed the tenth server red with blood. When he arrived at the Heavenly Domain at Level 55, he was chased by Level 70 players, who were even top experts of the big guilds.

Then, Lord Grim's identity was revealed. Lord Grim was God Ye Qiu. And from this moment on, Lord Grim's life became more difficult whenever anyone met him.

Every famous character in the game had experienced this sort of vexation. Whenever famous characters logged on, the luckier ones would just be surrounded non-stop. The unluckier ones would be chased and killed. But for this type of large-scale event, these characters couldn't miss it because the drop rate of all sorts of items would increase in this event. And among these items, there was one kind that was bound to a character and couldn't be traded. Only the character who picked it up could use it, so no pro character would dare ignore it.

Skill books!

Even the most end-game content, wild bosses, very rarely dropped them. Finding a skill book from a random monster required heavenly luck. If not, these pro characters would have maxed out their stats even if they died. They wouldn't be missing 100, 200 skill points back when they were Level 70.

The skill book drop rate was greatly increased like everything else, so pro characters naturally hoped to seize this opportunity. As a result, whenever a large-scale event came out, it wasn't difficult to find pro characters. However, these pro characters wouldn't be wearing their Silver equipment. If players killed them and their equipment dropped, it would be gigantic headache. Pro characters would just pick some random Purple or Orange characters to wear.

Lord Grim could obviously switch equipment too. It was just that his equipment had always just been in-game level equipment. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was a Silver equipment though. However, this weapon couldn't be switched, so Lord Grim would definitely be able to show his full strength.

Fireballs shot out in rapid succession. The flames gradually spread until it covered the entire willow tree. The willow tree branches kept on twitching as if it were struggling. As the flames rose into the sky, it burned. Finally, it stopped moving. Lord Grim went back, raised his arms, and his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear. With a Circle Swing, the willow tree was knocked into the air and then broke up into burnt chips. It had been thoroughly killed.

"How strange. That didn't count as a first kill?"

The players on the streets were still screaming because of the various objects that had turned into ghosts. On the other hand, the God was wondering why he hadn't gotten the first kill. This was the difference between them...

Chapter 1097: Intense Competition

The ghosts appeared so suddenly and unexpectedly, catching countless players off guard. As a result, Ye Xiu killing a ghost so easily and calmly made him seem that much more imposing. It wasn't just the player that Ye Xiu had saved. The entire street of players quickly realized that someone over there had successfully killed a ghost.　

It didn't seem like all that much?

This scene made the confidence of the players skyrocket. Quite a few immediately took out their weapons and charged at these strange phantasms.

Their spirited shouts quickly turned into cries of despair. Too many of them had only seen that a player had killed a ghost and hadn't paid attention to that player's ID.

Lord Grim, Ye Xiu. He was a figure that stood at the top of Glory. How could normal players hope to replicate his grandeur? Dungeon monsters weren't that easy to kill for normal players.

The entire street transformed into a field of slaughter. The players hadn't been prepared for the difficulty of this time's Ghost Parade. Their confidence from seeing Lord Grim successfully kill the willow tree instantly disappeared into nothingness.　

The players screamed and fled in fear. As for the imposing figure that had killed the only ghost over here, he became their savior. They couldn't help but gather towards this player. After getting closer, they saw his name and finally understood that they had made a misunderstanding.

"God, save us!!" Several players begged. Lowering themselves in front of God Ye Xiu was nothing shameful.

"Everyone, calm down!" Ye Xiu called out, "These ghosts aren't difficult to deal with. Pay attention to their weaknesses and then choose a target that you can easily restrain to fight! If that's not enough, party up."

Yes, if they couldn't solo an enemy, partying with others was the easiest solution. The players in the game should understand. It was just that for this event, would playing alone or partying with others give more rewards? The players needed to consider this question before deciding, so no one had immediately formed a party. However, after realizing that these ghosts weren't so easy to kill along with Ye Xiu's advice, the players started calling over their friends or searching for a party to join. Ye Xiu received countless party invites.

As for the ghosts' weaknesses…...　　

"What type of weaknesses do they have, God?" Someone asked.　　

"I'm studying them too." Ye Xiu replied. It was his first time seeing these types of monsters, "Wood is afraid of fire. Fire is afraid of water. Basic logic shouldn't be wrong."

Ye Xiu had tested this theory before. For example, against that willow tree, he had only thrown out a few low-leveled Fireballs, instantly burning that willow tree to ashes. It was far more efficient than hacking at the tree.

The players seemed to somewhat understand. At this moment, all sorts of ghosts were starting to attack them.

Look for weaknesses! The players started racking their brains. The very first ghost that had charged over at them made them want to cry. Wooden barrels. What was its weakness?

Fire?

These barrels were made of wood. Players with fire element attacks tried their hand, but it didn't seem too effective.

What is it?

The players pondered over this question but couldn't figure it out. Ye Xiu was standing on the side and also sweating. When he said weaknesses, he had just been speculating. Who knew if all these ghosts had weaknesses? However, right now, the players were bitterly searching for one as if they were following an imperial decree. Ye Xiu suddenly felt like there was a lot of pressure on him.

Amidst the chaos, someone suddenly yelled in pleasant surprise: "Attack the bottom! Attack the bottom of these barrels. The lower you go, the lower their defense!"

Everyone was startled, but quickly responded. If a barrel didn't have a bottom, then it couldn't be used, so the bottom of the barrel was the weakness?

It was quite logical, but anyone who thought of such an answer had to be a bit crazy.

After finding this weakness, the players discovered that these buckets weren't that difficult. A bunch of wooden barrel bottoms were destroyed. These wooden barrels instantly lost their liveliness. They fell to the ground and rolled around powerlessly.

"Kill!" Their morales had truly risen this time. After figuring out the trick, they suddenly became fearless.　　

As for Ye Xiu?

His goals weren't so low. As he looked for monsters to kill, he checked the leaderboards.　

The leaderboards were dazzling to the eyes. The event had just begun, but the pro players were already displaying what true strength was. The first ten and even as far as the first twenty places were occupied by pro players.　　

Troubling Rain, Vaccaria, Cloud Piercer, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Desert Dust, Demon Subduer…...

The previous events also had leaderboards, but they weren't fully occupied by pro characters because if it wasn't an event taking place during a holiday, pro players wouldn't usually be the ones playing on these characters. It was usually someone from the guild department playing in their place. The staff members of the guild department could be considered elite experts in the game, but they were far from possessing the dominating skill of pro players. However, the Ghost Parade happened to take place during the summer. The pro players personally took up the task, resulting in them sweeping the leaderboards.

Ye Xiu looked at his ranking. He wasn't in the top ten, but he wasn't too far away either. He was currently ranked 16. Surrounding him were a bunch of pro characters. The points were constantly fluctuating. A few moments later, he dropped from 16 to 18, overtaken by Flying Sword and Blossoming Chaos.

"Everyone's working hard!" Ye Xiu mumbled. He couldn't relax either. The street that he was on had quite a few ghosts, but there were also quite a few players. Everyone was fighting over them. No matter how skilled he was, it was hard to avoid his efficiency dropping. A quiet and desolate place was ideal. Unfortunately, when Ye Xiu logged on, he couldn't find any good places. He could only blame it on his bad luck.　

Yes, luck.

In this type of event, technical skill and tactical skill were secondary. Luck was most important, especially for pro players who were all at the similar skill levels. Only normal players would flee in terror because of these ghosts.

However, the normal players had started forming parties and helping one another as if it were a dungeon. Their combat power instantly shot up. The ghosts on this street were quickly cleared. Ye Xiu found the time to check the leaderboards again and found that he had already dropped outside of the top 20.

Only a fixed number of ghosts spawned every day all in one wave. As time went on, trying to catch up to those ahead required even greater luck. Today clearly wasn't Ye Xiu's day. After that street was swept clean, he looked for another place to hunt, but his kills were intermittent. He continued to fall on the leaderboards, making Ye Xiu feel even more helpless.　

After going around several blocks, Ye Xiu realized with astonishment that there were bunch of tails following behind his butt.

Yes, not just one tail, but a bunch.

Ye Xiu's Lord Grim stopped on a stone bridge in the city and turned around. He could already recognize some of their names. However, these guys were still pretending. Some of them were switching equipment. Some of them acted like they were chatting with each other. Some of them even pretended like they were just passing by, walking past Lord Grim.

"Which guild are you guys from?" Ye Xiu asked.

No one paid him any attention. They continued with their act.

"Stop pretending. You, the one following me since that clock tower. You, the one from the river area four. You, you were at that street in the very beginning, no?" Ye Xiu pointed at a few characters. They finally stopped pretending and started backing away cautiously. They were also sizing up the other players around them.　　

"It looks like you're not all from the same guild?" Ye Xiu saw this scene and said.

Still no one answered. Ye Xiu didn't need them to answer. These guys obviously weren't here to admire him and ask for his signature. The big guilds had found his location and sent people here to mess things up for him. They couldn't stop him, but they could at least slow him down.

"How mean! Who sent these people to follow behind my butt!!" Those players weren't going to talk, so Ye Xiu could only go to the pro player chat group and fiercely denounce the conduct of these guilds.

No one paid him any mind.

Everyone was playing the game, and the pro player chat group was unexpectedly dead. How long had it been in the pro scene since everyone had gone into the game? Ye Xiu felt a bit dazed.　

"Wu Chen, have our guild members take note of where the other pro characters are located." Ye Xiu returned to the game and messaged Wu Chen. His Lord Grim was also in Guild Happy. Any orders that he gave in the guild would naturally be followed. However, their guild leader was still Wu Chen and since this was a new guild, establishing a guild leader's authority was very important. Pro players abusing their statuses to do certain things in the guild was harmful to the guild's management.

"Oh, okay." Wu Chen replied back and then announced it to the guild.

Guild Happy had also reached max capacity. There were certainly spies from other guilds inside. Five minutes hadn't even passed since Wu Chen's announcement and the pro player chat group started livening up again.

"Revenge breeds revenge*." Wang Jiexi said.

"There will never be an end to it!" Huang Shaotian finished the saying, but a sentence was too short, so he added in his own personal opinion: "Old Ye, do you really need to do that? Insisting on a going an eye for an eye is too unsightly!"

"Exactly! Events like this don't come often. Let's all be friends!" Samsara's Jiang Botao also spoke his opinion.

"Then why don't you guys tell your guilds to withdraw the people tailing me?" Ye Xiu said.　　

"Yes yes yes..." The pro players expressed. Not long afterwards, the anonymous stalkers gradually dispersed.

"Okay, there's nothing wrong now, right? Let's all have a friendly competition. Old Ye, you've gotta work harder! When I check the leaderboards, I can't even see you!" Huang Shaotian said. His Troubling Rain was currently number one on the leaderboards. It was a rare chance for him to gloat.

But in time it took for him to type out these few words, the leaderboards suddenly changed.

"Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck!!" Huang Shaotian roared in the chat group. Zhou Zekai's Cloud Piercer had jumped from third to first, pushing Troubling Rain down to second.

"Ha." Zhou Zekai rarely spoke in the chat group, and he only said one word.

Chapter 1098: Seaweed Monster

Huang Shaotian wouldn't be Huang Shaotian if he didn't shoot back. However, Ye Xiu wasn't in the mood to admire his trash talking. He might have gotten rid of his tails, but his placing on the rankings hadn't changed.

32.

That was his current placing. The street he began on had helped him stay in the top twenty, but after leaving the street, Ye Xiu's luck wasn't very good. He didn't meet enough monsters to let him keep his position. His current 32nd place was temporary and considering how peaceful the street that he was on was, his placing would probably fall even more when he reached the end of the road.

No matter what, he couldn't just stay there and not move. The ghosts spawned at the same time. If they weren't there, they weren't there; it wasn't like you could wait at their respawn point for them to respawn.

　

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim walk over the stone bridge and ended up at a crossroads with a left, middle, and right path. However, all three choices seemed equally peaceful. Ye Xiu wanted to cry. Why was he so unfortunate today?

Let's just keep walking! Ye Xiu thought to himself as Lord Grim stepped onto the bridge. He was about to continue walking when, suddenly, he realized that he couldn't step forward. Next, his character's view spun and Lord Grim was thrown to the ground.

Where did this attack come from? Ye Xiu was stunned.

The moment Lord Grim was about to hit the ground, he hastily Quick Recovered, but it didn't work. The strike had been a grab, but it somehow managed to close in on Ye Xiu without him noticing, striking a direct hit.

　

It was only after his character had been pulled to the ground that Ye Xiu saw what had hit him as he turned Lord Grim's view. Something had tangled itself around Lord Grim's ankle.

What was it?

Ye Xiu didn't even have the time to look at it clearly when it suddenly yanked backwards. Ye Xiu slashed at it as it moved and Lord Grim's sword struck an accurate hit, but nothing happened. The thing shrank and then, with a flick, pulled Lord Grim upwards into the air. With this, Ye Xiu had a clear view. This weird thing that came out of nowhere had crept out of the lake under the stone bridge. Seaweed covered the lake surface, almost entirely, and it was impossible to see what was actually at the bottom of the lake.

Lord Grim switched the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to its gun form and sent a Gatling Gun towards this unknown monster. Water splashed everywhere and seaweed flew into the air, but this thing was still unaffected just like when he slashed at it. Ye Xiu still couldn't tell what was under the lake. Then, with a splash, Lord Grim was pulled under the water.

Where is it?

As soon as he went under, Ye Xiu looked around, but didn't find anything. The thing around Lord Grim's ankle was still there. Ye Xiu followed it upwards with his eyes and suddenly realized, how come it was coming from above the water now?

What monster was this?! Ye Xiu could feel a headache coming on. If there was any difficulty in the Ghost Parade, then for Ye Xiu, it would be what he was currently experiencing: the ghosts were all completely new NPCs. He had never previously encountered any of them in game, so he didn't know any of their characteristics or skills. Even Gods were newbies when up against these completely new monsters.

And now, Ye Xiu had encountered a very tricky one. Although he had confidence he could defeat his target, every minute spent on it was a minute lost. Just look, he had already fallen to 35 in this short span of time. Ye Xiu was still in the claws of this monster, but he still had time to check the rankings, finding he had fallen by another three places already.

In that instant, the monster finally launched another attack, and this time, Ye Xiu finally figured out what it was.

It was seaweed!

The seaweed that covered the entire surface of the lake, green like something that had been vomited out, was the true form of this monster. No wonder it had seemed to come from under the water at first, but later seemed to come from above. This thing was on the water's surface!

It had taken Ye Xiu quite a while to figure out what he was fighting and the seaweed monster had already began to attack him by then. The seaweed that had been floating on the surface suddenly sunk in clusters, like will-o-wisps.

Ye Xiu didn't know what kind of attack this was, but he wouldn't let it hit him so easily. He hastily had Lord Grim swim further down. However, something tightened around his foot. The seaweed was still tangled around Lord Grim's ankle.

What a long CC!

Ye Xiu was shocked. Even if it was an NPC, their skills still couldn't diverge from Glory's design. Offensive attacks dealt damage and crowd control effects lasted a duration of time. No matter if it was damage or duration, there had to be a limit. How long had this seaweed been restricting Lord Grim's movement? How was it still doing this? How long did this ghost's skills last for?

Ye Xiu didn't have the energy to spare on complaining because the will-o-wisp seaweed that had sunk down had attacked. Their attack was very basic, just throwing themselves at Lord Grim in an attempt to hit him. However, there were too many sunken clusters of seaweed to count. He could dodge one, but if they all began to attack together, then they'd form a net and then there wouldn't be any room to dodge.

He had to dodge them preemptively!

　

The seaweed was preventing him from going down, and upwards… Above him was the water surface which was covered in seaweed. Going upwards would be putting himself in the monster's embrace, an even worse choice.

Hurry up and break!

Ye Xiu could only keep going down. Snapping the restraint around Lord Grim's ankle became key. He slashed down again. The seaweed bent with the slash, but it refused to snap. It was clearly extremely flexible and durable...

Ye Xiu didn't have time to try out new methods and could only follow his current line of thought. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella switched to its gun form. With a bang, a bullet shot out. As the bullet left the chamber, the umbrella was transformed into a sword once more, striking down.

The bullet hit the seaweed and the flash of the blade slashed down as well. This time, the seaweed was cut through completely. Ye Xiu hastily had Lord Grim dive as the clusters of seaweed swarmed forth, crashing together in a ball.

That was close!

It was rare for Ye Xiu to ever experience such a heart-stopping moment in the online game. After noticing the flexibility of the seaweed, Ye Xiu gave it a Spitfire's Stun Bullet, and after causing it to tense, he was able to easily slash through it. Then his eyes landed on the cluster of seaweed behind him and had Lord Grim throw a Grenade over. It'd feel very good to blow it up.

As expected, it felt delightful!

The large cluster of seaweed was blown to pieces and several pieces hit Lord Grim. His health immediately plummeted, falling directly to red blood.

What the fuck!

Ye Xiu flailed in a panic. He immediately opened up the umbrella as a shield, while casting all his healing skills on himself and ingesting all the potions that would help him save his life. Only then was his health stabilized.

What a powerful attack! Ye Xiu was shocked. If just another two pieces had hit him, Lord Grim would have been KO'ed. This immense damage output was beyond anything Ye Xiu knew of. Their combative power rivaled that of dungeon monsters, but this sort of attack power was far beyond normal dungeon monsters, it was boss level, wild boss level even!

Ye Xiu didn't dare underestimate this monster. The seaweed that had been blown apart by the grenade hadn't died, floating in the water and preparing a new round of attacks.

How would he kill this seaweed? Would a Stun Bullet work again them? Ye Xiu had little to go on, but knew he had to try. He shot a small cluster of seaweed and struck down with his sword right after. The small cluster immediately broke apart, dispersing in the water as if it had dissolved.

It worked!

Ye Xiu was certain now, but he wasn't happy. With the seaweed covering the entire surface of the lake, how many attacks would he have to make to kill it completely?

As for how the seaweed got so strong, Ye Xiu immediately got the gist. This seaweed floated ever so peacefully on the water's surface like that, a very cunning disguise. Then, it would ambush passing players. Even Ye Xiu didn't realize what was happening after being caught, so there was little need to explain how much worse it would be for normal players. Continuously managing to kill players this way, the seaweed monster had grown this strong.

　

Should he count himself lucky or unlucky? Ye Xiu didn't know. Such a large monster would definitely provide many points, so he should be happy about finding it. The problem was, this monster wasn't just big, but powerful. Could he beat it?

This thing's attack power rivalled a wild boss. If its health was also that shocking, then Ye Xiu would just give up on it entirely. But for now, he decided to take a shot.

The small clusters of seaweed were just a method of attack for the seaweed monster. Destroying them was just defending himself. If he wanted to kill this monster, he had to attack its main body, the seaweed that was floating on the water's surface. However, he had to deal with these small clusters first.

Not long later, Ye Xiu baited the small clusters of seaweed into trying to catch him again like before. Then, at the last minute, he dodged.

The small clusters of seaweed once again clustered up into a larger group. Lord Grim turned and delivered a Stun Bullet before his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella swung up as a spear, Dragon Tooth stabbing up before a Double Stab followed. As for skills like Falling Flower Palm that required him to get even closer, Ye Xiu didn't dare use them before he tested them out. After the Double Stab, he finished it off with a Sword Draw.

The three skills were completed in an instant, and with the whooshing sound of flowing water, the scattered seaweed vanished.

It worked!

With this experiment a success, Ye Xiu's spirits lifted. The seaweed monster was above him. After this experiment, Ye Xiu had a good idea of how to deal with it. Now he had to see if he could destroy the main body of the seaweed monster with the same method. If it had the durability of a wild boss, then he'd leave immediately.

In the next moment, Lord Grim entered attack range of the water's surface, flicking his sleeves and gathering a chunk of the seaweed on the water's surface into a ball with a Shadow Cloak. Then, a Stun Bullet and an attack!

Chapter 1099: Jumping to Number One

Dragon Tooth, Double Stab, Sword Draw!

Ye Xiu chose to continue use what had worked before, except that after three skills, the cluster of seaweed was still good and well. The durability of the main body was, as expected, slightly better. However, it was only slightly. Ye Xiu quickly followed up with a fourth skill and, at last, the seaweed he had gathered with Shadow Cloak dispersed into nothingness. Ye Xiu gave a long sigh of relief. In that moment, he had been rather nervous, because the effects of Stun Bullet had a limit to its duration. When he had delivered the first strike, he knew that the problem wouldn't lie in if he could deal enough damage to destroy the main body or not, but time. Could he deal enough damage in the time given by the Stun Bullet?

In the end, he succeeded. This made Ye Xiu feel much more secure. Lord Grim jumped out of the water, right through the destroyed cluster of seaweed. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened into a Rotor Wings and he immediately left the water behind him.

The seaweed monster wasn't willing to let go of its target so easily, hurriedly sending out a tentacle to catch him. Ye Xiu had been expecting that and had Lord Grim rise up at full speed. The seaweed wasn't slow either, but characters could move around in the air with Rotor Wings, so Ye Xiu would naturally use this to dodge. Ye Xiu wasn't planning to leave. Leaving the lake surface was just to wait for his skill cooldown. Low levelled skills always had short cooldowns, but those that had a bonus effect like Stun Bullet would have a longer cooldown, otherwise, if someone could endlessly keep their opponents CCed - and one like stun, too - there'd be no need to fight.

Stun Bullet's cooldown was a full ten seconds and Ye Xiu was currently trying to last through these ten seconds. However, he wouldn't just keep dodging. As he dodged, Lord Grim threw a Grenade down. The surface of the lake exploded. Though this didn't really do any damage to the seaweed, since it had come out of the water, the seaweed had all been squeezed into a cluster.

It worked!

Ye Xiu was relieved. If he could gather the seaweed like this, then killing the seaweed monster would become much faster.

Soon enough, the cooldown for Stun Bullet was over and Lord Grim landed as Rotor Wings ended, striking his sword at the water's surface and sending out an Earthquake Sword to sweep the seaweed together. Then, he added a Shadow Cloak. This time, he had gathered even more seaweed, but when Lord Grim began to attack, Ye Xiu knew that this wasn't good.

The more he gathered, the more health the seaweed had. This was a very logical design. Ye Xiu hadn't neglected that, of course. He had gathered the seaweed this time with the intention of trying things out. After making so many attempts, he was now certain he'd be unable to destroy the seaweed in the time the Stun Bullet gave him.

Stun Bullet's stun effect lasted for two seconds and this duration wouldn't see much increase as the skill's rank was raised. After all, the control effect of a stun was very powerful. An eight or ten second stun would be beyond broken. When Stun Bullet was maxed out, the stun effect would only be increased to 3.5 seconds, so it was up to the player to decide how many ranks to raise it in accordance to their reliance and usage of Stun Bullet. Lord Grim's Stun Bullet was only rank one with the basic two second stun. Using four skills in two seconds was already his limit and Ye Xiu had to make sure he didn't slip up at all. Now, the seaweed had even more health, so Lord Grim, with his abysmal damage output, wouldn't be able to destroy such a large cluster no matter what.

This result was greatly disappointing for Ye Xiu. However, with two rounds of gathering to go on, he now knew very clearly on how much to gather at one time. Then, all he had to do was repeat.

The seaweed was cleared up bit by bit by Ye Xiu and the lake soon returned to its original clean state.

He was nearly done.

Seeing the two clusters of seaweed over there, Lord Grim swam over and then Ye Xiu heard voices coming from the bank.

"It's right over here!"

"We don't know how many players it's killed already. This seaweed monster is extremely powerful, so keep your guards up."

"However, we've already found a way to defeat it. Witches and Spitfires, make sure to cooperate. You're the key."

　

A large group of people had gathered at the lakeside. Normal players weren't idiots either, having also found a way to deal with the seaweed monster. It was just that they had no way of completing all the steps on their own, so they could only get helpers to cooperate with them. The group of people had excitedly rushed over to kill this massive monster, but what they were met with was a clear lake. Where did the seaweed that was said to be taking over the lake?

"Shit! No way!"

Some observant players quickly noticed Lord Grim's existence, swimming to a cluster of seaweed, Shadow Cloak, Stun Bullet, then a rapid stream of combos… Wasn't this the strategy their team leader had been emphasising the whole way here?

"Are you goddamn kidding me?!"

The one who had gathered all these people here was a Spitfire player. The first time he had came, he had been ambushed by the seaweed monster and killed. Then, running over to get his revenge, he had been killed again. He couldn't accept it and came again. By then, the seaweed monster had grown quite a bit and he was even less of a match, but this time he had discovered a way to kill the seaweed monster. The fourth time, he had charged over, thinking that knowing the method to killing the monster would assure his victory, but he had underestimated the strength of the seaweed monster. After dying four times in a row, he finally relented and went and gathered a team, also figuring out a good way to gather the monster. However, by the time he returned, he found most of the seaweed gone and the one who did it had done so with the method he had gained through four sacrifices.

"Who dares!" The leader was enraged. He thought that this person had been watching him and stole his method. He was a dirty thief.

Chasing after the figure along the bank, the team leader held up his gun to shoot, but was suddenly knocked into by one of his companions. With a stumble, his shot missed.

"What?" The team leader was furious.

"Are you stupid? Shadow Cloak, then Stun Bullet afterwards, then followed up with a combo including Sword Draw. Can't you tell who this is through those variety of skills?" The one who had knocked into the team leader said.

The team leader paused. In the past, if anyone saw a character using skills across different class types, they'd think it was an NPC, but now, all the players knew that there was such an existence: God Ye Xiu and his unspecialized, Lord Grim.

The team leader trembled as he walked along the bank a little further, and by then, Lord Grim was also swimming towards the last cluster of seaweed. The name above his head was finally visible to the team leader.

Lord Grim. Sure enough, it was Lord Grim.

Immediately, the misunderstanding of stealing his method was dismissed. If he couldn't even figure out this method on his own, then would he still be God Ye Xiu? It was just that the team leader had been bustling around, sacrificing himself and gathering helpers, confidently returning to reap his profits, but in the end he didn't even manage to get the scraps. That was too depressing...

"There's another cluster!" The team leader couldn't accept this. "Witches, go, Shadow Cloak!"

The Witch didn't move.

"Why aren't you guys doing anything? Did you disconnect? You there?" The leader yelled.

　

"And try to steal God Ye Xiu's kill? Are you crazy?" The Witch asked in shock.

"But I found it first!" The team leader wailed.

"Found it first…" The entire team was speechless. Though they understood this guy's feelings, you might have "found it first", but if you "found it first" yet didn't kill it first, then it wasn't yours. This was common sense.

"Go on, hurry up and go!" The team leader went to yell at another Witch, seeing that the first one refused to move.

This one seemed to be close with the team leader and didn't have the heart to reject the other. However, he went up slowly, raising his broom into the air for several seconds without doing anything. By the time he was done posing, Lord Grim had ended the battle. The one who had been about to attack turned back around in relief. "Oops, it's too late now…"

The team leader cried. However, he neither had the skill or a good reason to bother Ye Xiu about this. What made him even more jealous was that after the seaweed monster was killed, Lord Grim's position on the rankings had managed to instantly jump to first.

The team leader hadn't noticed at first. What brought it to their attention was someone suddenly yelling about it in the global chat.

"Fuck fuck fuck!! What cheat did you use, Ye Xiu!? How did you suddenly get to first, did you kill the GM?! You cheat, I'm reporting you, isn't there a GM here to make sure this sort of thing doesn't happen?!"

The cathartic speech came from Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain. The entirety of Glory was silent. No one had thought they would get the chance to admire Huang Shaotian's trash talk in the game's global chat.

Huang Shaotian had been overtaken by Zhou Zekai, but then his luck had been pretty good and rapidly took his place back. As for Ye Xiu's Lord Grim, he was thirty something already, so Huang Shaotian had disregarded him as a competitor. But that was when he killed a monster and wanted to check his score, only to be met with Lord Grim's name above his Troubling Rain's.

Am I seeing this correctly?

Huang Shaotian rubbed his eyes and after confirming what he had seen, immediately exploded in rage in the global chat.

Ye Xiu himself had noticed before him. This seaweed monster had managed to raise his points all the way to first place. He was also very surprised at that. Immediately, he thought of an idea of getting a bunch of smurfs to feed up a monster and then killing it with his main account, then noticed Huang Shaotian's yelling in the global chat.

"Ha." Ye Xiu replied.

None of the the players found anything out of the ordinary about this, but the pro players were all laughing their heads off by then.

Just now, in the pro player chat, didn't Zhou Zekai give the same response when Huang Shaotian had been trash talking after being overtaken by Zhou Zekai? Now Ye Xiu was copying Zhou Zekai. Huang Shaotian was probably choking on his anger by now. The global chat in the game had a message cooldown, so he couldn't spam. Instead, the pro player chat was flooded by him.

Seeing the number of new messages jumping rapidly, Ye Xiu knew that it had to be Huang Shaotian erupting again, as well as those who were greeting him despite knowing that he was just trash talking. Ye Xiu was thinking about the possibility of raising a monster. The only thing he wasn't sure about was how many characters he'd have to feed to a monster to get it to grow to this level. Was an experiment necessary?

Ye Xiu thought about this as he had Lord Grim climb back onto the bank. On the bank, the team of players stood there, stunned. After the trash talk in the global chat, they also realized that Lord Grim had managed to jump to first place. The sheer number of points the seaweed monster was worth was clear for all to see. Even though they wouldn't have as many gains after the points were distributed amongst them, it would still be quite heft. But now, it was all for nothing. Everyone was disappointed, but what could they say when faced with God Ye Xiu?

"So amazing, God!"

"God, are you leaving?"

"Don't rush off, God…"

The players fawned over Lord Grim like a paparazzi.

Chapter 1100: Raised Monsters

"Raise them?"

Ye Xiu couldn't do his monster raising plan alone. He needed to coordinate with his guild for this to work. Directly asking guild members to sacrifice themselves was somewhat inhumane, so he would need to rely on his alternate accounts to complete the task.

Ye Xiu was just about to discuss with Wu Chen how exactly they should carry this out, but Wu Chen already replied back: "This isn't going to be easy."

"Why?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I've already tried it. The base value of a ghost is 100 points. If the ghost kills a player, it's value will increase by 1. Let's put aside issues like manpower and account cards on hand. Let's just look at the problem with the ghost killing players. If a player doesn't wear any armor and doesn't defend, a ghost will need 10 or 20 seconds to kill the player. Killing 100 players is equal to 100 more points. If we average it out and say 15 seconds per person. 100 players would need 25 minutes. Of course, the ghost having the ability to attack en masse and killing faster the stronger it grows are factors, but if you consider the issue of the possible risks involved and our current manpower, raising a monster won't be an easy task." Wu Chen explained.

"Oh, understood." Ye Xiu replied. As soon as he heard that a single player killed was only worth one more point, he knew that it wouldn't be easy to make this work for the current Happy. Putting aside the calculations that Wu Chen made, finding enough manpower would require a lot of effort. He didn't have enough on hand. The Internet cafe customers had account cards, but who was going to help him for no reason? Especially since all of the Glory players were all busy with this event too. As a result, his only option would be to hire people. With Happy's current resources, he could afford it, but was that worth it just for this event?

Ye Xiu calculated, but then he felt that something wasn't right. When he had killed that seaweed monster, Lord Grim had obtained 625 points. It had already killed 525 players? It had only been an hour since the event had started. It didn't conform with Wu Chen's calculations. How did this seaweed monster do it? Could it be that its original value was high? It had started out as a mini-boss level ghost? The event never said anything about that though!

Ye Xiu was pondering over this mystery, when he saw a team of players from the far end of the street charging over. He recognized the person in front, Samsara's guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths.

When this team reached the bridge, they hastily looked towards the water beneath the bridge. In that instant, Ye Xiu realized something. As for Three Realms Six Paths, the instant he saw Lord Grim, he stopped looking under the bridge and shouted: "FUCK YOU!!!"

"Uh... you guys raised it?" Ye Xiu said.

He figured it out. This monster that had eaten 525 players hadn't grown naturally. It had been intentionally raised by people. Ye Xiu hadn't been the only one to think of raising a monster. Just look at Wu Chen. Wu Chen had already tested it before Ye Xiu had even asked. He had clearly noticed that there was a potential exploit. As for the other guilds, their in-game experience was far richer than pro players, so they had noticed it too. Those guilds had the manpower and the accounts to carry out something Happy couldn't. As a result, raising a monster seemed to be an obvious course of action.

Samsara had tried, and the ghost that they found was quite a good one.

This seaweed monster had weak defense and low health. It seemed to be a feature that all ghosts in the Ghost Parade had in common. But apart from that, it had powerful attacks and the scattered seaweed clumps could attack many players at once, making it a ghost perfect for growing quickly.

Even though it had been raised…...

"Why didn't you have anyone guard it?" Ye Xiu raised an honest question. What had just happened was one of the "potential risks" that Wu Chen had mentioned. Ye Xiu had just taken away all of the effort that Samsara had put into the ghost, yet now he was giving them a suggestion.

Three Realms Six Paths wanted to cry.

Why wasn't anyone guarding it? They obviously had people in the beginning, but as the seaweed monster became stronger, players started coming over and becoming its food. That was a cherry on top for Samsara, so not only did they not stop them, they welcomed them! As a result, the guards felt like there was no need to watch over it. They might as well just become its food and make it grow faster.

Lord Grim just happened to pass by and get caught by the seaweed monster. He just happened to be an unspecialized too, allowing him to kill the seaweed monster alone because of his multi-class skill set. After Samsara saw Troubling Rain cursing in the global chat, they realized something wasn't right. They didn't know if other guilds were raising monsters, but they were doing it. Three Realms Six Paths immediately asked the players stationed there whether the seaweed monster was safe and sound, but the team guarding the seaweed monster had sacrificed themselves and were on their way back, so when Three Realms Six Paths asked, they kept stalling.

Three Realms Six Paths suddenly had a bad feeling and personally went over. The others were still checking under the bridge, but Three Realms Six Paths immediately noticed that Lord Grim was on the bridge. Lord Grim had suddenly gained 600 points in one go and jumped to first place. The seaweed monster that we had painstakingly raised had been snatched away by this fucker?

Three Realms Six Paths felt bitter! But after cursing "Fuck you", he couldn't say anything more.

How could he blame Ye Xiu? He couldn't because Ye Xiu had already started scolding him justly and forcefully: "You have to watch over it!! You guys raised such a terrifying monster. Who knows how many innocent players were harmed? I almost died too! You've gotta be more careful next time!"

NEXT TIME?! This bastard was thinking of a next time??

If this were someone else, Three Realms Six Paths would have had called everyone over to blast this guy to smithereens. But it had to be Ye Xiu….. It wasn't like he revered Ye Xiu. It was a question of whether they could actually beat him. He didn't have that many people on his side, and all of them had been "food". They had lost a lot of experience and had no equipment on them. If they actually tried to fight him, they would probably be the ones getting eaten, no?

Three Realms Six Paths grit his teeth, but he could only swallow his anger. They could only blame themselves for being too greedy, wanting to use other passerbiers as fodder. If they had made their guards stay to watch over it, their guards could have warned other people not to come over. They could have at least warned a dangerous fellow like Ye Xiu... fuck, would he have left just because they warned him? In reality, Three Realms Six Paths didn't think so. The purpose of a guard wasn't to warn people. Was a warning going to stop other people? When was the Heavenly Domain ever so peaceful? Especially between the club guilds.

There were no grounds to argue with him. What's more, he didn't even know. Have him pay? Three Realms Six Paths wasn't naive enough to say that. This time, he could only take the blow and watch as Lord Grim marched out magnanimously. As for the food, they were standing on the bridge, staring blankly at the clean river water.

He obviously needed to tell the pro team what had happened because Three Realms Six Paths had already told them that they were raising a big monster for the pros to come get the points. But now, there was nothing. He had to at least tell them.

Samsara wasn't the only one raising monsters. Clubs had their own dedicated in-game divisions. How could they not do any research towards this event? After looking at the rules, the club guilds had already been planning on doing this way before the event even started. It was just that they didn't know the specifics yet. When the even started and they tested it, they found out that one death was only one point. Such miniscule gains only allowed these guilds to gather enough manpower to raise a single big monster. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim suddenly jumping to first wasn't anything too surprising. Even though Huang Shaotian had been cursing in the global chat, he also understood.

However, why did Happy kill it so early? Why did Happy kill their raised monster so fast?

The rather innocent people thought in this way. However, some people thought of the storm that Ye Xiu always brought up wherever he went and guessed something very close to the truth: he hadn't stolen someone else's monster, did he?

As a result, in that instant, it wasn't just Three Realms Six Paths checking on the situation. The various guild leaders were all asking about their raised monsters. Unfortunately, it was only Samsara with the grievous news.

The other guilds heard that their raised monsters were safe and sound. They instantly felt their hearts relax. However, in the end, they were also curious about whether a guild had gotten unlucky or not.

It wasn't hard to find out. They didn't even need to put their spies to use. Someone directly asked about in the guild leader chat group.

"I say… did Lord Grim steal someone's monster?" The first to speak was Tyrannical Ambition's Jiang You. As Excellent Era's old rival in the past, Tyranny always analyzed Ye Xiu from the worst way possible.

When Jiang You asked, the other curious guild leaders didn't need to ask. They simply replied with a "Not ours."　

In the end, Three Realms Six Paths typed out a sad face. Everyone saw it and immediately understood.They rejoiced in their hearts, but they put on a fake smile and consoled him: "Oh no, how could you be so careless?"

How could Three Realms Six Paths not know how happy these guild leaders were, but he really needed to speak his mind right now. These competitors of his were quite good listeners too.

After hearing Three Realms Six Path's tragic story, everyone naturally consoled him. Even though hadn't done it intentionally, with their impression of Ye Xiu, they weren't going to defend him. They could only look at him through an evil lens.

"That guy definitely knew!"

"Yeah, it was so obvious. How could he have not!"

"What a terrible person!"

"The scum among Gods!"

"Everyone's got to be more careful!"

As they chatted, the guild leaders ordered their monster raising team: "Be on high alert, especially against Lord Grim and anyone from Happy! Samsara too!"

Don't look at how everyone seemed to sympathizing with Three Realms Six Paths. In reality, they treated him the same as Ye Xiu. They looked at him in the worst way possible too. Samsara's raised monster was gone. Would they try to steal someone else's? Everyone had thought of this issue.

And at the same time, this exchange had let everyone realize that raising monsters wasn't something that they alone were doing. All of the guilds were doing the same. Then….. Where were they? If they could be stolen, they they had to try!

As a result, in an instant, the spies and open accounts of the various guilds started moving.

Chapter 1101: Revival Point

While the various guilds pondered how to steal the monsters raised by other guilds, they certainly wouldn't forget to protect their own. Each of them sent extra players to stand guard over their own monsters.

After receiving news from guild leader Changing Spring, Blue River sighed. Another round of deception and scheming was beginning again… how tiring! Nowadays, Blue River no longer led teams. He preferred to serve as an ordinary guild player, just fighting wherever he was told. But there was an overabundance of players willing to do such work in the game; Blue River was more valued for his ability to lead and manage teams. Changing Spring understood and respected Blue River's state of mind, but faced with the current situation, he still highly valued Blue River's ability, and ultimately sent Blue River to organize patrols at the revival points of each city.

Revival points!

These were unavoidable for the guilds raising monsters. Even if they brought Clerics with the Revive skill, Revive's cooldown was thirty minutes, not to mention that there was a limit on how many times in a row a player could be revived. It would be impossible to rely on Revive to seamlessly continue the process of raising a monster. Because of this, during this process, there would inevitably be players travelling from the revival point to feed themselves to a monster. And these players had a distinguishing characteristic: in order to quicken the process, they often wouldn't wear any equipment.

Blue River quickly understood this point and began to direct his subordinates.

Changing Spring gave him three five-man teams. Including Blue River himself, that made 16 people in total. There was a reason for this number - there were 32 cities in the Heavenly Domain, and therefore 32 revival points. 16 people meant that each person was responsible for two cities. After Changing Spring finished distributing the troops, he began to take action.

Kansas City was one of the two cities for which Blue River was responsible. By the time he arrived at the city, Blue River had already switched to another account. His main account Blue Bridge Spring Snow was a well-known figure in-game and attracted much attention, so he couldn't use it for covert operations like this. Now that he switched to an alt, Blue River tried to lie low, picking roads that weren't frequented by many people as he quickly made his way to the revival point.

Once he was close, Blue River stopped.

A good deal of time had passed since the start of the event, and the guilds must have reached a steady rhythm in raising the monsters. If Blue River stayed here for a while, he was sure that he would make some discovery. The guilds had to be efficient, so they wouldn't be raising the monsters somewhere in the deep mountains and forests - too much time would be wasted travelling.

Blue River hid his character behind a corner of a wall. Because there was an event going on, there were more players online than usual. In addition, the inherent difficulty of Ghost Parade made the death count high. There was a constant stream of players emerging from the revival point. Every time the white light flashed at the revival point, Blue River tensed. At the same time, he closely observed the players and his surroundings, and he discovered that there were several other players nearby doing the same thing that he was! Some were ducking this way and that as they furtively looked around, while others merely waited casually by the revival point as if they were meeting up with someone. Blue River turned his camera, studying his surroundings, and sent a message to Changing Spring, advising him to conceal their tracks carefully. Blue Brook Guild definitely wasn't the only guild that had sent players to watch the revival points.

"How many did you find?"

Just when Blue River sent the message, he suddenly heard a voice from right beside him, startling him so badly that he burst into a cold sweat and instinctively directed his character to roll to the side and unsheathe his sword. But once he finished the roll and saw the other player's name, he faltered.

Lord Grim!

What kind of luck was this?

Blue River felt like he was going crazy.

32 cities. 1 in 32 chance. Yet despite the odds, he still ran into this difficult guy. And this guy had just directly approached him! Was Blue River exposed?

No… no, he shouldn't have, this must be a coincidence because Blue River had been very careful, choosing the most cautious and secure route here. And this guy wasn't even using an alt, he was directly using Lord Grim, so of course he would be taking the quieter roads as well. So for the two characters to meet here like this, it could be considered an inevitable coincidence.

Blue River steadied himself. And then… and then without waiting for him to say anything, the other side had already asked, "Which guild are you?"

I've been seen through...

Blue River felt regret. Even though he wasn't using an account with the guild tag, in this current situation, who could fool anyone? Hadn't Blue River just sent a message to Changing Spring to warn Blue Brook Guild to be more careful?

"I'm in… Herb Garden." Even though Blue River was sick of this sort of deception, with things as they were now, he still had to play this game. He didn't have a plan in mind, but concealing his identity was a basic first step. With this easy lie, Blue River allied himself with Blue Brook Guild's death rivals, Herb Garden.

"Oh, how despicable, you're trying to steal the monsters that other people raised?" Ye Xiu said.

"Aren't you doing the exact same thing?" Blue River felt like coughing blood as he replied. It'd been a while since he'd seen him, and the great God was still as shameless as ever!

"Haha, I've actually already stolen one, you want to guess how I did it?" Ye Xiu said.

"How did you do it?" That caught Blue River's attention. Was the God about to reveal some sort of ultimate technique?

"I was just passing by and picked it up. How lucky!" As Ye Xiu spoke, he sent a thumbs up emoji to float above Lord Grim's head.

Blue River resisted the urge to stab him, and laughed dryly. "Lucky indeed."

"Did you discover anything here?" Ye Xiu then asked.

"Not yet." Blue River's reply was automatic, but once the words left his mouth, he regretted it. Why was he telling him anything?

"There, there, and there, there, those are all guild alts, right?" Lord Grim lifted his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, pointing in several directions as he spoke.

"Should be," Blue River said.

"If all the guilds continue like this, what do you think will happen in the end?" Ye Xiu said.

Blue River stared blankly...

The actions of the various guilds were too predictable. If it were really just one or two or three guilds sending people to monitor the revival points, they probably wouldn't be exposed. But now, however many guilds there were, that was how many people there were. With that many people loitering about the revival point, it'd be very difficult for them all to conceal themselves. If they discovered each other like this, they'd send news to their own guilds, and then… and then of course the players who were sent to be food for the monsters would disguise their identities by putting on equipment and what not so that they would be harder to recognize.

At that point, in order to tell if a player was food, then you'd have to check their stats. Repeatedly dying in-game would cause their stats to drop drastically. But checking another player's stats was much more of a hassle. Blue River's current hiding place was far enough away from the revival point that he couldn't see the stats of the players appearing there, so if he wanted to check, he'd have to go closer. But if he did that, then it'd be obvious that he was monitoring the revival point. If the opponents were really in this city, and they discovered him doing this, then what would they do?

Blue River was still thinking when he saw a person's shadow pass by him. He glanced and saw that Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had actually just walked right out there. He boldly stood at the exact center of the revival point, turning this way and that, surveying all of the revived players.

This guy, he's already just doing that!

Blue River was dumbfounded, and his mind rapidly ran through calculations. If he were in charge of raising a boss, and suddenly received news that Lord Grim was sitting at the city's revival point, what would he do?

He would certainly pause the feeding process.

And then… and then things would be difficult! Taking direct action against Lord Grim would be akin to admitting that yes, our guild's boss is right near here. Even if they were able to kill Lord Grim, he would certainly come back. The revival point was unavoidable, and moving the monster elsewhere was even more unrealistic. Would they have to send a special team to protect the players who were being fed to the monster? Then that would just attract all of the other guilds to attack them! And considering that the monsters were ultimately being raised to be fed to professional characters, it was very likely that the attackers would be the gods of the various teams! That was a terrifying thought! No, it couldn't be allowed to come to that.

Just thinking about this all was enough to get Blue River sweating. And so he decided, if he were trapped here by Lord Grim waiting at the revival point, the safest plan would be to just sacrifice a little time. Lord Grim had no reason to wait at this revival point forever if nothing happened, and the feeding could resume once he left.

As Blue River thought this, another character appeared at the revival point, and this time, Lord Grim fixed his sight on this one character.

Was that...

Blue River jolted. He was too far away, but he saw that once this character noticed Lord Grim, he also immediately stopped moving. Blue River had a feeling that this was the person they were hoping to find.

Which guild was still bold enough to continue sending players?

Blue River wondered. He didn't consider himself especially smart, so he figured that any issue that he could think of, the other guilds absolutely would have realized as well. When there was someone so domineering monitoring the revival point, there really shouldn't be any reason for someone to expose themselves like this! But as soon as he thought that, Blue River suddenly realized, there was one situation where that could happen, which was… the guild didn't know that there was someone so bold at this revival point.

The guilds had only just started to mobilize, and then monitored and investigated each other. When the plans couldn't keep up with changes, there would inevitably be mistakes. This guild member was wearing equipment, which showed that their guild had realized that everyone was spying on each other. But they hadn't yet sent their own people to monitor all of the revival points, so there was a hole in the reports they received. They just inferred the condition of this revival point from what they knew about the other revival points. And so, they put on equipment and boldly continued, only to find that there was an anomaly at this revival point.

Were they overconfident?

Of course they were. But then again, aside from Ye Xiu, who else could be this domineering?

Blue River ultimately felt that this guild was just unlucky, very unlucky that Ye Xiu came to their city and dragged the fox by the tail out of its den.

"Kansas City, a guild is raising a monster, the situation right now is unclear." Blue River immediately sent a report to his guild.

As for the player at the revival point, once discovered by Ye Xiu, he obviously wouldn't lead him to where the monster was being raised. This alt just directly logged off.

"Looks like we'll have a lot to do here." Lord Grim walked over and spoke to Blue River.

We? Blue River wondered. Since when was there a "we" in this?

Chapter 1102: Who’s Raising this One?

Blue River had sent his message, but the members from other guilds, who were who were also clustered around the revival point, weren't slow either. Kansas City's teleportation formation was soon bustling with people sent by each of the big guilds. It didn't matter who was raising the monster, only where it was located.

There were guildless alts, as well as many famous guild elites that were easily recognizable even without their guild tag. These people met each other at the teleportation formation, but quickly went their separate ways. However, after going their ways, they didn't forget to send people to spy on one another.

Kansa City was soon filled with a jumble of different people ,and Blue River also received a message from Changing Spring, telling him and the other teams from Blue Brook to regroup.

"Understood." Receiving the message, Blue River immediately headed for the coordinates Changing Spring had sent. However, he had only taken a few steps before realizing something was wrong and turned to look.

"What are you doing, following me?"

"Hm? Haven't your people from Herb Garden arrived?" Ye Xiu asked.

"What does that have to do with you?" Blue River yelled.

"Don't you need a powerful helper like me?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Haha, of course we welcome powerful helpers, but not you." Blue River laughed coldly. Did this guy still think he could take advantage of them after so long?

　

"Is that so? What a shame. I'll be off then," Ye Xiu said, a shrug emoji appearing above Lord Grim's head as he turned to leave.

Blue River watched him go, but soon realized that the scouts from the other guilds hadn't left the revival point. Their gazes were all locked onto one character: Lord Grim. Soon enough, they all began to head in the same direction that Lord Grim went.

Blue River suddenly came to a realization.

There was no way they could let a dangerous person like Lord Grim go unwatched. He had brought on the current situation, so why wouldn't he have tricks up his sleeve?

Of course he would!

This guy definitely had some sort of scheme. They couldn't be careless; they had to keep an eye on him.

Thinking of this, Blue River hurriedly had his alt follow as he sent a message to Changing Spring: "I'm not coming anymore. I'm keeping an eye on Lord Grim."

"!!!" Changing Spring, who didn't like chatting through messages, used three exclamation marks to express his emotions.

"Yes, he's here. He's also the one who leaked that there was a monster located here." Blue River explained.

Chang Spring didn't dare be even a little careless, immediately turning to order the other members of the guild. "We need another three teams in Kansas City."

"Three teams! Is that necessary!?" Someone objected. "Stealing raised monsters is just to get some points, but it's also very important that we keep up with the event on a larger scale. Isn't it too risky to have so many elites focus on the raised monsters?"

"You're right." Changing Spring calmed himself immediately. "We need to keep a balance. We don't need three. One team will be enough."

Ye Xiu, Lord Grim. Just the name could cause a guild leader to lose his cool at once. The trauma his presence had left on these people in the Heavenly Domain was clear as day.

What was he planning here?

It wasn't just Changing Spring wondering about this. He wasn't the only one allocating more people to Kansas City.

Kansas City suddenly became an important tactical point for them. They hadn't even found the raised monster, but were already on their highest guard against Lord Grim. During all of this, the situation in Kansas City brought a lot of attention. The guilds that hadn't check this city yet all heard of the unusual situation and quickly gathered people. This was almost like stealing a wild boss. The activities of guilds were obvious. This was because if you had few people, you wouldn't have a chance of winning, but if you had many, then it would be very hard to cover up your movements.

With this, the guilds fell into a very awkward situation.

Manpower!

How much manpower should they send?

For a wild boss, they would naturally have all the elites join in the fray, but now they had to consider a balance. They didn't want to waste their resources on this battle and affect the overall score of the guild in this event. It was just that different guilds had different ideas of balance. Some guilds would think one team was enough, others, three. That meant if they faced three teams with one team, they wouldn't have a winning chance.

Thus, the guilds looked for the monster as they scouted out the strength of the other guilds. After that, they would make the necessary adjustments. Most of their adjustments were to increase their numbers, because it wasn't just enough to have the same manpower as the others, but they had to be stronger. That way, they would have a better hold. Thus, if one side made adjustments, the other side would, too, then this side would notice and make more adjustments. Was there an end to this loop?

After sending two more teams to Kansas City, Tyrannical Ambition's Jiang You was the first to break. He jumped into the guild leader chat and sent a message. "Holy crap, are we planning to put all our manpower here?"

　　

"Where?" Someone asked.

Jiang You was about to type, but then stopped suddenly.

The one who asked was Blossom Valley's guild leader, Blooming Blossoms. Did Hundred Blossoms have any people in Kansas City yet? If they didn't, then wouldn't he give it away by speaking? Jiang You hurriedly looked back at his message history. He really couldn't recall if Hundred Blossoms had or not.

　

Yet soon enough, someone gave him an answer. Herb Garden's Arisaema replied, "Stop pretending, Blooming. Where do you think?"

"Haha, I'm just testing the waters. Is everyone here?" Blooming Blossoms said.

Jiang You wilted. The communication between them guild leaders never hid any good intentions. But, speaking of, since when did they start gathering to chat about things like this? They hadn't had this habit before; they would just scheme against each other in the past! Jiang You thought for a while until he saw someone mention a name in the chat.

Lord Grim!

That's right. It wasn't until after this guy appeared that their relationship had changed. Just this one person had managed to force these rival guilds to work together against a common enemy. He really was something! And this time, was this person here again? Tyrannical Ambition had been a little late to the game, so they didn't know Lord Grim's role in all of this, and Jiang You had only just gotten wind of his participation.

　

No wonder everyone was willing to talk about this together again! Could it be that everyone would be facing a dire situation whenever this guy appeared?

By now, all the guilds that could come had come to Kansas City, so there was no problem in openly discussing this. However, they had a problem to solve!

"Hey everyone…" Herb Garden's Arisaema spoke up, "The event is still ongoing and time is precious. Expending too much manpower and time on this isn't worth it. I suggest that we settle things peacefully for once and don't fight. Let's just use luck to decide this. Finders keepers, okay? This way, we won't have to endlessly put more resources into this.

"Good idea!" Someone immediately agreed.

"My ass!" Yet soon enough, someone objected. Curt and straightforward, it was Blue Brook's Changing Spring. It was impossible to have this guy type out and explain things clearly. It was a good thing that someone else had also thought of the same thing as him. Soon enough, the guild leader of Howling Heights, West Riding Wind said, "Hey, have you guys forgotten that this isn't a wild boss? This thing has an owner, and that owner is someone amongst us!"

　

Arisaema was stunned. He really had forgotten about that.

　

"Could it be Herb Garden's?" A guild leader immediately suspected. Though it didn't really matter, Arisaema's suggestion of a peaceful resolution, not adding more manpower, finders keepers was just too much of a benefit for the owner, causing people to immediately suspect them of being the owners.

"Tch…" Arisaema immediately acted uncaring, but was it real nonchalance or was it pretending? Like the whole question around who the owner of the monster was, this was unimportant as well, so no one bothered to press. It was just that after realizing the target they were acting against was amongst them, everything became awkward. No matter what they came up with, the defending side would be able to put in precautions against them all! Poor guy, though, having to discuss how to deal with himself with everyone else. That was pretty harsh!

"How troublesome…" Some people began to complain. They clearly had not an inkling of an idea as to how everyone should proceed.

　

"Who's monster is it? It's not like you can run with it anymore, just tell everyone already!" Someone yelled.

No one would own up to it, but this made many of the guild leaders realize something.

They couldn't run...

If the guild that was raising the monster also realized this, then what would they do?

Doubtlessly, kill it immediately!

"Quick, check the rankings, see if anyone's points just jumped," Some guild leaders swiftly gave the order.

But then, they thought things through again. What was the goal of raising monsters? To give them to the pro team. Even if Kansas City's raised monster was still rather small, it would still be better than a normal monster. If they were being forced to kill it, then they could also call people from the pro team over!

"Keep an eye on the teleportation formation, send people to the gates, take note of pro characters!" The new order immediately spread through the guilds. Each guild leader had about the same reaction speed to situations like this.

　

Pro characters!

This was key. If the other was forced to kill, then they had to call pro characters over. Pro characters, pro characters...

This order was swiftly relayed to everyone at Kansas City. Many people quickly replied to their guilds, "Pro characters? Does Lord Grim count?"

Lord Grim?

Damn!

Several of the guild leaders suddenly jumped up. Could it be that the monster being raised here belonged to Happy?

With that thought in mind, the guild leaders became excited. Always, it had been Happy giving them blow after blow, and them? They hadn't ever seemed to be able to manage to deal a painful strike back. This time, they finally had the chance. So it was Happy who was raising a monster in Kansas City?

Chapter 1103: Who?

"Happy!" Changing Spring ran excitedly to the chat group to type a message.　　

"What?" But his exclamation was too short. No one understand what he meant.

"Kansas City's monster should be Happy's! From our reports, the only pro character at Kansas City is Lord Grim. Does anyone else have information of any other pro characters there?" Another guild leader explained in Changing Spring's place.

Other pro characters? No, none.

"But… wasn't it Lord Grim who revealed this information?" Several guild leaders hadn't gone over their heads just because it might be Happy's. Misty Castle's Misty Lock asked.

"What?" The guild leaders had been very excited, but then they discovered that they seemed to have neglected an important detail.

How shameful!

It was such a stand-out logic, yet these grand guild leaders had unexpectedly neglected it. What a disgrace.

"So no matter who it belongs to, it can't be Happy's. Why would they invite trouble to themselves?" Misty Lock said.

"Or maybe it's some sort of scheme?" A guild leader was dead-set on it being Happy's.

"Scheme? What type of scheme requires one to reveal one's own raised monster?" Misty Lock was doubtful. Then, he saw a report come in on his QQ. He clicked on it.

"Our raised monster has been discovered!!"

"What? By who?" Misty Lock was shocked. It was too sudden.

"By Happy."

"Hold the fort." Misty Lock couldn't think too much. He could only give this reply. But before he could even get back to the game, a reply had already come: "We can't hold it!"　　

They were truly unable to hold it.

After news of a raised monster being exposed came out, the big guilds dispatched scouts to probe the situation, while they also increased their defenses and vigilance towards their own breeding cities. However, at this moment, outside of where Misty Castle's raised monster was located, every character there was from a pro team.

Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion, One Inch Ash, Deception, Little Cold Hands, Concealed Light, even….. Dancing Rain!

This was everyone in Team Happy apart from Lord Grim. Even though they were a new team, if they could beat Team Excellent Era, how could in-game elite troops be a match?　　

Misty Castle tried to form a defensive line in an attempt to stop them, but their defenses were instantly broken through. Happy's team headed straight for their raised monster. Misty Castle's most effective method of obstruction was probably their angry yells and curses.

A raised monster didn't have the same amount of health as a wild boss. In addition, no matter how long a monster was raised, it would always have a weakness. Ye Xiu hadn't taken long to kill a seaweed monster worth 625 points, let alone an entire team charging at one. Misty Castle's raised monster might be a bit stronger than Samsara's seaweed monster, but under the combined attack from a team of players, it died even faster than the seaweed monster.

"It's over….." Besides reporting to their guild leader, Misty Castle's players couldn't do anything else. They couldn't stop Happy's team from breaking through their defenses, let alone killing Happy's team. The monster, which they had spent close to two hours raising by sacrificing countless alternate accounts, was taken away by Happy just like that. Even though their guild was also working hard trying to steal other guild's monsters, they were still incredibly furious after getting theirs stolen away.

By the time Misty Lock returned to the game, everything was already over. He had no time to do anything.　　

What the hell?

Misty Lock now had plenty of time to ponder over what had just happened　　

His heart was in chaos. Even though he had the time, he wasn't in the mood to ponder over this question. The guild leader chat group was still arguing over what Lord Grim was trying to do, exposing Kansas City like that.

Why?

Seeing the guild leaders repeatedly ask this question, Misty Lock suddenly realized something.　　

Could Lord Grim… be trying to divert their attention?

The guild leader chat group was in a fervent discussion. All of the guilds were focused on Kansas City. What about the other cities? It didn't seem like there was any information on the others. At least, Misty Castle didn't have any. But what about Happy? Not only had they found where Misty Castle's raised monster was located, they sent their pro team to kill it.

Was it Misty Castle being unlucky or could it be the start of Happy's scheme?

Misty Castle's intuition told him that it was the latter. Lord Grim revealing Kansas City not only diverted Misty Castle's attention, but all of the other guilds. No, it would be more precise to say that they weren't focused on Lord Grim, but rather the monster located in Kansas City. But who had first discovered this monster? Lord Grim.

Did Kansas City really have a raised monster? Misty Lock was starting to become suspicious of it. Their guild had searched for so long already, yet they hadn't found anything. What about the other guilds? They all seemed to be busy, but if they found anything, they wouldn't share it with anyone else. Even if they killed it, they might pretend like it hadn't been killed yet. Trying to confirm anything was very troublesome!

Misty Lock discovered that they seemed to have walked into an alleyway, starting from when Kansas City's monster had been revealed. Misty Lock was very doubtful that this alley would end up being a dead end, but he didn't have any plans of telling these doubts to anyone because his guild had already suffered. It hoped that the other guilds would also suffer too. Now that he no longer had a raised monster, he needed to steal someone else's. As for what exactly Happy was scheming, why couldn't Misty Castle take advantage of their scheme too?

Kansas City.

Blue River had been carefully following Lord Grim the entire time, going around and around the city. Lord Grim wasn't moving too fast because whenever he saw a ghost, he would go kill it. He wasn't very focused on searching for raised monsters.

Blue River understood the reason very well.

Ye Xiu had previously done everything on his own because Happy didn't have the conditions for it. Now that Happy had grown, even if it couldn't compare to the powerhouses yet, it wasn't so small anymore that God Ye Xiu had to personally do everything. If Lord Grim had truly been focused on searching for raised monsters, Blue River would have been suspicious. But Ye Xiu prioritizing killing monsters, while also scouting around in the passing was reasonable. It was very reasonable.

There were no signs showing that Lord Grim was doing anything unusual, but Blue River always had an uneasy feeling in his heart. His intuition told him that he was definitely missing something.

Blue River replayed over and over everything that Lord Grim had done today including all of the small details.

Suddenly, his cellphone rang.

Blue River checked his cellphone. To his surprise, it was Changing Spring.　

Blue River's expression changed. Changing Spring could have easily contacted him online. He could even see that both Changing Spring was online both in the game and on QQ. Instead, he chose to make a phone call, meaning that he had something very important to say. This was because this guy refused to change his habit of not liking to type. If there was something important to say, he would always choose to make a phone call.

"Hello?" Blue River picked up the phone.

"Our raised monster has been stolen by Happy."

That was the first sentence he heard.

"How? Impossible!" Blue River whispered. He could still see Lord Grim from his screen, "Lord Grim is still on this side."

"Lord Grim didn't go, but the others in Team Happy went." Changing Spring said.

"The others…"

"Yeah, everyone else in Team Happy apart from Lord Grim."

"..." Blue River didn't know what to say.

"What is Lord Grim doing right now?" Changing Spring asked.

"The same as always. Wandering around while occasionally killing monsters." Blue River said.

"He obviously knew what his team was doing, but he was still idly killing monsters. There must be a scheme in this." Changing Spring was exasperated.

Blue River stared blankly. His mind was a mess. He had replayed all the events that had happened today with Lord Grim, but he still wasn't able to find the important point.

"Does Kansas City have a raised monster or not? We've been searching for so long!" Changing Spring shouted.

"Of course, there's one... I've personally seen that character….." Blue River said, but then he suddenly stopped.

"What about that character?" Changing Spring heard the hesitation.

"I feel like I've seen that character before….." Blue River tried hard to search his memories, but his deepest impression of this character was that he had a dark red status. This was the main point he had noticed because he had tried to determine how much experience this character had lost based on his lowered stats to see whether he was a feeder or not.

"What's his name?" Changing Spring asked.

"Backside Attack... Where have I seen him before?" Blue River thought hard.

"Backside Attack?" Changing Spring was even more puzzled than Blue River. However, the number of people at his disposal was more than just himself. He immediately had the entire guild reflect on this name.

Sure enough, the collective knowledge of the guild was boundless. Soon afterwards, an upper level player from Blue Brook Guild pointed out: "He used to be from our Blue Brook Guild. There was this one boss fight where they and Ye Xiu ripped us off. Did you forget, guild leader?"

Changing Spring suddenly thought to himself.

Changing Spring remembered quite clearly that time's fight for the Level 65 wild boss Swamp Hunter Leipu. Apart from Ye Xiu participating and extorting them, more importantly, he had talked with one character, the character called Windward Formation. At that time, Windward Formation had been a part of Blue Brook Guild, but because of an incident, Changing Spring kicked him out. After that, he found out that Windward Formation was unexpectedly Team Blue Rain's former captain. How could he forget about that experience?

As for this Backside Attack, he didn't have much of an impression of him. But with this reminder, Changing Spring understood that this guy must be together with Windward Formation, together with Ye Xiu.

Everything has come to light…...

The so-called feeder had been from Happy. As for those distinctly lowered stats, it wasn't just Changing Spring even Blue River got up. After that boss battle, that group of players had been attacked by all of the guilds and they annoyed everyone for a long period of time. But they were just purely annoyances. In terms of actual combat, those guys weren't their opponents. In the end, all of them lost a lot of experience.

And now, this type of trash account was being used by Ye Xiu and it was being used well too.

All of the guilds were focused on Kansas City. And at this moment, their rears were being wiped by Team Happy. A team... a pro team.

Chapter 1104: Leaderboard Dominance

Changing Spring's target shifted back to the guild leader chat group, where everyone was trying to cheat each other.

He wasn't someone who liked to chat through typing, so after there was nothing really important being talked about, he stopped paying attention to the group.

The guild leader chat group suddenly became quiet at some point. If one looked through the chat log, guild leaders talked less and less as time went on. Something urgent seemed to have happened and every guild leader suddenly left the discussion, one by one. Up until the end, one of the sentences was left hanging as if it had suddenly been cut off.

No way!

The strangeness in the chat group made Changing Spring realize that the tragedy of getting their raised monster stolen wasn't unique to just Blue Brook Guild. Where did those guild leaders, who suddenly stopped chatting, go? Could they all have received emergency alerts, reporting that their guild's wild boss was being stolen?

They couldn't all have been Happy, right?　

Thinking of this point, Changing Spring suddenly felt frightened.

How? Their guilds had been searching for the raised monsters of other guilds the entire time. Even if they had focused more of their attention on Kansas City, they hadn't relaxed their searches for monsters in other cities. Why? Why was Guild Happy so efficient? How did they find out where every raised monster was located?

"What information do we have on Guild Happy?" Changing Spring couldn't help but turn his head and ask one of his subordinates.

"Happy? Information?" This subordinate stared blankly, "None."

"None?"

"We don't have enough manpower. Everyone's busy searching in the other cities for raised monsters!" The subordinate reported.　　

Changing Spring suddenly froze.

He suddenly realized something. Happy had found these raised monsters so efficiently through a certain method.　

It was very simple: send a message in the guild and have everyone in the guild pay attention for any powerful monsters.

Why didn't the other guilds employ such a simple method?

One word: slow.

The guilds had moved too slowly. From when Lord Grim suddenly jumped to number one on the leaderboards to the guild leaders trying to cheat each other in order to set their own plans in motion. They figured that they had to be discreet, so that the others wouldn't figure out their plans.　

In reality? Unnecessary! It was completely unnecessary. In this sort of situation, which guild wouldn't want to steal other people's monsters. Wasn't it pointless to hide their intentions from one another?

The guild had been thinking too much. Not only did they want to take advantage of others, they were also afraid to take losses, so they hoped to catch the others off guard and kill them in one go. They didn't want to encounter a well-prepared defense.

But it turned out that if everyone was being sneaky, no one was being sneaky. Everyone's intentions were laid bare in the end. Despite having reached this step, their thoughts still hadn't changed. They still hadn't thought of directly getting their entire guild involved in the search. News of just a single Kansas City had made them excited enough to all start chatting about it.

Ha, what a joke.

Changing Spring actually laughed out loud.　　

While their chat group had been bickering about Kansas City, everyone in Happy had already mobilized for who knew how long already. Happy might have already found all of their monsters' locations by that time.

The guilds had tried to catch each other off guard and do things in secret. Guild Happy, on the other hand, brandished their swords for everyone to see, directly calling out to everyone in the guild. And the outcome? Happy's large-scale movements actually became secretive, completely catching the other guilds off guard.

Because they had to act discreetly, they needed trustworthy helpers. The guild spies were naturally trustworthy, so with them temporarily being assigned elsewhere, there were no spies left, leaving them unaware of Happy's movements.

Was it their stupidity that allowed Happy's plan to work beautifully, or was it Ye Xiu guessing that they would act stupidly? Changing Spring didn't know. The silence in the chat group let him know that their guilds had paid the price for their stupidity. After having waged war with each other for so long, it was as if they were now all carved from the same mold. Changing Spring once again couldn't help but laugh.

In the chat group, someone had finally discovered how abnormal the chat group felt and typed in chat, breaking the ice.

"Happy." Herb Garden's Arisaema typed just one word.

Emojis followed one after the other.

Petrified…

Sweating....

Anger…

Fuming...　　

Sadness….

(Replace these with QQ emojis for better effects)　　

Everyone suddenly had a gut feeling that there was an 80-90% chance that everyone had been duped by Happy. Whether or not someone had escaped from Happy's clutches was no longer their concern.

Everyone ran to check the leaderboards.

Everyone had been checking it constantly. If someone had instantly shot up like Lord Grim had, they would have definitely noticed it. No one had noticed anything when Happy had cleaned up another raised monster because it was Happy's team that went. Lord Grim killing the seaweed monster alone gave him 625 points, which would obviously make him shoot up the leaderboard. The seaweed monster was equivalent to killing 6 monsters, but for Happy's team, since the points were divided amongst everyone, the point increase wasn't as big. These ups and downs happened all the time in the leaderboards. It was nothing particularly noteworthy.

They hadn't noticed Team Happy's rise in the leaderboards until they, who were originally at who knew where, had squeezed into the top 200, top 100, top 50, top 30 rankings. And from this, they realized that Happy hadn't stolen just one raised monster.

Misty Castle's raised monster had been stolen first, but instead of telling others, Misty Lock had kept it a secret. Now, the fruits of their efforts had been reaped. Even though Misty Castle lost their raised monster, seeing the other guilds suffer lifted Misty Lock's mood. And relatively speaking, the earlier a raised monster was stolen, the smaller the losses were.

After these emojis were spammed, the chat group returned to silence. No one knew what to say. Condemn Happy? Condemn Ye Xiu? Everyone was dealing with shady business. The only difference was that Happy had succeeded and they had failed. Condemning Happy or Ye Xiu was the same as slapping their own faces.

This time, the guild leaders didn't explode in fury amidst this silence. They simply left. They told the unfortunate news to their teams. The teams didn't criticize them too excessively either. It was just that, after Happy had swept their pots clean, sending their characters up the leaderboards, the outcome was too stunning. Who knew how many pro characters had been left in the dust by them.　

On the leaderboards, of the first ten places, Team Happy had stolen away five spots, monopolizing the top three.

Lord Grim, Deception, Dancing Rain.

After those three, it was Huang Shaotian's Troubling Rain, who was spamming the pro player chat group in anger.　

At this point, there weren't many monsters left. Many players weren't able to find anymore. The fluctuations in the leaderboards became less and less frequent. Even though the system showed that there were still 21 ghosts left, the Heavenly Domain was so vast. Twenty one was too few. Many players didn't want to waste their time wandering around for a chance to encounter one. Some of them directly logged off, while others started doing their normal day to day routine.　

Most of Guild Happy's players had left to do their own things too. However, their most trusted members were all called together.

The play had come to an end and now it was time for the audience to go?

Ye Xiu didn't think so. He believed that the other club guilds didn't think so either. As the end neared, there were fewer and fewer monsters. As soon as a monster was discovered by a guild, that guild would certainly start raising it, and it would be easier to protect too. After all, the event could practically be considered over already.

As a result, Ye Xiu had called Guild Happy's most loyal members and tasked them with watching revival points. If a guild was going to raise a monster, a revival point must be used. Watching a revival point would reveal their activities. At the same time, an announcement was made in the guild chat. Players who hadn't logged off yet should be mindful for any monsters, as well as movements from the other guilds.

For normal players, the event had ended, but for the club guilds, it was just the beginning. The remaining targets might be the key to their comeback on the leaderboards. These 21 monsters became the deciding factors for their victory. The guilds were sending out their forces, searching or monitoring their competitors' movements. There weren't just Happy's players at the revival points. All of the parties involved had made arrangements.

It was just that this time, even with their enormous resources, they failed to make any progress.

21, 20, 19, 18…

The number of ghosts continued to decrease, but these ghosts were killed by players, who just happened to encounter one on accident.

Soon afterwards, announcements were made by the various guilds in the global chat: spend money to buy the location of these ghosts.

After one guild sent it, the other guilds followed suit. How could a club guild not afford these types of rewards? With everyone offering rewards, players either compared offers between several guilds or looked for the one they liked the most. The guild leaders didn't directly shout out an exact offer in the global chat. If not, if everyone kept raising the bar and entered a price war, when would it stop?

Although they were unwilling, in the end, midnight struck. The system announced that today's Ghost Parade was over. There were still 17 ghosts remaining, but when the system event ended, the system automatically removed them from the map.

Yes, after the guilds started offering rewards, no one managed to find any of the 17 remaining ghosts all the way until the system removed them. The leaderboards didn't change.

The drops from killing ghosts was one portion of the rewards for the event. The other rewards came from leaderboard rewards. The leaderboards were split into daily rankings and overall rankings. The daily rankings would reset every day, while the overall rankings accumulated over the course of the event. When the day ended, the rewards could be given out. The rewards would obviously be given out according to the rankings on the leaderboards. There was no luck involved. Someone at a lower ranking wouldn't get better rewards than someone at a higher ranking.

An event was an event. Just killing ghosts gave good rewards. The leaderboard rewards were even more resplendent, especially the top ten rankings. The system publicly announced those in order to excite players. Five of Happy's characters, Troubling Rain, Cloud Piercer, Demon Subduer, and Peaceful Hermit received brilliant rewards.

Chapter 1105: Comprehensive Textbook

What was the significance of the leaderboard?

Most directly, of course, it was that the system used to distribute rewards. Even the club guilds couldn't disregard these extremely valuable rewards, so they too actively strove for the top spot.

Aside from this, the leaderboard was also a way of proving the strength of an individual or a guild. An in-game event like Ghost Parade was partially based on luck, but when the top of the leaderboard was entirely occupied by pro level accounts, it was clear that luck only mattered when skill levels were similar. In front of the crushing power of pro players, no matter how good an ordinary player's luck was, he simply couldn't compete with the raw skill of the pros.

The club guilds paid close attention to leaderboards, whether it was for the first wave of dungeon records for new servers, the records for the highest-level dungeons, or the rankings for in-game events. The rewards were part of the motivation, but aside from that, ranking higher meant showing off their strength and expanding the influence of the team.

The pro teams relied on their performance during the season to demonstrate their strength, but the club guilds, their representatives in-game, were a presence closer to home. Unlike pro players, the guilds didn't exist in a separate space; they existed right alongside the numerous ordinary Glory players.

Expanding the team's influence through activities in-game was one of the most important jobs for every club guild. And the leaderboard was the main battlefield for all of this.

Thus, after the first day of the Night of a Hundred Ghosts leaderboard battle, the club guilds were unhappy. Very unhappy.

It had been a rare opportunity for the pros to mobilize in-game, but in the end, the various guilds had been unable to coordinate well with their respective pros. Ultimately, of the top 27 places, 9 were occupied by members of Guild Happy. They managed to steal a third of the top spots. Of the top 10 places, Happy had snatched 5. First, second, and third place, Happy dominated, not leaving a single chance for the other guilds.

The big guilds discovered that they had never tasted such a victory before.

This result was a lively topic of discussion in the pro player group as well, after Huang Shaotian's angry spamming, of course. Happy's elegant victory had earned even their respect. And, from the reports of their guilds, they essentially understood how Happy managed to pull it all off.

Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and the others still hadn't joined the pro player group; from Happy, only Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng were in here. Ye Xiu was obviously targeted from all sides. After Huang Shaotian's spam, everyone directed their spearheads toward Ye Xiu, half-jokingly calling him sneaky, dirty, treacherous.

"Hahaha," Ye Xiu laughed. "If you're jealous, then just say it directly!"

They had no words. They were all pro players, after all. They didn't need this leaderboard to prove themselves, and they didn't care too much about particular rankings. They did care about the earnings that came with each ranking, but aside from that, it was all for fun. Would they really be jealous over something like this?

"Jealous my ass you fucker you fucker you fucker!!" Huang Shaotian responded instantly, chaining together so many swear words that it seemed like endless echoes.

System: Troubling Rain has been kicked out of [Glory Pro Players] by the group moderator.

Everyone sweatdropped. Several of the rookies in this group didn't even dare to say a word.

The mighty Sword Saint, Glory's number one Blade Master, was kicked out of the group just like that. Sure, this senior was very noisy, but if these rookies had been in Ye Xiu's place, none of them would have the courage to treat a God like that!

Was this the power of Glory's former king, God Ye Qiu?

This was the first time the rookies had really felt the power of this former king. After all, the retired Ye Xiu had been playing in the Challenger League during this past season, and hadn't surfaced in this group often. And now, the king made his grand return. In one move, he ruthlessly assassinated the noisy God Huang Shaotian.

How powerful! How tyrannical!

The rookies quietly admired God Ye Xiu and sympathized for God Huang Shaotian.

"Anyone else?!" Ye Xiu called.

"Childish!" In fact, someone did still have the courage to speak out. Everyone saw the name, Desert Dust - it was Han Wenqing, a rare participant in the group chat. Was it that only someone like God Ye Xiu could induce him to speak here? And was it that only he, who had toppled Excellent Era's dynasty, dared to directly call Ye Xiu out like this?

No!

Some seniors corrected the rookies. The main reason that Han Wenqing dared to confront Ye Xiu was that he, too, was a group moderator.

Moderators had no way of moderating each other, so neither feared the other. The reality was often this ordinary and boring.

"Then, what about the group owner?" one of the rookies asked. Only the group owner was more powerful than a moderator.

"Group owner? After joining this group, have you ever seen the owner?"

"No…"

"The group owner is a long-retired player and left this circle long ago. All we have left is this group."

"The group owner must have been a really incredible person," the rookies marveled.

"Eh, he was alright," was the response of the seniors. Because, in reality, this group-making senior really wasn't all that special. Of course, this person had made it to the Glory professional scene, one person out of millions of players - from that angle, he could be considered a remarkable person. However, comparing him to other pros, he really was a very ordinary person. He just made this group, that's all. There were no requirement necessary to do something as simple as that. Once again, the reality was disappointingly ordinary for the rookies.

"Ye Xiu, you bastard!" At this moment, Huang Shaotian crashed back into the group chat. His first sentence after returning was a shout at Ye Xiu. The rookies couldn't help but feel awe at Huang Shaotian's fearless spirit.

"I'll let you off for today," was Ye Xiu's indifferent response. After that, despite Huang Shaotian's provocations, he didn't say another word, having either muted the chat or gone offline.

The group had to wait a while for Huang Shaotian's ranting to subside. There was a moment where everyone thought, kicking out Huang Shaotian was actually pretty nice, why was he let back in?

Of course, these were just their thoughts. Kicking members, letting them back in, that was a battle for the moderators, a battle of gods. The rest of the ordinary members, no matter how important they might be in the pro sphere, were just insignificant little monsters in this group.

The group eventually quieted down, and everyone was finally able to discuss some more serious topics.

The pro players joked light-heartedly about Happy's huge victory today in the event, but in their hearts they were all shocked by the outcome.

They too had participated in this event; they too could direct their guilds to accomplish the tasks they wanted, but why couldn't they do what Ye Xiu had managed to accomplish?

"This guy, seriously…" One player wanted to talk about this, but couldn't find the proper words to express what he wanted to say.

"The Glory Textbook…" In the end, it was Xiao Shiqin who brought up Ye Xiu's long-time title. He then added, "An extremely comprehensive textbook."

"Xiao Shiqin, you faced off directly with Happy. How is their team, really?" someone asked.

"What do you all think?" Xiao Shiqin asked. Even though these people hadn't directly fought Happy, he knew that they had all paid close attention to Happy's players. Happy was really in the spotlight right now!

"Some of the players on that team really do have skill," said Lin Jingyan.

"Tang Rou?" Someone said. Indeed, Tang Rou, aside from Ye Xiu, was the most attention-grabbing member of Team Happy.

"A hot girl!"

"Yeah, when I saw that picture of her in Esports Home last time, I almost fell right in love!" Someone sent a rather shameless drooling emoji.

"It looks like you've already fallen in love?"

"You know, Happy really has a lot of hot girls!"

"Yeah, that's not fair!"

"Misty Rain's two new sisters aren't too bad looking either!"

"Twin flowers!" Drooling, it was the drooling emoji again.

"Could you all be any more despicable?" Finally, a table-slapping emoji - Chu Yunxiu of Team Misty Rain spoke up.

The group instantly fell dead silent.

In the eyes of the fans, the members of this group were refined, high-minded, all-powerful professionals, but in reality, they were just ordinary people who happened to be a little better at playing Glory. Like anyone else, they had normal thoughts and desires, good ones, bad ones, noble ones, dirty ones… Not to mention, this was a male-dominated world. So when a pretty female player was mentioned, it was inevitable that her gender and appearance would become the topic of discussion. Fortunately, Chu Yunxiu appeared at the right moment and cut short the vulgarity of this group of males.

"Tang Rou is an extremely outstanding player. It seems like lots of teams are interested in her, but in the end Happy was still able to hold on to her." The discussion quickly turned back on-topic.

"She's very strange, it's unclear what she wants…" Wang Jiexi said. He was the first to offer her an invitation, and was also the first to be confused by her desires. Honor? Status? Money? He couldn't figure out what would move her. These three things were the main motivations for most pro players!

After Wang Jiexi said this, Team Void's Li Xuan added, "Happy's Ghostblade is also pretty good! Wasn't that kid on your Tiny Herb before? Why'd you just let him go?"

"You're interested in him?" Wang Jiexi didn't directly answer Li Xuan because he knew Li Xuan wasn't really asking, it was just a casual comment. Every transfer period would have the transfers of good and even God-level players. Being a good player didn't guarantee that one would be able to remain a part of the team.

"Us? For now, no," Li Xuan said. But, he had said "for now." Void's Ghostblade Duo was still at their peak, they weren't yet ready to retire, so they didn't need another Ghostblade. However, did Li Xuan's "for now" suggested that Void already had an idea in mind?

"Did anyone pay attention to that Brawler in Happy?" Samsara's Jiang Botao suddenly spoke up, inserting himself into the conversation.

The group chat wasn't like a competition onstage. During a competition, everyone could just battle to their fullest without holding back, but communication in the group involved feelings. There was less talk between those that didn't know each other well, while veteran players who had interacted with each other more were much more familiar with each other, and thus tended to speak more. This was a normal pattern for any human interaction.

So, most of the time, veteran players took the initiative in conversations, while newer members of the group, even God-level players, found it difficult to open conversations in an unfamiliar setting, but this Jiang Botao was an exception to the rule - even though he couldn't really be considered an old player, he had integrated with the older players early on, and he was able to communicate naturally with all types of people.

"Oh, that guy, you noticed him too? What do you think?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"Don't know. I can't understand him." Jiang Botao said.

Chapter 1106: Event Easter Egg

The Gods certainly wouldn't overlook Steamed Bun's strength, but after a close investigation, they all shared the same thoughts as Jiang Botao: incomprehensible.

"His mechanics are pretty solid, but his decision-making is rather fleeting." Lin Jingyan commented as the most experienced Brawler player in the chat.

"That's what makes it incomprehensible!" Jiang Botao sighed.

"To quote Zhang Xinjie: an excessively random player." Lin Jingyan said.

"That sounds like something he would say." Li Xuan laughed. Zhang Xinjie was known for his strict manner, so randomness was his greatest enemy.

"All these assessments are very good! He is indeed very random, and his movements are very hard to predict. He doesn't seem to use his experience and fights by relying on some sort of innate instinct." Jiang Botao said.

"A natural destructor of balance." Wang Jiexi said.

"Were there any other players like him before?" Jiang Botao asked.

"Look at who typed before you." Lin Jingyan laughed.

"Uh… the Magician was never this random." Jiang Botao said.

"Is it because the Magician's innate instinct is more precise?" Lin Jingyan said.

"That's a pretty accurate explanation." Jiang Botao was in a worshipping state.

"But do you still have this kind of instinct now, Wang Jiexi?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"Would you like to see for yourself?" Wang Jiexi said.

"Haha, I wouldn't dare." Lin Jingyan laughed.

"What will Steamed Bun Invasion's future be like?" Jiang Botao sent another thinking emoji.

Wang Jiexi was able to help Tiny Herb win the championships because he had adjusted his playstyle. Steamed Bun didn't have the same talent as Wang Jiexi though. Could he continue to persist with such a random fighting style?

This kind of problem was difficult to answer, so the pro player chat fell silent. It was unknown what everyone was thinking. Perhaps it was about time for them to go to sleep…

The first day of Ghost Parade came to an end.

On the second day, the ghosts spawned again at the same time. However, some attentive players would notice that the number of ghosts that had spawned on the second day seemed to be greater than the first day.

Kill kill kill!

After gaining experience from day one, everyone no longer stumbled over fear before these weak ghosts. Although the ghosts had strong attacks, they had their own unique weaknesses. Even if the players couldn't fully grasp their weakness, everyone could just group up and help one another.

As for the big guilds? They no longer hid or stayed on the conservative side. The moment the event started, they publicly announced in the guild for everyone to take note of the existence of any raised monsters.

Raising was no longer a method in this type of environment, so all of the guilds gave up on this thought.

Since they no longer had any strategical confrontations, it was natural for the leaderboards to have rises and drops on a large scale because everyone's point totals were very close. Of course, the ones in the lead were the pro players. In the end, the ranking was no longer important because it depended on a person's luck and the number of mobs they were able to find.

Third day, fourth day, fifth day…...

The event progressed mundanely. The headstart the characters from Happy had achieved on the first day couldn't serve as a strong foundation. Their ranks fell in the overall ranking. After all, effort was useless in this case because luck was something that couldn't be explained.

The guild leaders of the big guilds finally let out a sigh of relief. They had been very worried if Ye Xiu had any demonic tricks up his sleeve. Now that a few days had passed, their hearts were at peace. They saw Lord Grim's rank fall from first to seventh in the current overall ranking, so all the guild leaders felt an unspeakable happiness from inside.

However, they were still unhappy with the player on the top of the list.

Deception!

Mo Fan's luck in the event for the past few days was pretty good. He was even able to pull a decent lead over those behind him in the rankings. The event only had two days left. Unless someone had an extraordinary boost in luck, first place seemed to be Happy's.

The guild leaders were also racking their brains and wanted to use different methods to help their pro players. However, during the few days of peace, they had discovered a truth: in this peaceful environment, Ye Xiu didn't seem to be so fearful; it was only when they tried to play tricks that they lost everything they invested by encountering Ye Xiu.

Maybe they should gamble their luck for the next two days? If they concocted a plan, Ye Xiu might take advantage of it and send all of Happy's characters into the top ten though.

It would be better to stay cautious!

As they thought, the top guilds decided to not speak or act. On the sixth day of the event, Deception's place seemed immovable. However, Ye Xiu's luck seemed to have gotten worse; Lord Grim fell straight out of top ten. This brought happiness to all the big guilds just by looking at it.

Following Lord Grim's drop from the ranks, Happy only had Deception who was first in the top ten, the rest had fallen out of the top ten.

On the sixth day, it was the first time that all the spawned monsters were completely eliminated. No one would have thought that there was a bonus here. After the mobs had been cleared out, the system didn't announce the event's end for the day. Instead, it announced that after the monsters were all cleared, their Ghost Lair had been discovered by five heroic warriors.

These five monster-slaying heroic warriors were Peaceful Hermit, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Deception, Something to Hide, and Howling Fire.

Everyone saw the names. These five were definitely not picked at random. They were the top five characters who managed to gain the most points today.

The system then announced that the five warriors would each lead a small team of five to enter the Ghost Lair to find the ghost king. The team who killed the ghost king would be awarded with their choice of materials and equipment as rewards.

When the details of this announcement came out, the teams that didn't make it in today's top five stamped their feet and beat their chest. The winner had the freedom to choose their rewards! Rewards like this were too too too tempting. All teams had a clear plan of what they needed, so rewards that could freely be chosen could complete their most crucial needs. However, the ones who had this opportunity were only those five characters. This meant that only their respective teams had the chance of getting this reward.

Peaceful Hermit, Team Royal Style.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Team Tyranny.

Deception, Team Happy.

Something to Hide, Team Misty Rain.

Howling Fire, Team Wind Howl.

Every character could bring five people, which meant that this was a standard team. The competition between the five teams would then unfold in the Ghost Lair, which was suspected to be a dungeon.

The people, who didn't get the chance, were cursing, while the five, who got the chance, were already starting to organize their teams When the system announcement came out, the five each received a teleportation scroll to Ghost Lair. If the scroll wasn't used in ten minutes, it would self-destruct automatically. This meant that they must create a team within ten minutes.

This was too easy for a team; they only had to bring in the formation of the main force and a five-man team would instantly be ready to go.

However, Something to Hide had a bit of a problem. His player, Lu Yining, was a sub in Team Misty Rain. Especially after Misty Rain had enrolled the beautiful Sharpshooter sisters, as another Sharpshooter player, the chances of him leaving this summer were very high. Players, who were put in this sort of situation, wouldn't be in the mood to sacrifice their break to get stronger. This was because there was a high possibility that their character would no longer be theirs next season. However, each person would look at each problem differently. Lu Yining figured that the probability of transferring to another team was very high, so he joined the event with vigor. He hoped his professional and vigorous attitude would give his potential bosses good impressions, which was more beneficial for his future development.

There was no difficulty in fighting these monsters for any pro player because everyone would have the same efficiency. Lu Yining's luck was pretty good today since he was ranked fourth and even helped Team Misty Rain get an entrance ticket to the event. When he realized that he was a character about to be abandoned by the team, Lu Yining truly had the heart to throw the scroll away. However, he clearly cared more about the feedback he would receive for his actions, so he could only forcefully raise his spirits to find his teammates from Misty Rain.

Another player who had a problem was Deception.

The system announcement was very clear about the bonus event, but the entrance ticket was a teleportation scroll that was only valid for ten minutes. Only Mo Fan knew this detail.

He was waiting for Ye Xiu and the others to call for him to group up, but no one knew about the time limit, so they were taking their time in handling the tasks they had in hand. Seconds and minutes flew by. Mo Fan looked around, hoping that someone would notice him. No one did. Neither did anyone send him a message in the game.

...

Nine minutes, eight minutes, seven minutes…...

Two minutes!

Mo Fan was so anxious that he stood up. With that, he was finally able to get everyone's attention.

"Two minutes left." He said.

"Hm?" Everyone was puzzled.

Mo Fan looked at the teleportation scroll, which his mouse was hovering over. It was no longer two minutes, but 1 minute and 45 seconds.

"Form a party for the Ghost Lair." Mo Fan said.

"Oh oh, let me see who should go!" Ye Xiu looked to the left and right unhurriedly.

"Quick, one minute and half!" Mo Fan said.

"There's a time limit? Fuck, why did you only tell us this when there's only a minute and half left!" After Ye Xiu understood, he panicked. "Little Tang, Steamed Bun, Mucheng, let's go!"

The moment Mo Fan heard Ye Xiu randomly call out the names of the people he picked, he quickly sent team invitations to the characters. It was only when he was about to type their names that he realized he hadn't even added these people as friends.

The sweat on Mo Fan's head was about to fall, his hand speed increased explosively while Ye Xiu was hurrying him: "Hurry hurry hurry." Due to a slip of his hand, he messed up on of the names. Dancing Rain... such a strange name*. Mo Fan even hurried and cursed at it.

At last, the five-man team was formed when the scroll only had ten seconds left. Mo Fan didn't even dare delay for half a second as he clicked the 'use' button with a right click. Happy's five-man team entered the Ghost Lair.

"Stay alert." After they were teleported, this was the first thing Ye Xiu said. Only one team could win the prize, but the system didn't explain how they would get it. Did each team enter different dungeons and compete for the fastest speed? Or did they all enter one dungeon, so they would have to fight the ghost king as well as one another? None of this was known at the moment. Ye Xiu reminded them to stay alert beforehand in order to avoid the second situation. He quickly spun around in a full circle and began observing the situation in the Ghost Lair.

*TL Note: (沐雨橙风) Dancing Rain. It's a play on Su Mucheng's (苏沐橙) name, which makes it easy to make a mistake. The first two characters 沐雨 is a play on 沐浴, which means to bathe. The first character is replaced with part of Su Mucheng's name. The third and fourth characters 橙风 is a play on 乘风. The third character is replaced with another part of Su Mucheng's name. The name (沐雨橙风) comes from a poem (载驰载驱 , 沐雨栉风), which translates to "Gallop swiftly horses, keep moving in spite of the wind and rain." That was shortened to Dancing Rain. Fun fact, Su Mucheng/the author Butterfly Blue likes to name characters after poems. Lord Grim, One Autumn Leaf come from poems. Peaceful Hermit, Vaccaria, Desert Dust, Blue Bridge Spring Snow, Sleeping Moon, and many more also come from poems.

Chapter 1107: Ghost Lair

"Stay quiet for now." Ye Xiu sent this message to the team. Right now, not only did they have to watch, they had to listen, and perhaps they would hear the voices of other teams talking.

So everyone kept silent. There wasn't a single sound to be heard.

This Ghost Lair was an underground dungeon, the type where you couldn't see the sky. Ye Xiu looked around carefully and didn't hear anything, but he didn't dare to be overconfident, and sent in the team channel: "We'll use messages to communicate for now."

"Okay," the others answered.

"There are two paths, which should we take?" While Ye Xiu had been examining the surroundings, the others had as well, and Su Mucheng saw that they could take either a left or a right tunnel from their start point.

The situation was entirely unclear and there were no clues, so right or left didn't matter.

"Either's fine!" Ye Xiu said. His Lord Grim was already headed toward the left tunnel.

"Will there be small monsters?" Tang Rou asked.

"Still not clear, let's just all be careful!" said Ye Xiu.

As he spoke, the five characters had all entered the left tunnel.

"What's that sound?" Ye Xiu immediately sensed something.

Everyone listened closely. There was indeed a sound, a sort of rumbling that seemed to be getting closer and closer, and then their cameras began to tremble, as though the ground itself were shaking. At the end of the tunnel, there was a shadowy mass that kept approaching, until they could finally see what it was.

"What, how cliche!" Ye Xiu yelled.

"Run!" Su Mucheng said, already using Aerial Cannon to retreat. The other four also turned their characters and began to sprint back along the path they came. Behind them was an enormous boulder rolling toward them, so large that it filled the entire tunnel.

With this, the issue of which path to take was resolved.

They returned to their start point and charged into the right tunnel, but that boulder was persistent. The system must have helped it move, because it also rolled into the right tunnel, and continued to chase them.

"Watch your rhythm!" Ye Xiu reminded everyone, seeing the boulder's perseverance. How long would they have to run along until this was over?

So they ran and ran, the boulder behind them. There was still no way for them to get rid of it, and the road ahead didn't show any new opponents. It was just one tunnel, continuing on.

"What's that new sound?" At this moment, Su Mucheng heard some new movements.

"Echoes?" Ye Xiu guessed.

"No… ahead… it sounds like the same thing is happening," Tang Rou said. With her ear training, her ability to distinguish sounds was quite high.

"No way? That shameless?" The five were dumbfounded. They hadn't even done anything since entering the Ghost Lair! Sending boulders from the left and right tunnels to squish them dead, wasn't this design just too unreasonable?

When they thought of that, the five couldn't be bothered to continue running. Their footsteps slowed to a halt, but then they heard very clearly, aside from the sounds of a boulder up ahead, there was also the sound of hurried footsteps.

"Oh hey, another group as unlucky as us?" Ye Xiu said.

"There has to be an exit. Let's continue forward!" said Su Mucheng.

The five once again began their frantic running.

At last, they could clearly see the boulder ahead that was rolling toward them. But more clearly, they could see the five characters running ahead of it, almost like the opening credits of the animation Saint Seiya.

The five now discovered Happy's five, or perhaps they had heard their sounds earlier, but they didn't falter in their steps, because the danger of getting flattened by the boulder was much more pressing than the danger posed by Happy. If they hesitated for just a second, the boulder would crush them.

"Yo, it's the old bros!"

As they neared, Ye Xiu called out. The five that were approaching were none other than Team Tyranny, and the characters were the five on their main roster, including the four Gods.

"Is there no path on your end?" Someone from Tyranny shouted toward them.

"Nothing," Ye Xiu replied.

"Is this system actually as shameless as you are?" Zhang Jiale exclaimed.

But right at that moment, the two approaching teams simultaneously discovered a thread of hope. Right between the two teams, there was an indentation on one side of the tunnel.

Did it lead to an exit? They couldn't tell.

But this was the only choice they had, unless they just waited to be crushed by the two boulders!

Lord Grim dashed forward and was the first to get into this temporary hiding spot.

Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was the second to enter, and immediately raised his guns toward Lord Grim. He didn't fire, but kept a close watch on Lord Grim's movements. Afterwards, the characters of the two teams jumped in one by one. This wasn't any exit, it was just a nook in the wall. With ten people squeezed inside, it suddenly felt like a crowded elevator.

"Zhang Jiale, what are you so nervous for? Are you claustrophobic?" Ye Xiu ridiculed Zhang Jiale's distrustful attitude.

Zhang Jiale hadn't relaxed a single bit, and neither had Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, or Zhang Xinjie. They all paid close attention to the actions of Ye Xiu's Lord Grim.

"You ran quite fast, you were the second to enter." Ye Xiu continued to talk. The word "second" stung Zhang Jiale, and he was absolutely sure that Ye Xiu was doing this on purpose, because that guy added, "What place were you on the leaderboard again? To get the teleportation scroll."

For today's leaderboard, Zhang Jiale had gotten second place.

"Fuck you!" As Zhang Jiale swore, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms finally lowered his gun. Not because Ye Xiu's taunting made him forget his wariness, but because just now, there was a giant crash as the two boulders finally collided, just outside of the nook. Just like that, the two teams, ten people, were shut into a nook that was about as large as an elevator.

"What's going on?" Someone said, confused.

"There should be an exit," Zhang Xinjie said.

"Where's the exit? There's not a lot of space here, if I turn around I might hit you with my weapon!" Ye Xiu said.

"Hey don't move now, be good for once!" Dazzling Hundred Blossoms raised his gun again.

"Fuck, don't be so arrogant, you're not the only one who can do that!" Lord Grim raised his Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, now in gun form. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain followed suit in perfect partnership, and her cannon was much more impressive than the small pistol in Dazzling Hundred Blossoms' hand.

"Everyone, look around, see if you can find anything on the walls near you." Zhang Xinjie completely ignored this squabble.

And so Zhang Jiale turned his camera to look at the walls near him, when - bang! The sound of a gun. Lord Grim had opened fire!

"My bad my bad, it went off accidentally!" Ye Xiu's voice came almost as quickly as the sound of the gun.

Would a game have accidents like this? Of course not! Zhang Jiale fumed, and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms reached for a hand grenade.

"Calm down, that can't go off accidentally." Ye Xiu hurriedly said.

"It seems like there's something over here." Lin Jingyan's voice finally drew everyone's attention once and for all.

"Oh, looks like it's nothing…" Lin Jingyan said.

"How do you know?" asked Ye Xiu.

"Because I already smashed it." Lin Jingyan's Brawler pulled his fist from the wall. His weapons were claws, after all. With one claw, he destroyed his discovery, and also got his hand stuck there...

"It looks like there isn't any trick here," said Su Mucheng.

Silence.

If there was no trick, would they just be stuck in here forever?

"Try blowing apart the two boulders." Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing finally offered this solution.

"How tyrannical." Ye Xiu sent a thumbs up emoji.

Straight Punch!

Han Wenqing was a man of action. As soon as he finished speaking, his Desert Dust already sent a Straight Punch toward the boulder on the left, in order to try and send it rolling in the opposite direction.

But even with this punch, the boulder didn't move at all.

Collapsing Fist!

Han Wenqing's willpower was similarly unmoved. Desert Dust continued with a barrage of attacks, yet the boulder still refused to budge.

Emperor's Fist!

One of the Striker's fiercest charged attacks was unleashed. It looked the same as a normal punch, but it would be a big mistake to think that this was only as strong as a normal punch.

The Emperor's Fist burst forth! At the same time, a silhouette flashed to Desert Dust's side.

Lord Grim, a Falling Flower Palm struck the boulder at the same time as Desert Dust's attack.

With that, the boulder finally wobbled a bit, as though it were finally about to separate from its companion.

But it still wasn't enough.

Desert Dust clenched his two fists and his body tensed. Striker Level 75 status skill: One Inch Burst.

A high-end status in which the attack range was shortened to raise the power of the strike. Desert Dust released a chain of punches, the Level 70 skill "Ferocious Tiger Flurry."

Light flashed. There was the nonstop sound of strikes hitting the boulder, which continued to lurch back and forth, and finally seemed as though it were about to separate from its partner.

"Little Tang!" Ye Xiu called.

"Coming!" Tang Rou answered. Soft Mist twisted her spear, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

The Battle Mage's Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had a high knockback effect, and was now used by Soft Mist from a close range on the boulder. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim couldn't contribute this high-level attack, and just used another Falling Flower Palm to increase the pushing force.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky slammed into the boulder. The boulder wasn't easily pushed away, but Soft Mist herself was pushed back from the force of the blow.

Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock immediately stood behind her.

Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale, Su Mucheng… Everyone's characters immediately clustered together, giving Soft Mist support.

Boom!

The boulder finally rolled in the opposite direction. Between the two boulders there was finally a gap through which people could pass.

Everyone let out a sigh of relief.

"It knocked away some of my health." Lin Jingyan looked at his character. Just now, when they had all gone to use their bodies to support Soft Mist, they had suffered some damage.

Zhang Xinjie sent a few heals his way, then glanced at Happy - they hadn't brought a healer.

Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing's characters had already walked between the boulders to look around and evaluate their next step.

"Are we going to continue pushing them like this?" Someone asked.

"There's a little bit of space above, we can see if we can squeeze through," said Ye Xiu, after studying the surroundings.

The boulder didn't block the tunnel entirely - in order for it to roll along, there had to be some space. At the top, especially at the two sides of the tunnel, it looked as though there were enough space for a character to pass through.

"We'll go this way." Ye Xiu pointed to the path from which his team had come.

"We'll go this way." Han Wenqing turned to face their own path.

"I hope we don't meet again."

"Likewise," said Han Wenqing.

"Alright everyone let's go, watch out for these sneaky old foxes attacking us from behind, hurry, hurry." Ye Xiu directed his team.

Chapter 1108: Shards of the Ghost King’s Chamber

The two teams took a path each and soon made their way through the gap on top. Two large boulders laid between them.

Before they got a good understanding of the Ghost Lair, it was reasonable for the two teams to not have any real conflicts. However, they still secretly hoped that when the other team climbed over, another boulder would immediately come to squish them flat.

Unfortunately, both sides were disappointed. After they climbed over the boulder, the whole path stayed clear. After they walked through the same path as before, the dungeon finally started to open up more.

"This seems like a tomb." The five members of Happy reached the tunnel's end. The room was square and very spacious. It was also e quite tidy. Apart from the chamber... there seemed to be no other constructions in the dungeon.

After he spoke, the center of the room started to move and creak, a stone coffin slowly rose up from the ground.

"Hm? Is the boss about to spawn?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Ghost king?"

"This easy? We gained without spending any effort!" Ye Xiu spoke while the five members of Happy started to stand in formation.

"We should figure out the boss's attack patterns before we start our attacks. We don't have a healer, so everyone should be extra careful." Ye Xiu reminded. Judging from the general event, the ghosts had high attack, but weak defenses. It was easy to handle them after their weakness was found, but before that, they were hard to deal with.

Thinking back to the seaweed monster, the boss should be able to deal damage at that level. That ghost's attack was strong to the point it could instant kill anyone.

Happy scattered and stood in position. The stone coffin was also finally able to rise up completely from the ground. A a creaking sound came out as the coffin lid was pushed aside.

The five were relatively calm because they had seen too many of these tricks in the game. A player might find it mysterious and terrifying the first time, but they grew insensitive to these long ago.

When the coffin lid was shifted halfway, a pale, slim hand rose up to grab the edge of the coffin. The thing that was previously sleeping in there quickly sat up.

It was a female ghost.

The hair, skin, and clothing. All gave hints about it being a female ghost.

Ye Xiu didn't hesitate and threw a grenade into the stone coffin.

The grenade exploded and the female ghost shrieked, her voice sounded as if she was terrified. Being scared by this type of skill wasn't something that should happen to a boss.

The female ghost flew out from the stone coffin and rushed towards Lord Grim's direction with a shrill shriek.

The surrounding area instantly turned piercing cold.

"Ice attack!" Ye Xiu called and Lord Grim had already rolled to the side.

Dancing Rain set up her cannon, and three consecutive shots were let out. The female ghost was very quick and knew how to dodge the attacks. This was indeed the sort of intellect only bosses possessed.

After dodging past the three Anti-Tank Missiles, Tang Rou's Soft Mist blocked her way. She used series of low-level skills, combined with Chasers. This forced the female ghost to a point she couldn't fight back.

"Be careful, don't fight too close together!" Ye Xiu reminded.

"Understood." Tang Rou's focus was concentrated. What other unknown attacks did this female ghost have? They didn't know, but someone had to try. They wouldn't be able to test her thoroughly if they relied on long-ranged attacks, so they could only try with different methods.

A Fire Chaser flew out. The buff from the Fire Chaser wrapped around Soft Mist's arms and her strength increased significantly. The female ghost let out another mournful scream.

"She's afraid of fire, so she's a pure ice-type!" Ye Xiu recognized firmly.

"Gasoline Bottle!" Ye Xiu shouted at Steamed Bun.

Steamed Bun Invasion threw out a Gasoline Bottle, and as expected, the female ghost was suffering and enraged in every way.

"Flame Cut!" Ye Xiu called again.

Deception sprinted ahead.Trails of fire followed behind the ninja blades as they sliced the female ghost's body.

The female ghost continued to shriek miserably. As the blade pierced her body, it directly left a cutting mark that seemed burnt. It seemed that this was more effective than the previous fire-type attacks.

However, the female ghost's counterattacks also became incisive. She opened her mouth and blew out a gust of icy whirlwind. It was quick and covered a large area. Deception tried to dodge, but he wasn't able to dodge it fully, so his left arm, which got caught in the wind, turned into an ice block.

"What happened?" Ye Xiu asked. He wanted to know the effect of this attack.

"It's frozen." Mo Fan replied. This was the state the system gave Deception's left arm at the time.

"Can you still form seals?" Ye Xiu asked.

"No." Mo Fan said. All his controls that included movements with his left arm were forcibly deactivated. All the seals naturally required both hands, so without his left arm, the seals couldn't be formed.

"Then it would be like a Silence?" Ye Xiu said. Steamed Bun was a good fellow, when he saw Mo Fan's Deception was injured, he gave up his safety to help. However, the female ghost was very agile, so after she had injured Deception, she immediately turned around to blow towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

"Be careful, Steamed Bun!" Ye Xiu reminded immediately. Steamed Bun had already dashed behind the female ghost, but he didn't expect her to suddenly turn around and blow straight onto Steamed Bun Invasion's head.

Could it be that his head would be sealed? What were the results of that? Would his Intelligence decrease drastically? Because his brain was frozen?

Steamed Bun roared even sharper than the female ghost's scream. Of course, his roar didn't deal any damage, because key presses were required for an attack.

Steamed Bun Invasion, who faced the female ghost directly, lifted both his arms with a calm and collected manner.

The female ghost opened her mouth to blow a gust of icy whirlwind, but she was lifted horizontally in midair. Steamed Bun was able to brush straight past her.

Back Throw!

Steamed Bun Invasion threw the female ghost out with a Back Throw, so the icy whirlwind didn't even manage to brush him.

"This guy..." Ye Xiu was covered in cold sweat head to toe. He managed to use Back Throw's control to dodge the attack. Ye Xiu wasn't sure whether Steamed Bun consciously knew what he was doing, but it was a brilliant move nonetheless by replacing defense with offense.

"So close so close!" In the next second, Steamed Bun exclaimed and controlled his character to escape by rolling and crawling. He carefully kept his distance between the female ghost.

They had discovered the female ghost's weakness and had witnessed her attacks. Ye Xiu quickly adjusted his strategical thoughts, and commanded how everyone should deal with the ghost.

The grave chamber was instantly filled with shrill shrieks of the female ghost. After further inspection, the ice-type attack she activated through her shrieks was the fastest and strongest. Finally, with the cost of Steamed Bun Invasion's head being frozen, the female ghost was completely taken down within some wave of attacks.

Everyone hurriedly rushed ahead to surround Steamed Bun.

There was a large ice cube on his head. At this moment, Steamed Bun Invasion looked like a bean sprout.

"What's up, is your Intelligence still normal?" Ye Xiu was concerned about his hypothesis.

"There's nothing wrong with my IQ." Steamed Bun said.

Ye Xiu noticed that his voice was weak. It was obvious that the sound didn't come from the game. His voice had reached his ear in the training room, but it had been sealed in the game. This was very realistic because his mouth was one of the parts that were frozen!

"I mean your Intelligence stat." Ye Xiu spoke while he clicked onto Steamed Bun to check his stats.

His Intelligence was normal.

The hypothesis that a frozen brain meant lower Intelligence proved to be false.

Keeping up with the large, frozen head, Steamed Bun Invasion took a few steps forward. He swayed to and fro, which showed his terrible balance. This was probably due to the destruction dealt by the freeze.

"Look, what's this!" When everyone surrounded Steamed Bun Invasion, Su Mucheng noticed an item dropped by the female ghost.

Shard for the Ghost King's Chamber.

"Hm…..." Ye Xiu saw it.

If there was one shard, there would definitely be a second one, as well as a third, fourth, or fifth. The female ghost was obviously not the Ghost King, but one of his subordinates. The shards of this chamber was probably a type of key to unlock the hidden chamber. How many shards were there? Were they still on the boss? Since they have already collected it, if someone else wanted it, would they have to kill them in order for the shard to drop? Could the teams cooperate by using the shards together?

He tried to use it by right-clicking it. The system said that they needed the second, third, fourth, and fifth shard.

As expected.

Between the five teams, the five shards could only be used when they were put together. Through this type of method, only one team out of the five would have the opportunity to fight the Ghost King in the end.

Countless of thoughts flashed past Ye Xiu's head. At that moment, the wall facing them started to crumble. In an instant, the wall vanished. The crushed stones left on the ground didn't seem to match the quantity lost on the wall.

When the wall tumbled down, the chamber became even more spacious. Ye Xiu immediately saw a team before them who also just finished watching the wall tumble. Most importantly, a ghost's corpse also laid on their side. It wasn't the fully pale female ghost, but it should have been a ghost on the same level.

The people on both sides were startled at first, then they became aware of something. The pupils of the players on both sides contracted.

Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire!

The opponent's attacks came quicker and more direct. Young people! They were always rather impatient.

The people who came over from the opposite side of Happy belonged to Team Wind Howl. Zhao Yuzhe immediately launched an attack. He attacked while using the spell's lights to cover his team. The tomb chamber was wide and spacious, so there were no covers. After going through two years of his career life, Zhao Yuzhe was no longer a fresh rookie. He was one of the excellent players from the new generation, despite not having received a God's title yet.

The five from Happy dodged hurriedly.

It was pretty easy to dodge such a high-level skill when it was launched straight ahead without any base. Even Steamed Bun Invasion, who still carried the large ice cube on his head managed to sway aside and dodge.

However, Zhao Yuzhe's aim wasn't to attack in the first place, his intentions mainly laid in screening.

This was a fairly mature way of fighting for Wind Howl. Under the cover of his spell's light, Wind Howl's master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, started to fill the ground with his traps.

"Retreat for now." Ye Xiu informed. Steamed Bu Invasion's rhythm was slow and his balance was messed up because his head was still frozen. Happy couldn't fight at full power at the moment, so they could only keep away from the vanguard temporarily.

Unfortunately, Team Wind Howl's captain and ace, Tang Hao, was the type who wouldn't let things slip when he had a reason not to.

The more Happy retreated, the fiercer he rushed ahead.

The Brawler was originally a class that was very nimble and could change constantly. But with the class in his hands at this moment, Demon Subduer was brave and fierce like Desert Dust, the King of Fighting.

Tang Hao was extremely annoyed over the fact that his Brawler didn't have an impressive title.

Just like the Battle God, Great Gunner, Sword Saint, and King of Fighting, Demon Subduer should have an extravagant title too.

Demon Subduer then rushed ahead with a tyranny that his class didn't originally possess...

Chapter 1109: Two 1v4s

"He's too arrogant." Ye Xiu sighed deeply upon seeing the ferocity of Tang Hao's Demon Subduer. "Old Lin was never so indecent, despite playing a Brawler his whole life."

"Steamed Bun, why is your head still frozen?" Ye Xiu spoke as he turned around to see Steamed Bun Invasion's big frozen head.

Steamed Bun shook his big frozen head and expressed helplessness and regret.

Demon Subduer arrived. He was currently the blade of Wind Howl, a dagger that was even sharper than when Lin Jingyan was present.

Poison Needle, Gasoline Bottle, Sand Toss...

Demon Subduer used a series of skills the moment he arrived. Lord Grim opened up his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella into its shield form. Tang Hao was enraged and made Demon Subduer leap up. He stamped directly onto Lord Grim's head as he flew above the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella contracted immediately. Behind the umbrella stood Dancing Rain's cannon, which was already set in place.

Tang Hao's heart thudded. The ray from Laser Rifle was launched out of the mouth of Dancing Rain's cannon.

Eagle Stamp!

Demon Subduer forcibly used this technique in midair, which seemed to have allowed him to halt momentarily during the time he stamped. He used the very technique Han Wenqing had used against Sun Xiang in the All Stars Challenge.

However, the AoE that the Laser Rifle covered wasn't something one could fully dodge just by making small changes such as a temporary halt in midair. Half of Demon Subduer's body was blasted by the Laser Rifle, and the strong force made him go spiraling through the air. There was a roof because they were in a dungeon. In the end, Demon Subduer didn't continue to fly in midair, but instead crashed rather tragically into the ceiling…..

"Young people…" Ye Xiu sighed emotionally as he enjoyed the sight of Demon Subduer embedded in the roof.

Tang Hao felt extremely aggravated, such a penetrating charge was instantly defused with the snap of a finger. He was even embedded into the ceiling like some sort of hanging light, how could he endure this?

However, that wasn't all!

Ye Xiu wouldn't let things slip when given the opportunity. Such as now, he was sighing with emotion as the muzzle of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella was aimed at Demon Subduer. With the addition of Dancing Rain, two sets of Gatling Guns were brought out together. The bullets crossed and shot Demon Subduer in sync. The attacks were very satisfying.

Unsightly, it was too unsightly.

Even the teammates of Tang Hao found it difficult to watch. They rushed ahead to save him. As a result of this, it was Happy's turn to act tyrannically.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou's Soft Mist sprinted ahead by using her customary starting skill. The players of Wind Howl, who sprinted ahead and were ready to attack, went past her like a strong gale. Soft Mist didn't bother with the charging players ahead, but passed through a gap between them to look for the healer standing behind them instead.

The players of Wind Howl were stuck in a difficult situation. They had their captain at the front, and the healer at the back. Who should they save first?

"Save the healer!" Their leader finally gave them a command.

Everyone retreated to save the healer in a hurry. Lord Grim and Dancing Rain's joint shooting was also finally complete, and Demon Subduer fell down. Tang Hao impatiently wanted to attack.

A shadow suddenly flickered behind him.

Tang Hao was able to notice it, but since he was still adjusting himself in midair, he wasn't able to make too many movements freely.

It was as if the other team had prepared for it, because they started their attacks immediately.

Countless shadows scattered around Demon Subduer.

Ninjutsu: Shadow Dance!

Mo Fan was the one who attacked. Deception grabbed onto the chance by giving Demon Subduer a wave of fierce attacks as he dropped from the air.

Tang Hao was on the verge of coughing up blood. He had never been beaten into such a wretched state like this, not even when he was playing in professional matches. He was passive in every way, powerless to fight back.

He longed for reinforcement, but he had just told everyone to save the healer. If he immediately called out for them to help again, wouldn't it become a joke? Would he have any reputation left?

Tang Hao could only grit his teeth and endure.

Wait until I reach the ground!

He thought to himself.

He finally reached the ground.

What met him were Poison Needles, a Gasoline Bottle, and a Sand Toss!

He used these three skills earlier when he sprinted boldly ahead with the grandeur of annihilating Happy all by himself. As Happy welcomed his landing with joy, they used the same three skills.

Steamed Bun finally attacked. When the ice around his head melted, his condition returned to normal and he became exceptionally nimble.

Tang Hao wanted to avoid it, but couldn't. He truly longed for reinforcements, so he spun his camera around. He then realized that Happy had Tang Rou take on the four players of Wind Howl by herself.

It's been so long and you still haven't taken her down? Tang Hao was truly angry. Honestly speaking, he had never really thought much of Happy, including Ye Xiu.

Ever since he had gained fame in the All Stars Weekend by usurping the senior as a junior, he naturally possessed a strong psychological advantage when he fought with the older generation.

For him, Team Happy was just a combination of old farts and rookies. What was there to fear? A bunch of Gods were even seriously analyzing the members of Happy in the pro player chat. Was that necessary?

And now, it seemed that the four from his team weren't able to swiftly take down Soft Mist like he had expected. After feeling mad, he realized that he needed to face Happy seriously.

Soft Mist was fighting four by herself, and he was currently fighting four as well. Despite fighting the same numbers, they were in completely different situations: she had the initiative, while he didn't.

Soft Mist was doing what he had originally intended to do! He was able to sprint ahead with daring spirit because he had planned to stall the majority of the opposition's main force by himself like what Soft Mist was achieving right now. Then, his side would have the numbers advantage. This was the role of an ace.

But now, he was on the back end.

It could be said that the purpose of him as the ace was completely blown off by Happy. He had walked straight into the trap!

However, he didn't want to lose face. He didn't want to call for reinforcements because he wanted to take on the burden of the current situation by himself.

After Steamed Bun Invasion had greeted him with three skills after his landing, he dashed ahead with a Strangle.

Tang Hao was naturally incomparably familiar with the Brawler skills. When Steamed Bun Invasion slightly moved his shoulder, he predicted that a Strangle was coming. Tang Hao hastily controlled Demon Subduer to dodge. No matter what happened at this moment, he would not allow himself to be hit by this type of CC skill.

Despite having avoided Steamed Bun Invasion's Strangle, Demon Subduer was still caught in a Strangle.

Lord Grim's Strangle.

This was a low level skill under Level 20, so it was natural for the unspecialised Lord Grim to use it.

The Strangle was the starting signal for focusing a target. When he was taken down by the Strangle, the other three immediately launched another wave of targeted attacks. They wouldn't be able to recover because they didn't bring any healers, which increased the risk in fighting, but when focusing on a single target, their attacks stirred the soul.

On the other side, Fang Rui's group of four was dealing with Tang Rou. Even though Fang Rui was an expert, his style of playing dirty was never a quick-paced fighting method. His specialty lay in continuous consumption. However, Tang Rou's ferocity and boldness made Fang Rui feel uneasy. He most definitely did not disapprove of the players of Happy like Tang Hao. There was no problem in taking Soft Mist down at all, but it definitely was not as easy as taking her down in one go the moment they reached her. More time was needed.

If they needed more time on their side, what about Tang Hao? Could he hold on?

Fang Rui soon recognized this problem. However, the moment he looked at the other side, he witnessed Tang Hao being in a complete mess as he was tortured by the other four. His situation was more miserable than that of Tang Rou's.

Fang Rui sighed. He knew that Tang Hao's pride wouldn't allow him to call for help. But at the moment, he really, really needed reinforcement.

Switch targets!

Under the signal of Fang Rui, Zhao Yuzhe's group of three sprinted to assist Tang Hao. They left Tang Rou for Fang Rui to fight by himself because they didn't have any doubts about Fang Rui's abilities.

When the three switched targets to reinforce the other side, Tang Rou now had a much easier time. After all, Tang Rou wasn't able to take care of every single one of the four.

However, the moment they left the battle to switch targets, Fang Rui immediately said: "F*ck."

Soft Mist immediately increased her speed.

By going from a 1v4 to a 1v1, it was natural for her to suddenly release her battle prowess after the pressure dropped. What Fang Rui didn't expect was Soft Mist's immediate increase in speed to be so astonishing. What type of acceleration was this? At this moment, Fang Rui felt threatened and nearly lost his composure.

He was the master at playing dirty, after all. Patience and calmness were top qualities that this style required. However, a mere increase in speed but nothing else had frightened Fang Rui.

Then, her hand speed burst forth. A wave of powerful attacks pursued and rumbled its way towards Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon, the only target. Fang Rui realized that Tang Rou's sudden increase in speed had covered all of the distance between them. He was too busy being shocked that he actually forgot to pull away to a comfortable distance.

Thieves weren't specialized in close-combat fights. After suddenly having Soft Mist sticking with him, the wave of power smashed Fang Rui's heart into pieces. What made it worse was that the power didn't seem to have an end to it. What type of fighting spirit is this? Fang Rui was unable to relate this with the pretty girl in the report, who was beautiful to the point that one's heart would feel untroubled and pleased.

What a troublesome person!

Fang Rui came up with this complete analysis. However, despite being hard to deal with, he still believed that he could handle her. Doubtful Demon was on the defensive under Soft Mist's suppression and continued to retreat step by step. However, they were moving straight towards the direction Fang Rui had hoped to reach.

Nearly there!

Fang Rui counted quietly. As a master at playing dirty, it would be impossible for him to forget where he had previously planted his trap. That was alway his strongest weapon.

Young people!

Seeing Tang Rou's ferocity when she fought closed up, Fang Rui thought to himself.

But it's over now.

Fang Rui smiled. He was about to succeed in fooling a person. He enjoyed this kind of feeling, the delight when a prey lost it composure the moment it was caught in a trap.

What sort of reaction would this pretty girl make?

Fang Rui looked forward to it.

However, the moment Soft Mist was about to run into his trap, she stopped.

Switch positions!

"I'm here!" Ye Xiu shouted. The spear form of Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestation Umbrella flew forward and followed after Soft Mist's previous attack.

"What did you come here for?" Fang Rui fumed. It was as if a good scene was just about to unfold before him, but someone called out "cut"! Itt was too anticlimactic!

"I'm here to teach you how to play dirty!" Ye Xiu yelled. There weren't many people who dared to say those words to the master.

"F*ck off!" Fang Rui yelled. When facing Ye Xiu, the majority of the pro players would lose their composure...

Chapter 1110: Forcing Demon Subduer

Fang Rui didn't immediately contend with Ye Xiu. If Ye Xiu was over here, then what was happening on the other side? Fang Rui immediately turned his camera to look.

When he looked, Fang Rui almost cried.

Demon Subduer had always been the symbol of Wind Howl. But the number one Brawler in Glory was currently being ridden by another Brawler, who was using Tyrannical Chain Punch on him.

Fang Rui couldn't help but turn his head to look at Tang Hao, who was sitting not far away from him.

It was evident that Tang Hao was furious. The veins on his forehead looked as if they would burst into antennas.

What are they doing!

Fang Rui found it hard to believe. Didn't they all go over to assist him? Why was Tang Hao being bullied to such a state?

When he looked more carefully, he realized that Tang Hao wasn't the only person who was in a difficult situation.

The three classes that went over to help were an Elementalist, a Knight, and a Cleric.

It was needless to talk about the Cleric. He was a strong shield, but not a strong attacker.

The Knight? Since he moved so slowly in that plate armor of his, he was currently being blown to bits by Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain.

The Elementalist? It was unknown what had happened, but the Ninja from Happy was able to get close to him through a sneak attack, so Zhao Yuzhe was also in a thorny situation. However, the greater threat was still behind him. After Soft Mist had switched places with Lord Grim, she sprinted straight towards him.

What is happening?

Fang Rui found it unimaginable. He didn't mean to be contemptuous towards Happy, but to be completely oppressed by Happy like this?

"Retreat retreat retreat!"

Regardless of this, Fang Rui was still a general who could take charge. Although he was shocked at their current state, he wasn't panicked. It was still too early to determine whether this was a victory or a loss. Wind Howl just needed to reorganize themselves. After all, their team made it to the semifinals last season, so it would be illogical for them to be completely oppressed by a new team like Happy. There was only one explanation: their attacks were too careless. Without having a clear plan behind their attacks, it became very easy for Happy to catch their weaknesses.

Happy was able to catch this point and counterattacked. Every mix-up was aimed at their flaws, forcing them into a passive state, making it difficult for them to establish a steady tempo. Excellent Era was defeated in the same way in the Challenger League.

At least Excellent Era had the advantage in equipment at the time. They had made preparations as well unlike Wind Howl. As a result, it wasn't surprising that Wind Howl was in an even more embarrassing situation.

In any case, they should fully break away from the fight in order to cut off Happy's tempo. After that, they could start anew.

Fang Rui thought. Instead of challenging Ye Xiu by himself, he quickly turned away to provide cover for his teammates to retreat.

"In the end, it's the experienced players who are harder to deal with!" When Ye Xiu saw Fang Rui's decision, he couldn't help but sigh in his heart. However, he still continued to taunt: "Why are you running, you crude thief? Won't you listen to my lecture?"

Fang Rui ignored him. He was regretful that the middle finger wasn't an emoji, otherwise, he would definitely pointing it at Ye Xiu.

Doubtful Demon continued to run. He continuously planted traps in order to shrink Happy's maneuver space. Lord Grim pursued him, but how could Fang Rui give him another chance to close in again? He increased his speed to sprint all over the place.

Thieves weren't able to directly break through places like certain ferocious classes, but by letting him lay out his pieces in formation, the limitations that he created would affect the battle as a whole. Ye Xiu knew about this, but Fang Rui wasn't an opponent he could catch just by wanting to. The master of playing dirty wasn't a joke.

As a result, Ye Xiu decided not to waste any more energy and switched targets.

F*ck, this guy wants to kill Tang Hao!

Fang Rui immediately perceived Ye Xiu's intentions. As expected, it was unrealistic for him to divert Ye Xiu's attention so easily

In the end, it's the experienced players who are harder to deal with! Fang Rui came up with the same evaluation.

The oppressed Tang Hao was finally able to find an opportunity to break out. After all, Steamed Bun couldn't oppress him forever

Uppercut, Knee Attack, Powerful Knee Strike!

Tang Hao delivered a wave of counterattacks after seizing the opportunity. He nailed Steamed Bun Invasion onto the wall in an instant.

He then spun his view around. In the end, he still remembered to take note of their situation first and saw Soft Mist charging forward in a threatening and aggressive manner. Tang Rou originally intended to fight Zhao Yuzhe's Elementalist with Mo Fan, but when she saw Steamed Bun being knocked over by Tang Hao, she immediately assisted him first.

Tang Hao let out a cold 'hmph'. He was incomparably confident in a direct confrontation.

Demon Subduer didn't retreat and sprinted straight towards Soft Mist.

You're fierce? I'll be even fiercer!

Tang Hao liked this style.

He wasn't afraid, so Tang Rou was even more fearless. When it seemed like the two characters were about to clash, Tang Hao took advantage of a Brawler's mid-ranged attacks and launched the first attack. As his body flickered, he sneakily threw out a Poison Needle.

If you played a Brawler and couldn't play dirty, then you couldn't possibly be qualified to be called a Brawler. This class had many skills that were suited to trick people.

Tang Rou didn't detect Demon Subduer's hidden Poison Needle sneak attack, so she was hit by it. Tang Hao seized the opening and used a Powerful Knee Strike. Right when his flying figure was about to crash into Soft Mist, he heard his teammate warn him to watch out.

A sneak attack?

Tang Hao laughed coldly. He knew that Steamed Bun Invasion was currently behind him and that the fellow was very restless.

Tang Hao had been prepared. The Powerful Knee Strike was originally an attack that could fly out at high speed. If he slightly turned his body, how could a sneak attack hit him?

As he turned, Tang Hao shot a glance at Steamed Bun Invasion behind him. The glance showed contempt: Little guy, if you want to play with me, you're still lacking!

Unfortunately, a handful of sand immediately blinded Demon Subduer's eyes.

Why would you use a Sand Toss when sneaking up on a person from behind??? Steamed Bun Invasion turned out to use it, so when Tang Hao turned his head to look, he happened to be hit by it.

His screen completely blacked out as if the power was cut. Tang Hao was about to go mad.

In order to prevent the opponent from closing up on him, he quickly used a chain of punches and kicks for the sake of self-defense. But then, a Satellite Beam dropped down from the sky and completely engulfed Demon Subduer.

Supporting any spot on the map was one of Su Mucheng's strengths.

Screen Cannon?

This attack had an air of tactics to it. Fang Rui discovered that Happy's tempo provided many tactical options. Just a slight change could produce a different tactic.

Tang Hao immediately fell back down after just gaining the upper hand.

His other teammates were finally able to search for ways to retreat under Fang Rui's commands. The traps that the Doubtful Demon had buried started to reveal its might. The existence of traps was similar to the principle of a skill cooldown. As long as it was there and not set off, then it would be an excellent restriction and limitation. Fang Rui was able to see the awkwardness of Happy's formation in regards to the traps: They didn't bring their Cleric, so they definitely wouldn't dare to use methods like clear them out forcibly with their characters.

Their tempo slowed down immediately, which met Fang Rui's expectation. The players from Wind Howl slowly started to withdraw.

But their captain…

Demon Subduer was forcefully kept there.

Fang Rui was gloomy. Happy even used such a shameful method like abducting a hostage.

Should they return and launch a total fight with Happy with the help of traps?

It seemed that this was the only way!

The four made slight adjustments before advancing as a whole. This time, they kept a complete a formation.

Clang!

A Spike Trap suddenly flipped up from the ground and clamped onto the Knight's ankle. It locked his foot, so he wasn't able to move.

The Knight's player looked at Fang Rui with astonishment.

Fang Rui didn't know whether he should cry or laugh: "Are you stupid, is it even possible for it to be my trap?"

Traps couldn't be triggered by allies, so there was no doubt that it had been placed there by Happy. Fang Rui knew Lord Grim's unspecialized possessed three traps. However, Fang Rui wasn't aware in the least about when this guy secretly planted his own trap among his.

However, there were only three traps, so the threat wouldn't be too great. But the Spike Trap's effect in sealing one's movement was rather worrisome because their offense instantly became strangled.

After that, Fang Rui realized that Ye Xiu did something even more shameful.

He summoned a Goblin…...

That's right, compared to clearing the traps on one's own, there was one method that was even more grievous for fellow Thieves. That was to... summon creatures to clear out the traps.

Unspecialized characters were too shameless.

Fang Rui wept as he commanded everyone to destroy the goblin as soon as possible. However, under the command Ye Xiu's control, the goblin was abnormally nimble. It managed to step into three mines before it died a heroic death.

He can remember the location of my traps better than me, Fang Rui thought with a tear-streaked face. If he had these methods earlier on, why did he only just use it? Fang Rui now understood, in fact, he understood too well. It was in order to get an opportunity to kill Demon Subduer.

Although Tang Hao was strong, he still feared being grouped on. People like Fang Rui wanted to rescue him, but they needed a systematic approach in their rescue. Unfortunately, Ye Xiu's hidden trap was able to detonate Fang Rui's traps, which immediately messed up their plans. They could definitely continue to charge ahead, but if they did so, what difference would it be from the unplanned attacks they had launched previously? It would probably be oppressed by Happy in two or three moves again.

Happy wasn't a jack of all trades team that they could forcefully take down by merely relying on their skills. Happy was a pro team, so they had their own strength.

"Cut across to the right!" Fang Rui called. His traps on that side were in good condition and could still be used.

Wind Howl's players finally came over and met up with Tang Hao. The battle started once more. However, Fang Rui's original tactical plans were cut into bits and pieces earlier on.

Retreat after rescuing Tang Hao!

Fang Rui already made up his mind. He was resolute in not fighting with Happy and going at their pace.

They wanted to retreat, but Happy wouldn't allow it. The power of focusing a single target was extremely prominent. They charged towards Demon Subduer, refusing to give up until he died.

When had Tang Hao ever been this type of target? Fury burned in his heart.

Fang Rui didn't understand. If they attacked forcefully like this, they could indeed take out Demon Subduer, but without a Cleric, they would also take a lot of damage. Even if it was a 4v5, it was very possible for Wind Howl to wear them down to death!

But considering the dungeon's contents, they would still have to face competition with the other teams. Without their ace player Tang Hao, they couldn't bear this trade!

However, the current situation didn't leave them with any choice because Happy was the side attacking.

Either the fish dies or the net splits... Fang Rui couldn't come up with any ideas. Tang Hao also seemed to have understood the situation, and that it was very possible for his character to die the earliest. However, he could also strive for the team's victory. Due to his professional attitude, he wasn't discouraged. In fact, he fought even fiercer than before. If he could exchange the team's victory by sacrificing himself, then he would have fulfilled his responsibilities as the ace.

Demon Subduer finally fell. As Fang Rui had predicted, Team Happy had paid a great price for this kill.

Let's see how you'll keep going! Fang Rui thought.

He then heard Ye Xiu cry out: "F*ck, the shard wasn't on him? Retreat!"

F*ck, that was their aim? Fang Rui felt like fainting...

Chapter 1111: Wind Howl Internal Strife

Just like this, Tang Hao became the first member of Team Wind Howl to get eliminated, but at this moment, Fang Rui didn't have time to pay attention to Tang Hao's expression. After understanding Team Happy's intentions, a feeling of dizziness washed over him, making him almost fail to hold onto his own mouse.

If this were the competitive stage, Wind Howl might be down a member, but they had the overall advantage right now. Happy had sacrificed a lot of health to take down Demon Subduer. Let alone having no healer, even if Happy did have a healer, in a situation where every team member was at low health, it was very possible for the healing speed to not be able to keep up, resulting in the team being killed off one by one.

But the problem was that this wasn't on the competitive stage.

As a result, Happy had previously been fighting in disregard for everything else, but now they were running away as fast as possible.

"Where are you running!" Zhao Yuzhe roared. How could he put up with Happy running away? Elementalists had powerful attacks and strong AoE skills, the bane of Happy, whose members were on the brink of death.

Their captain's sacrifice couldn't be wasted!

Zhao Yuzhe was quite confident. His Elementalist charged forward like a Battle Mage.

"Careful!" Fang Rui immediately warned.

He hadn't seen what exactly Happy had set up, but since their intentions were so obvious, how could Happy not have made any arrangements for their escape? Let Wind Howl chase and kill them? If that was the case, it was no different from seeking their own deaths.　

Fang Rui's intention told him that Happy definitely had traps set up during their escape. Rashly chasing after them was dangerous.　　

But Zhao Yuzhe seemed to not be able to hear him. Even though Fang Rui was his senior in the team and had named a God for a long time, playing dirty was looked down upon by many. Zhao Yuzhe rather liked Tang Hao's vigor with his "the junior succeeds the senior". He didn't admire Fang Rui's dirty playing from the bottom of his heart. Although he didn't dare disrespect his senior most of the time, his hot-bloodedness had consumed him. There were a bunch of nearly dead players in front of him, ripe for him to kill. It wasn't hard to understand why he ignored Fang Rui's warning.

Teleport!

Zhao Yuzhe was afraid of letting go of even a single player from Happy. He directly teleported into the enemy ranks in an attempt to kill all five of them at once. When he teleported, he had already activated Mobile Cast. His magic staff glowed with light, ready to release a spell.

Fang Rui saw Zhao Yuzhe's audaciousness and was stupefied. The opponents were at low health, but they weren't dead. For him to advance prematurely, did he really think these five were frightened dungeon monsters? Or did he think that his bold move would catch Happy off guard…

Okay, Fang Rui admitted. From a reverse psychology standpoint, such a stupid decision was truly surprising. He only hoped that everyone in Happy was too smart and think that it wasn't possible for someone to be so stupid! Maybe because Zhao Yuzhe had done it so quickly, the other side wouldn't be able to react in time?

He looked back. Beautiful Light 1 was already laying on the ground…

Fang Rui felt it was a pity that he couldn't see the expressions on everyone in Happy. Were they surprised? Were they in admiration of Zhao Yuzhe's boundless bravery? They didn't seem to think twice though. After Beautiful Light was smacked to the ground, he was quickly smacked into the air. Then, Lord Grim and Soft Mist both used Falling Flower Palms, sending him back along with an artillery shell from Dancing Rain.

After all, no one in Happy had a lot of heath. They didn't dare keep fighting. After sending away Beautiful Light, they borrowed his body as their first form of obstruction and then utilized long-ranged attacks to suppress them further. The team's Knight wanted to rush forward and block the damage, but in the end, he was yelled at by Fang Rui.

"Why aren't you all attacking!!!" Zhao Yuzhe's Beautiful Light climbed up from the ground after being sent back and shouted thunderously. In this instant, his dissatisfaction towards Fang Rui had reached its peak.

"The other side has made preparations beforehand. They're just waiting for us to fall into their trap." Fang Rui said.

"How would you know if you don't try!" Zhao Yuzhe yelled.

"Did you not just try?" Fang Rui asked back.

Zhao Yuzhe was suddenly at a loss for words. He had tried, but he really wanted to say that Happy's way of dealing with him didn't seem to be the result of careful preparation. But why did it turn out the way it did? Because he had been an idiot! In a moment of hot-bloodedness and impulse, he had made a move thinking he was invincible. The other side didn't need any careful set ups to deal with him. The openings that he showed were too big so much so that they instantly swatted him away. However, Zhao Yuzhe was unwilling to admit that he was stupid to Fang Rui. He felt like if he had just been a bit faster, the ones lying on the ground would Happy.

"Hurry up and chase!" Zhao Yuzhe didn't reply to Fang Rui's retort. He just called over the other two members to give chase.　

Without captain Tang Hao, there was a clear disagreement to how Wind Howl should fight. The Knight and Cleric weren't entirely focused on the game. They stole a glance at Fang Rui and Zhao Yuzhe outside of the game. In the end, they didn't move. Zhao Yuzhe's was an important part of Wind Howl's future, but Fang Rui was their team's most experienced senior. In addition to Fang Rui's status as vice-captain, the two didn't move, implying that they recognized Fang Rui's authority.

Zhao Yuzhe's Beautiful Light rushed out, but discovered that the other two didn't go with him. This time, he didn't dare charge into Happy's enemy ranks so simply. In the end, he could only have his Beautiful Light stop. Outside of the game, he glared fiercely at those two players. He didn't dare be too brazen to Fang Rui, but he wasn't scared of those two at all.　

The entire practice room was deathly silent. There were only five players that could form a team to this Ghost Lair. The other five team members, who weren't participating, hadn't left. They also wanted to see what this Ghost Lair was all about. Instead, they got an internal conflict between their team's players.

Most of the people there felt very uneasy, but a certain resolute person watched with interest at everything that was happening.

Liu Hao.

He gave up on Thunderclap and transferred to Wind Howl.　　

It hadn't been long since he had joined the team. He didn't impatiently jump into the team and instead carefully observed this new team. Because this time, he truly wanted a achieve something here unlike with Team Thunderclap. In his eyes, Thunderclap was nothing more than a stepping stone. That type of small team couldn't contain this senior.

Speaking of which, Liu Hao felt like his strength was enough to replace Team Samsara's Jiang Botao. Unfortunately, Samsara was clearly very satisfied with the synergy between Jiang Botao and Zhou Zekai. They had invited Liu Hao's former teammate, Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf, but they definitely had no intentions of dropping Jiang Botao. In the end, Liu Hao was brought into Team Wind Howl. This rising team had performed outstandingly last season. Liu Hao was very satisfied and decided that he would do well here.

However, in Team Wind Howl, Tang Hao was their core. Zhao Yuzhe was the Best Rookie. His talent and growth would put him as a star in the future. Fang Rui was an All Star and their team's most experienced member. The team couldn't lack any healers, so of the five positions, only one spot remained.

Was this spot for Liu Hao?

From what he saw, he didn't think that Wind Howl valued him that much. They didn't seem to have determined that Liu Hao was the missing jigsaw piece. They were still searching for the most suitable combination. As for Liu Hao, as someone skilled and someone who free transferred, their thoughts were that they might as well sign him and test him out.

This type of attitude meant that they weren't particularly fervent about signing Liu Hao. In fact, there were many other teams that were sincerely interested in him such as Team Miracle.　

This team had took in three Excellent Era players. They had contacted Liu Hao too and gave him sincere promises. Core, team captain. They had prepared a generous offer and clearly laid it out to Liu Hao, but he rejected it without much thought.

Miracle? In Liu Hao's eyes, more like joke*. They were a team that had just gotten into the Alliance, and they wanted him to play for them? He might as well have just stayed on Thunderclap then! Core? Team captain? You think I care about being the core or team captain of a team like that?

Liu Hao ignored their sincere offer. When Team Wind Howl expressed their interest towards him, he immediately accepted. This type of powerhouse with hopes of winning the championships was where he hoped to be!

Liu Hao. At the moment, he was just one of Team Wind Howl's choices. Rather than saying that their sincerity moved Liu Hao, it was more like Liu Hao's eagerness moved them to just sign him along in the passing.

The team didn't need to offer any signing bonuses to a free player. The only requirement was to provide a salary. To be champions, no team would find it difficult to try out a player like that. As a result, Team Wind Howl moved quickly and immediately took Liu Hao as soon as the transfer window opened.

Wind Howl hoped that Liu Hao would bring change to the team. However, they didn't have any clear plans at the moment. They were still studying Liu Hao, so Liu Hao could feel that he didn't have a stable position in the team right now. As a result, he was careful. As someone who had once been a part of a powerhouse, he obviously knew how to find opportunities in the team.

And at this moment, a conflict had erupted in Team Wind Howl. Liu Hao observed it with interest.　　

Fang Rui.

Zhao Yuzhe.

It was a common conflict between a rookie and a senior. The rookie felt like the senior was blocking his path forward. The senior felt like the rookie was a threat to his position… This type of conflict didn't appear only in pro teams. It happened all the time in all levels of society.

Right now, at Wind Howl, the conflict was fully out in the open. However, whether it was Fang Rui or Zhao Yuzhe, they weren't the players with the most authority in the team! The direction that this conflict would move towards would depend on Team Wind Howl's captain and core, Tang Hao.

Yes, Tang Hao. The Tang Hao who had become famous with his "junior succeeds the senior". Liu Hao realized that the resolution to this conflict was very easy to predict.

Chapter 1112: Conflict Between Ideologies

Wind Howl's captain Tang Hao expressed displeasure at the conflict between Fang Rui and Zhao Yuzhe. His eyes stopped at Fang Rui. It was plain as day who he favored.

No one uttered a word. Team Wind Howl seemed to only be just three people.

Zhao Yuzhe continued to glare at Fang Rui with unwillingness. Tang Hao didn't show any resentment towards Zhao Yuzhe, but he wasn't looking at him in a good way either. As for Fang Rui? He was still playing the game.

His Doubtful Demon suddenly rushed out.

What? Is he regretting it now? Zhao Yuzhe, who was also in the game, noticed Doubtful Demon's movements. He could see that he was chasing after Happy.

"Isn't it too late to start chasing?" Zhao Yuzhe was puzzled.

Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon suddenly stopped chasing. He just stood there, looking around for something.

Zhao Yuzhe couldn't bear it anymore. He had his Beautiful Light move over there as well. The other two players followed.　　

Fang Rui was looking at the passageway that Happy had left through. Zhao Yuzhe had solid fundamentals too. After all, he had accumulated quite a bit of tactical experience throughout his career of two years. When he looked at this passageway, he realized how the entrance could be utilized. At this instant, he noticed: Fang Rui was right.

Happy indeed had made preparations. It would be very easy for Happy to ambush them at this entrance.

"So what?" Zhao Yuzhe refused to admit his mistake, "With their health, so what if they ambush us?"

"In important playoff matches in season two, season four, season five, and season seven, several teams encountered situations like this and lost as a result." Fang Rui said.

"..." Zhao Yuzhe stared blankly. He didn't know about these precedents. For a moment, he couldn't think of which matches Fang Rui was talking about.

"Do you think you're safe because the opponents don't have much health left? Throw away such naive thoughts! Glory isn't as sweet as you think it is." Fang Rui said　　

"I…" Zhao Yuzhe was at a loss for words. Fang Rui didn't say anything more to him. He glanced at captain Tang Hao, "We'll continue."

"Okay." Tang Hao nodded his head. He had heard the conversation between the two. Right now, it was very clear who had been in the right and who had been in the wrong.

The four players continued onwards. The other players in the team let out a sigh of relief. Only Liu Hao looked pensive.

The others only saw it as different answers for a question. But Liu Hao saw it as a conflict in ideologies between two players.

Fang Rui's style of playing dirty didn't synergize well with Tang Hao's and Zhao Yuzhe's style of play. And those two were the pillars of Wind Howl's new generation. After Demon Subduer switched hands from Lin Jingyan to Tang Hao, Fang Rui's playstyle became more and more lost in this type of team. As Tang Hao's playstyle matured and as their other main talent Zhao Yuzhe grew, Fang Rui's playing environment became increasingly difficult. At the same time, his existence itself made Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe very uncomfortable.

Wind Howl's style hadn't changed completely enough! With Tang Hao as the core, the set of strategies employed during Lin Jingyan's generation might no longer be suitable.

Wind Howl still had its struggles!

In the game, Happy's five players quickly retreated. After confirming that there were no pursuers, they stopped to rest. They drank potions and ate food to recover their mana and health. After all, this was the game and not the competitive stage.

Though it wasn't the competitive stage, the dangers hadn't passed. When were there ever these sorts of large chaotic fights on the competitive stage?

Happy stopped at a place to recover. It wasn't just a random place. Ye Xiu saw that it was a wide open space, where they couldn't be ambushed. After starting to recover, he requested that no one use food that made a lot of noise so as not to let any sound leak.

The five characters sat together on the ground and recovered silently. The tense environment constructed by Ye Xiu made everyone turn and look at their surroundings from time to time.　

Happy's cautiousness wasn't for naught. Amidst the silence, they could hear the sounds of footsteps coming from the passageway.　

That wasn't the direction Wind Howl would be coming from. Which team was this?

Tyranny and Happy had run in the opposite directions. It was too early to meet up. Thus, it should one of the other two guilds. Was it Royal Style or Misty Rain?

"Withdraw for now." Ye Xiu typed in the chat.

The five characters stood up. To hide the sounds of their footsteps, they either crouched or rolled and quickly found a hiding spot. Ye Xiu had found these spots as soon as Happy had gotten here.

The footsteps grew closer and closer. Ye Xiu told the others to retreat back, while his Lord Grim was positioned slightly more forward.

The five characters finally revealed themselves.

It was Team Misty Rain!

Windy Rain, Something to Hide, Dark Forest, None Dare Attack, Lower Your Head.

Misty Rain's character choices were as bold as Happy's. They also didn't bring a healer. What's more, their team had three Sharpshooters. Along with Windy Rain, that made four long-ranged attackers with Dark Forest as a Ninja.

"Get ready to fight." Ye Xiu called out to the other four.

Their positions were hidden. It wasn't possible for Misty Rain to directly see them. What followed depended on what Team Misty Rain did. If they decided to investigate this side, Happy had to attack first to catch them off guard.

However, Misty Rain didn't seem to have any intentions of searching this area. Their team quickly passed by this point and moved ahead.

Happy's five players slowly went out of hiding.

"Follow them." Ye Xiu said, "It'd be best if they clashed with Wind Howl."

Just when Ye Xiu sadi this, sounds of gunfire could be heard ahead.

"How aggressive! They really are pro teams! They've already encountered each other!" Ye Xiu praised.

Team Wind Howl didn't chase after Happy as soon as possible, but in the end, they still headed in this direction. After all, Happy was moving about in this direction. They hadn't given up and obviously wanted to get all the shards too, but then they encountered Misty Rain.

Wind Howl knew that Happy was ahead, so they had advanced very cautiously. When they heard footsteps, Fang Rui thought that Happy had finished recovering and had come back to kill them. This situation was within his expectations. He quickly set up traps and arranged a formation.

When the first trap was triggered, a battle soon ensued. Fang Rui looked at the enemies and suddenly felt like crying.　

If it wasn't Happy, it was okay. But it just had to be Misty Rain. Misty Rain just had to have so many long-ranged characters too, reducing the threat of his traps. Long-ranged attackers didn't need to stick close to them to attack. If they didn't enter the trap zone, how could his traps be of any use?

Today's been such an unlucky day!

Fang Rui was gloomy. Wind Howl had once again been thrown into disarray. This time, under his arrangements, Zhao Yuzhe felt like he could finally breathe.

Chu Yunxiu and her Windy Rain!

Zhao Yuzhe really wanted to fight her. He hoped that he could crush her to prove that he was the number one Elementalist. Even though it was just the game right now, these thoughts were deeply rooted in him. As soon as he saw Windy Rain, his emotions became fervent. He started to think about how he should contend with Windy Rain.　　

"Retreat!"

But then his spirits were once again dampened. Again by Fang Rui.

As soon as the situation looked slightly unfavorable, they would immediately retreat. If the enemy advances, we retreat. If the enemy retreats, we harass. These were the guidelines on how to play dirty. Fang Rui was commanding the team, so he naturally made decisions depending on his own habits.

But this made Fang Rui very very unhappy. Extremely unhappy.

"Retreat again? When are we going to fight? Didn't we already set up traps?" Zhao Yuzhe shouted. Even though he could see that these traps would mostly fail because Misty Rain consisted of mostly long-ranged attackers, he had to say it to slap Fang Rui's face.

"The traps are no good. Retreat for now." Fang Rui's style of playing dirty didn't have the same sort of pride as Zhao Yuzhe's playstyle. He simply admitted that his traps were ineffective.

F*ck, communicating with this type of person is impossible!　　

Zhao Yuzhe felt very bitter. The ideologies that the two sides had for Glory were completely different. But seeing how the other two team members had followed Fang Rui's orders and started retreating, Zhao Yuzhe didn't dare challenge Misty Rain alone. He could only retreat as well.

But Misty Rain refused to let them go. The three Sharpshooters shot at them as they chased closely behind.

The sounds of gunfire provided a good cover for Happy. They didn't need to hide their footsteps to avoid the notice of the others, making their tailing very easy.

Soon, Wind Howl retreated back to where Happy had found the shard after killing the female ghost. When they saw the walls collapsed over there, they wanted to cry.

Another team was coming in this direction, Royal Style!

The poor Wind Howl was suddenly surrounded like a dumpling. No matter how crafty Fang Rui was, it would very difficult for the entire team to escape. Both escape routes were sealed!

Their only choice was to fight!

"You don't fight when we should fight and fight when we shouldn't fight!" Zhao Yuzhe shouted in discontent.　　

Indeed, compared to the previous five players from Misty Rain or the nearly dead Happy, their situation was even more disastrous right now.

However, fighting in an tricky situation was one of the strengths of someone who played dirty.

Team Royal Style was led by Tian Sen's Exorcist, Peaceful Hermit. Starting last season, he had spent much effort in the game in an attempt to help Royal Style grow. Unfortunately, the effects weren't good. Royal Style once again failed to enter the playoffs. As for he and his Peaceful Hermit, his ranking in All Stars dropped again to 21st place. If he dropped another three places, he wouldn't make it into All Stars.

To get chosen into All Stars was an honor for many players and characters. However, Peaceful Hermit was a God-level character that had been equally as famous as One Autumn Leaf and Desert Dust back in the early days! And now, Peaceful Hermit was actually struggling to make it into All Stars? Tian Sen felt that they were incapable of making it into playoffs.

There has to be change!

Tian Sen muttered to himself again and again. This summer, this break, he threw himself into the game even more fervently.

Chapter 1113: Sending a Shard

Royal Style on the left. Misty Rain on the right. Wind Howl in the middle.

In this situation, no communication was necessary. Royal Style and Misty Rain were already thinking the same thing: eliminate Wind Howl first.

Tian Sen's Peaceful Hermit grabbed with his left hand and pulled out a talisman, crackling with lightning, from the void. He swung his right hand and a scythe flew out along with that lightning talisman towards Wind Howl.

"Lightning Talisman! Dodge!"

Fang Rui shouted. Wind Howl's four players quickly dispersed. The scythe landed at the center of their original location. The Lightning Talisman exploded and lightning spread from where the scythe had pierced into the ground.

Throwing the weapon was an Exorcist skill called "Spirit Guidance". Many Exorcist skills could be utilized along with "Spirit Guidance". A weapon thrown with "Spirit Guidance" wouldn't be considered as dropping it. Others wouldn't be able to pick it up. On the other hand, the Exorcist could grab the weapon back from afar. It could be considered as one way for an Exorcist to show off how cool he was.

But for experts, looking cool was secondary. These types of class-specific skills were skills that best displayed a class's ability. All of these skills needed to be mastered.

As the number one Exorcist in Glory, Tian Sen's mastery over this skill was needless to say. "Spirit Guidance" brought a Lightning Talisman with it, splitting up Wind Howl's team.

Misty Rain coordinated very well with them. Chu Yunxiu complemented with a Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire, a Flame Storm, and a Thunder Apocalypse. Three AoE spells completely split apart Wind Howl's four players.

Behind Winy Rain, Team Misty Rain's three Sharpshooters focused Wind Howl's Cleric. Bullets rained down wildly onto Wind Howl's Cleric.

Tian Sen saw Misty Rain's actions and directed his team to coordinate with them. Team Royal Style's players belonged to the strength category. Xu Huiliu was a Striker player. His fame might not be comparable to Han Wenqing's, but he definitely belonged to the upper ranks among Strikers. Shen Wanhe was a Spitfire. After Zhang Jiale retired, he was even a candidate for Dazzling Hundred Blossom's successor. His skill wasn't as high as a God's though, and in the end, Team Hundred Blossoms chose their own team's Zou Yuan. Then, there was He Weitang. He even had a slight connection with Zhao Yuzhe. The two had joined the pro scene the same year and were both contenders for Best Rookie that year. Even though Zhao Yuzhe was chosen to be Best Rookie, the lead had been very slight. He Weitang lost, but he was definitely a talented rookie worthy of being nurtured. He Weitang was a Summoner, which was a class that had always been missing among the All Stars cast. The last player was their Paladin, Ren Junchi. He wasn't particularly outstanding among healers, but for him to be a starter on a pro team, he couldn't be bad.

The current Team Royal Style was their starting five players. Tian Sen's Peaceful Hermit initiated with a Lightning Talisman and then directed his team to coordinate with Team Misty Rain to target Wind Howl's Cleric.

Wind Howl was still within Fang Rui's trap zone. However, Royal Style had He Weitang, who quickly had his summons lead the way. Shen Wanhe's Spitfire was also a long-ranged attacker and he quickly formed a crossfire with Misty Rain's three Sharpshooters.

How could a Cleric defend against so many attacks? His allies had been separated from him by AoE attacks. When Xu Huiliu's Striker reached him, Wind Howl's Cleric could no longer persevere and was the first to fall.　　

Misty Rain only attacked from afar. They coordinated closely with Wind Howl, making sure to avoid any accidental injuries. But the instant Wind Howl's Cleric fell, Misty Rain's Liu Hua's Ninja, Dark Forest, very precisely teleported to the fallen Cleric with a Shadow Clone Technique.

Royal Style was startled, but quickly realized Misty Rain's intentions. Xu Huiliu's Striker was just about to punch, when everyone saw that the Cleric hadn't dropped anything when he died.

Xu Huiliu forcefully canceled his skill. The two sides typed haha and tacitly understood to focus on the next target.　　

Wind Howl's Knight became the the next target of the two teams. But this time, Royal Style was prepared. He Weitang's summons swarmed the Knight. If Li Hua's Dark Forest tried to use Shadow Clone Technique again, he wouldn't be able to squeeze in.　　

Misty Rain saw this and figured that all of their efforts would have been for nothing, so they immediately switched fire to Zhao Yuzhe's Beautiful Light. They planned on testing their luck with Royal Style to see which player from Wind Howl would have the shard.

Zhao Yuzhe was in a dire situation, but his fighting spirit didn't dampen. Even though he felt like there was no possibility of him escaping, he still wanted to attack Windy Rain to prove his skill.

When the enemies stopped attacking him, Zhao Yuzhe was able to find an opportunity. He was just about to send a fierce wave of attacks at Windy Rain, when Team Misty Rain suddenly switched targets. Bang bang bang! The three Sharpshooters had shot three Thunder Snipes, striking the frail Elementalist and shattering not just his heart but his body into pieces.

Zhao Yuzhe, who had been planning on launching a fierce assault, didn't even have a way out anymore. He could only brace himself for the attacks and continue charging ahead as if he were a Battle Mage.

But midway through, Li Hua's Dark Forest intercepted him. Along with support fire from the rear, Beautiful Light wasn't even able to touch Windy Rain's clothing.

"Fuck!" Zhao Yuzhe cursed fiercely. The instant he fell, he saw that their team's Knight couldn't hang on any longer either. But what about Fang Rui?

Zhao Yuzhe immediately checked and was dumbstruck. Their teammate Fang Rui found an opportunity when the other three players died to run away.

"You!" Zhao Yuzhe fumed. Sound could no longer be transmitted in the game. He could only turn his head and shout at Fang Rui outside the game. But Fang Rui was completely focused. His hands were dancing across the keyboard and mouse. He didn't notice Zhao Yuzhe's existence at all.

You think you can escape from this kind of encirclement?

Zhao Yuzhe was solely preoccupied with Fang Rui's dirtiness, but ignored the outcome that resulted from it. Windy Rain and Royal Style, ten pro players, discovered that none of those three in Wind Howl had dropped the shard. At the same time, they also realized with a start: Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon had disappeared!

The Thief's Stealth allowed the character to move while invisible. But even so, with the two pro teams attacking from two sides, slipping away without them noticing showed Fang Rui's skill with it.

"Find him!!!" The two teams ordered.

The Stealth effect would be removed at the slightest touch and under Stealth, the character would move at 60% speed. Even if the skill was maxed, the movement speed could only reach at 85%. Any attack or any movement that used stamina would automatically cancel Stealth. The only exception was if the Thief had Trap Proficiency and placed down traps under Stealth.

Pro players obviously understood how the skill worked. They naturally knew how to get a Thief out of stealth, but despite their best efforts, they were unable to dig out Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon.

The two teams continued to do their best, but at the same time, they had gradually started to shift their intentions. Next up was time for the two teams to fight. The teams already understood how this dungeon worked. They knew that they needed to fight for these shards. Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon was gone, so now it was time for them to fight.

Spirit Guidance! Ice Talisman!

Tian Sen's Peaceful Hermit moved first. He tossed his scythe, which landed on the ground along with an Ice Talisman. A ring of ice was just about to spread out, when a pillar of fire shot up from the same spot! Raging Flames! Team Misty Rain had been prepared. Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain had practically casted the spell at the same time.

Ice and fire crossed. The two elements restrained each other, neither attack greater than the other. Raging Flame's fire pillar didn't last for even a second before it disappeared. The Ice Talisman's ice ring failed to spread outwards and disappeared along with the fire pillar.

Following afterwards, the two sides attacked each other fiercely. Team Misty Rain had no healer, so they couldn't fight head to head with Royal Style. Their long-ranged attackers coordinated with one another, while Liu Hua's Ninja weaved around. This type of playstyle was Team Misty Rain's distinguishing style. Only this time, they had no healer and instead had a long-ranged attacker. Their offensive was more powerful, but they needed to be more careful in protecting themselves.

"So they've finally started fighting. Time to run!"

Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon started moving. This was the brilliant spot he had chosen. He knew that the two pro teams would quickly realize that he had disappeared with Stealth. If he went to look for any hiding places, he would definitely be forced out by the enemies, so he simply stood there in place and gambled on it.

Fang Rui's gamble paid off. The two teams were searching around the exit and failed to find him. The two then started attacking each other. Fang Rui was carefully weaving past the fires of the battle. Even though Wind Howl only had one person remaining, Fang Rui felt like they hadn't lost yet because the remaining teams would have to fight each other. After the teams killed one another, perhaps there might be an opportunity for him to finish it off?

Doubtful Demon slowly left the battle, but he wasn't willing to go too far. He wanted to see what the outcome of the battle would be. Perhaps there was an opportunity there. He slowly retreated, looking for a safe place to peep at the battle. As he backed up, he discovered that he had backed up into a group of people.　

Fuck!

Fang Rui suddenly fumed. He was just one person playing dirty, but Happy was going too far. All five of them were playing dirty. They were all shamelessly hiding in a corner, waiting to reap the benefiits.　

Too shameless!

Fang Rui cursed inwardly, but he didn't dare challenge Happy's five players. He took advantage of the fact that Happy hadn't discovered him yet and tried to leave.　

Fang Rui had wanted to quietly move his Doubtful Demon away, when he suddenly heard a click from underneath his feet.

A trap had locked up his foot. Doubtful Demon's stealth wore off.

"What the fuck?" Steamed Bun cried out in surprise, seeing a person suddenly appear out of nowhere.

"Shhh. He's here to send us his shard." Ye Xiu said calmly.

Chapter 1114: Dangerous Game

"Shameless!!" Fang Rui immediately shouted, after being caught in the trap.

Was he really angry enough to resort to such an outburst? Of course not. He already knew that there was absolutely no way for him to escape, but he refused to let Happy get away with this so easily. By yelling, he hoped that he could catch the attention of Misty Rain and Royal Style, drawing them over here to impede Happy's progress.

"Hahaha, go ahead and shout all you want, you can shout until you go hoarse and no one will hear." Ye Xiu said accompanied by a smirking emoji. Fang Rui turned his camera. It was true, there was no use! They were too far away, not to mention that they were fiercely fighting, with all sorts of sound effects from the skills they used. The sound of his voice had no way of carrying all the way over there.

"Kill him quickly!" Ye Xiu ordered, his Lord Grim acting first. A Back Throw pushed Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon into a dark corner, and the other four members of Happy weren't as polite as they unleashed a barrage of attacks on him. Fang Rui noticed that these guys were avoiding loud and flashy skills, instead using silent and subtle ones - they intended to smother him here.

Fang Rui was upset, but what could he do? No matter his skill, no matter his status as the master of playing dirty, there was simply no way for him to escape from this corner after being surrounded by five pros.

Doubtful Demon fell. Now, Team Wind Howl was completely wiped out.

The shard that Wind Howl had obtained was held by Doubtful Demon, as expected. Fang Rui had gone through great struggles to protect this shard, using all of his shameless tactics to escape from tight spots, but in the end, Happy snatched it just like that.

Fang Rui shook his head and let out a sigh, then stood up and stretched his arms. He glanced around the room, and saw Zhao Yuzhe still shooting glares at him out of the corner of his eye.

Fang Rui could only smile bitterly. He was a veteran player, having played for many years now, and the problems that Liu Hao had noticed, he understood even more clearly.

After Tang Hao had joined Wind Howl, it seemed as though Wind Howl's strength vastly increased, and they had even made it to the semifinals last season. However, Fang Rui's capabilities in this team had been suppressed. His dirty playstyle was entirely opposed to Tang Hao's playstyle, as well as that of the newcomer Zhao Yuzhe.

As time went on, he felt like more and more of a stranger to Wind Howl. They'd gotten through last season like this, but the problem was very apparent. Fang Rui felt it. Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe felt too. How could the club managers not have noticed either?

Fang Rui remembered how the club had acted when encouraging Lin Jingyan to retire last year, and he felt lost as to what his own future now looked like. Seeing the dissatisfaction that both Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe displayed toward him, Fang Rui felt that his footsteps toward the exit were only quickening. Tang Hao was the now core of Wind Howl. Zhao Yuzhe had a good future ahead of him and was being looked after heavily. Fang Rui had no chance of winning this battle. Should he just back off? Accept Wind Howl's new style?

Unfortunately, Fang Rui had been playing dirty for so many years. These skills and instincts had been thoroughly ingrained into him. To have him follow Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe, the fierce and direct playstyle of these youths, he simply couldn't do it. His class wasn't suited for it either.

It looked like his time was up…

In the training room, Tang Hao stood up, Zhao Yuzhe stood up, and the rest of the players followed, returning to their rooms to rest. Fang Rui tilted his neck back and stared at the ceiling. For these people who spent their lives in the game, this was the sky they saw the most often, the ceiling lights acting as their starlight. After so many years, he was used to this sight. But now, it looked like he would be saying goodbye to this piece of sky.

Let's take things one step at a time!

Fang Rui shut off his computer. As the last one to leave the practice room, he didn't forget to turn off all the lights and power.

Wind Howl withdrew from the event, but the battle in the Ghost Lair continued. Happy now had two shards, and they were in a good position as they watched the ongoing battle without either of the two sides knowing. Right now, the most important thing was patience, patience to wait until these two teams beat themselves bloody.

This wasn't a competition where the goal was to kill the opponent. In this competition, there was only one goal: shards!

A shard could only be held by one character on the opposing team, so in this battle, the strategy of attacking everyone and defending everyone wasn't used. Instead, both sides directed all of their attacks onto one target at a time. Kill one, see if they held a shard. If obtained, then retreat, if not, then repeat the process.

Ye Xiu hoped that both sides protected their shards well, that way more characters would be killed off one by one as each team tried to find the other's. At the same time, he was also studying the battle closely, seeing if he could guess from their movements which characters held their respective teams' shards.

"Did you find anything?" Su Mucheng asked, as she too watched the battle.

"Hm, there's nothing stand-out about Royal Style. They're protecting their healer, but that's to be expected. The healer could have the shard, though, so protecting him would serve two purposes," Ye Xiu said.

"So Misty Rain is currently targeting Gentle Angel," Su Mucheng said. Gentle Angel was the name of Royal Style's Paladin. As a healer, this sort of sweet and pleasant name was relatively common. This character was also a female character, and its previous owner was female. But now, the owner had changed. Ren Junchi, a manly man, but with an account called Gentle Angel. Just looking at the conflict of these names, it was fairly clear what kind of person this player was.

"Yes, exactly. It's more difficult to judge Misty Rain's side though. The four long-ranged attackers have the safety of distance, and Li Hua's Ninja is nimble and evasive, the shard could easily be on any of them. Using what you know about Chu Yunxiu, who do you think she would have assigned the shard to?" Ye Xiu said.

"Like you said, it could be anyone," Su Mucheng said.

"Alright." Ye Xiu was helpless. The current situation couldn't be considered too good.

"Better pay attention closely. If Royal Style did give it to Gentle Angel, and he's killed first by Misty Rain and drops it…" Ye Xiu trailed off. That would be the worst outcome for these lurkers. They were hoping for both sides to suffer heavy damage, so if only one person died before the battle finished, they wouldn't be at as large of an advantage.

"Footsteps!" Tang Rou suddenly said.

"Huh? Where?" Ye Xiu immediately asked. After all, Tang Rou's ears had been trained professionally and were sharper than those of anyone else here.

"From the way we came!" Tang Rou said.

"I didn't hear anything?" Steamed Bun was still confused, controlling his Steamed Bun Invasion to crouch on the ground, turning this way and that as he pressed his ear to the ground.

This seemed to be the legendary "ear to the ground" listening method, Steamed Bun must have have learned it from somewhere. But would Glory have this sort of mechanism? Ye Xiu, the man titled the "Glory Textbook," made a face at Steamed Bun's idiocy.

"From the way we came." Tang Rou confirmed.

"It's Tyranny!" Ye Xiu said. It couldn't be anyone else but Tyranny.

With this, Happy was stuck in the middle. On one side, there was the fierce battle between two teams, and on the other side there was the rapidly approaching Tyranny. Happy had no way out. Although their current position hid them from the two fighting teams, there was no way they could evade the notice of Tyranny unless they were completely oblivious or distracted.

"Prepare for battle…" Ye Xiu was helpless. For another team to come from behind, they really were unlucky here.

Right now, should they try to keep their battle with Tyranny separate from the ongoing one, or should they try to group all four teams together into a one big chaotic free-for-all? Ye Xiu thought rapidly, and eventually reached a decision. A huge four-way battle like that would be disadvantageous to the parties without healers, which included Happy. Plus, Happy had three rookies who lacked experience and judgment. In such a chaotic battle, they would certainly fare worse than the more experienced pros.

Better keep the two battles separate!

Ye Xiu led his team out of the corner to advance towards where Tyranny was approaching from, to further separate themselves from Misty Rain and Royal Style so that they wouldn't discover their battle here.

The footsteps grew closer and closer, until finally, the silhouettes of Tyranny's five finally appeared in their view.

"Don't act rashly, follow my lead," Ye Xiu said in the team channel.

It could be said that there were no secrets between the Ye Xiu and Tyranny's old veterans. They understood each other extremely well, having fought for so many years, and it would be difficult for either side to surprise the other. With no surprises, then there was only direct confrontation left as an option. But Happy was much weaker than Tyranny. Ye Xiu would have to figure out some sort of tactic if they were to survive this.

Tyranny's five, upon seeing Happy's five, came to a stop. The two sides had already identified each other. Ye Xiu heard someone on Tyranny say, exasperated, "How come it's you guys again?"

"The feeling is mutual," Ye Xiu said.

Right after saying that, Ye Xiu heard the sound of an explosion from behind him.

He knew that there was a fierce battle ongoing back there, and he didn't want Tyranny to find out, so he arranged their meeting a little farther away. They shouldn't have been able to hear the battle from here, but that explosion… The battle over there, was it moving?

Ye Xiu heard the sound, so of course Tyranny heard as well.

"Flash Bullet? Who's over there?" Zhang Jiale immediately recognized the sound effect of one of his Spitfire skills.

"Royal Style it seems." Zhang Xinjie immediately made this judgment. Flash Bullet, a Spitfire skill. Among the 25 players who entered the Ghost Lair, there were only two Spitfires, Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and Chen Wanhe's Flash Save.

"Who are they fighting?" Zhang Jiale asked.

"Misty Rain?" The sound of numerous bullets gave them their answer. Only Misty Rain had brought three Sharpshooters.

How did the fight between those two teams move all the way over here? Ye Xiu was quickly thinking over this question - but in an instant, he understood.

It was Fang Rui!

That guy, harming others even without any benefit to himself! Before he died, he must have sent a message to those two teams telling them that Happy was over here waiting for an opportunity. Since everyone was using their professional accounts this time, they had each other added as friends and it was easy enough to send a message like this to them.

So these two teams pretended to fight, either trying to pull Happy into some kind of trap, or steadily approaching Happy until they could suddenly turn and attack them. In any case, they weren't going to let Happy just wait for easy pickings.

As expected of the master of playing dirty, he had played a dangerous game that could have backfired.

Messages were very easy to send, but Happy had forgotten this point. Good thing that Tyranny had come and caused a change in plans, otherwise who knew what would have happened?

Chapter 1115: What Kind of Line-up Is This?

Misty Rain and Royal Style's battle was approaching. It seemed like these two teams were preparing to fake their battle to paralyze Happy, then, once they were close enough, surround Happy and team up to attack them. But now that Ye Xiu saw their plan, the paralysis was broken. He obviously wasn't just going to wait for them to come.

Except now, Happy was trapped in between three teams and was unable to do anything. If Ye Xiu were on Tyranny and saw Misty Rain and Royal Style's intent, he wouldn't hesitate to team up with them right here and ruthlessly destroy Happy in a 3v1 before anything else.

What to do?

Ye Xiu's mind worked rapidly. At the same time, he looked around to observe the situation, and suddenly realized that Tyranny, upon discovering a battle up ahead, looked like they were subtly trying to retreat.

Avoiding the battle first? Then coming back to pick off whoever was left?

That was too naive! They were already exposed to Happy, how could Happy let them peacefully stand to the side and watch? Trying to retreat now would only make them suffer what would have originally been Happy's fate: being crushed by the other three teams.

Such a simple logic, how would Tyranny's old foxes be unable to see it?

In that instant, one possibility flashed through Ye Xiu's mind: had these guys still not discovered what the goal of the Ghost Lair dungeon was?

Because if that were the case, Tyranny still didn't know what the teams were supposed to be doing in this dungeon. And so they acted the same as when they had first met up with Happy, preferring to be cautious and avoid conflict, because they still had no idea why they should be fighting.

To this, Ye Xiu could only feel regret, even if it was a regret layered with elation. Luck was really a fickle thing. After obtaining a shard, the situation in the Ghost Lair was obvious. Happy, Wind Howl, Royal Style, and Misty Rain were all fighting for their lives, which showed that they all understood the point of this dungeon, and that they had all managed to obtain a shard. But Tyranny… It seemed like they still hadn't encountered a mini-boss and obtained a shard, so they still had no idea what was going on in this dungeon.

"Why are Misty Rain and Royal Style fighting?" Ye Xiu didn't waste any time, acting dumb to gauge how much the Tyranny members actually knew. Of course, on their own side, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Mo Fan didn't have experience in this sort of tactical competition, so they would probably be confused. Ye Xiu immediately sent a reminder in the team channel, so that they wouldn't expose his act.

"Unclear." Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie answered.

"There must be some special reason," Ye Xiu said.

"Obviously." Zhang Jiale said.

"Let's retreat first, move quickly," Ye Xiu called.

Tyranny immediately retreated the way they came, which showed that this had been their intent all along. Ye Xiu let out a long breath. They were too lucky! Happy was now, like Tyranny, a team that didn't know anything, and so together they could temporarily avoid conflict.

Two teams, ten people together they headed down the tunnel, putting some distance between them and the battle between Royal Style and Misty Rain.

"Let them fight first. And then we…" Ye Xiu sent a few laughing emojis.

"Shameless!" Zhang Jiale said.

"Dirty!" Lin Jingyan said.

"You aren't going?" Ye Xiu asked.

Tyranny fell silent, because there wasn't a good answer to that question. How could they not go? Up until now, they still hadn't figured out the goal of this dungeon, but Misty Rain and Royal Style's fight should give them the answer. But if they revealed this now, there would probably be negative consequences for them, so the best plan was to wait for the other teams to destroy each other and then go in.

And so Tyranny avoided directly answering Ye Xiu's question.

"How come they seem to be getting closer? How are these two teams fighting?" Lin Jingyan said, listening to the sounds of the battle.

"Did they discover us?" Ye Xiu pretended to be shocked.

In reality he was very clear, the situation was like this exactly because those two teams hadn't discovered them here. Royal Style and Misty Rain received Fang Rui's message and knew that Happy was waiting somewhere for an opportunity, so they pretended to fight fiercely as they moved in this direction to surprise and block off Happy. But the two teams still hadn't found any sign of Happy.

Was Fang Rui lying?

Even though this guy liked to play dirty, there was no reason for him to lie to Misty Rain and Royal Style like this. So they were fairly certain that Fang Rui's information was correct.

Then, there was only one explanation: Happy had figured out their intentions and were avoiding them.

This upset the two teams.

Happy avoided them, but would they stay away forever? Knowing that these two teams would fight sooner or later, would they just hang around to wait for their chance? The two teams couldn't decide what to do, and there was no further instruction, so they could only continue their pretend fight. When they arrived at where Fang Rui had said Happy was hiding, the two teams saw that there was only one path Happy could have taken from there.

The two teams decided that, without knowing Happy's whereabouts or status, they had no way of confidently fighting. But since the situation had already gotten to this point, there was no reason to continue the pretense, so the teams stopped their fighting, and began to charge down the path.

"Huh, they stopped?"

The sounds of battle suddenly stopped, coming as a surprise to Tyranny.

"They finished fighting? They shouldn't have!" Zhang Jiale said. Just then, there had been the sounds of all sorts of skills being used, so clearly there were a good number of players still alive. Was there some giant fire that wiped out all of the characters on one side? That didn't make any sense.

"They must have discovered us and decided to give chase!" Ye Xiu said.

"Who ran so slowly that they saw us?" Lin Jingyan said. Tyranny was still in the dark!

"Why are you still talking? What do we do? Continue to avoid them, or?" Ye Xiu said.

"We'll have to fight sooner or later," Tyranny's Captain Han Wenqing said. They still didn't know the reason for battle, but seeing how Misty Rain and Royal Style were fighting, it seemed like it was an inevitable outcome. So, if they were going to fight anyway, then retreating certainly wasn't Tyranny's style.

"Since it's come to this, then we'll go fight together, catch them while they're disorganized!" Ye Xiu shouted.

Upon hearing this, the Tyranny members agreed. If they were going to fight, then take this chance and fight quickly!

So the ten characters turned around and began charging back the way they came. At this time, Royal Style and Misty Rain had chased them here, and the two sides met. Happy and Tyranny's spirits were fierce and bright, but Royal Style and Misty Rain's spirits were suddenly crushed.

"Oh no! It's a trap!"

The two teams thought this simultaneously.

They had clearly been chasing only Happy here, where did Tyranny suddenly come from? It was originally supposed to be a 10v5, which the two teams felt would be an easy fight, but now it had unexpectedly become a 10v10. They had also spent quite some energy putting on that show of a battle… but even disregarding that, just look at the opposing side's roster.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale, Zhang Xinjie...

What kind of line-up was this? It was enough to make anyone cry! Royal Style and Misty Rain's line-ups weren't weak among the professional teams, but in front of this intimidating list of names, they suddenly seemed pathetic.

Could they fight this battle?

The two teams were still in a shock because of this line-up, but Happy and Tyranny were already upon them, attacking without even a greeting. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain fired a Stinger into the air, which exploded apart and rained down upon the players. To the left, Tang Rou's Soft Mist burst forward with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks. To the right, Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms covered a path with a display of light and shadows, into which Han Wenqing's Desert Dust disappeared. When he emerged again, it was with a Ferocious Tiger Flurry sweeping right into the heart of the opponents' ranks.

Happy and Tyranny's allied assault was too ferocious, too relentless, too powerful. Royal Style and Misty Rain originally thought they had the initiative when giving chase, but now they couldn't find their pace at all.

Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had also charged into battle, but his eyes, instead of being fixed on his battle target, were continuously moving about, analyzing the field. Ye Xiu was confident that in this situation, where the opponents were on the defensive, it would be easier to see which characters held the shards. These players would be at the center of their teams' adjustments.

Soon enough, Ye Xiu saw the clues.

Even though they had been caught by surprise, in the end these were professional teams, and there was order to their chaos. Misty Rain, for one, was trying to increase the distance between themselves and the others. The three Sharpshooters and Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain were continuously retreating, and the crossfire pattern made by the three Sharpshooters clearly served to protect one character in particular - Windy Rain. As for Royal Style, they didn't have such a sharp change in their battle pattern, but they continued to focus on protecting their healer Gentle Angel.

The answer was right there. For Ye Xiu, these were crucial clues, but Tyranny… it was a shame that they still didn't know about the shards. From their perspective, Royal Style's protection of their healer was a perfectly normal action, and Misty Rain using their Sharpshooters to cover Windy Rain also wasn't out of the ordinary. The Sharpshooters had much better mobility than an Elementalist, so this sort of retreat would of course involve the Sharpshooters helping out the Elementalist more.

After Ye Xiu determined who held the shards, he immediately informed his team through the team channel, but he didn't make any adjustments to the battle strategy. They were currently teamed up with Tyranny, whose primary goal was to wipe out every opponent, so for now they could only pay closer attention to these two targets.

Misty Rain, who lacked a healer, was currently in a much worse situation than Royal Style was. Additionally, in a chaotic 20-person battle, their long-range attackers didn't have enough space to maintain a safe distance and move around easily. Ye Xiu saw that they were trying to escape, and immediately ordered Happy to block their path of retreat, and at the same time loudly shouted at Tyranny, reminding them not to let the fish slip through the net.

Upon hearing this, Misty Rain and Royal Style became angry.

True, they weren't in a good situation right now, but up until now none of their characters had fallen. The battle was in a stalemate right now, it was far from the point where victory or defeat was apparent.

Fish slipping through the net? What are you talking about? Who's the net and who's the fish?

The dissatisfaction caused by Ye Xiu's words caused the fighting spirit of Misty Rain and Royal Style to suddenly spike. Multiple players suddenly started playing at a higher, fiercer level than before, suddenly stabilizing their positions.

"Can you shut up!" Seeing this, Tyranny seethed. This trash-talk, instead of crushing the opponents' spirits, served the opposite purpose! Misty Rain and Royal Style, in a disadvantageous position, had been hesitant with their attacks, but now that Ye Xiu said this, they were like fish fighting to the death to break free of the net. Because these two teams knew that Wind Howl was done for, and all that was left were the four teams right here. Might as well use this one battle to decide a winner once and for all!

With this thought, the two teams began to counterattack, with each player experiencing a small surge in power. And, as the battle rhythm shifted, the protection of their important characters inadvertently slipped, just the tiniest bit.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

At this moment, Ye Xiu sinisterly unleashed his ultimate move...

Chapter 1116: Duped

Cloud Grasping Fist!

Lord Grim's actions were sneaky to the extreme. He had made his way to Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, borrowing the flashiness of his attacks as cover.

Just looking at Ye Xiu's shameless sneakiness, Zhang Jiale was sorely tempted to toss a grenade to send this guy straight into the midst of Dazzling Hundred Blossom's attacks. Just kill him and be done with it. But then he remembered that they were supposed to be working together, and so he resisted the temptation.

Ye Xiu notice Royal Style's shift in tempo shifted and seized it, using the Hundred Blossom cover to launch a sneak attack. Royal Style was completely unprepared. As for Ye Xiu, it was actually quite tricky to accurately attack while under the cover of Hundred Blossom's light and shadows. This was a detail easily overlooked.

Royal Style's Ren Junchi understood that the victor of this dungeon could be determined with this one battle, and so he was supporting his teammates with all his strength, assisting their counterattack. But all of a sudden, his character was moving forward out of his control. Ren Junchi was confused, but he suddenly realized what had happened.

"Oh shit!" Ren Junchi only had time to give a shout to warn his teammates, but everyone's reactions were too slow. They could only watch, wide-eyed, as Ren Junchi's Gentle Angel was suddenly dragged from their sides, into the midst of Dazzling Hundred Blossom's attack range.

"Save him!" Tian Sen immediately shouted, already waving the scythe in his hand and sending several Lightning Talismans flying in the direction Gentle Angel had been grabbed. Before he reached the enemy ranks, first use some attacks to disrupt the enemy's rhythm.

But Ye Xiu was prepared. He directly pulled Gentle Angel out of the Hundred Blossoms Style cover, and with a Fling, Lord Grim sent Gentle Angel farther away.

"Fuck!" Zhang Jiale cursed.

Ye Xiu hadn't even warned him that he was going to do this, after flinging Gentle Angel, Ye Xiu just patted his butt and left. Meanwhile, Royal Style was still furiously trying to rescue their healer, and Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was about to take the brunt of their fury.

"What's wrong with you!" Zhang Jiale yelled.

"You can take care of this. I believe in you!" Ye Xiu replied as Lord Grim quickly made his escape.

Zhang Jiale was helpless; he couldn't just retreat. Once Royal Style saw that their healer had been sent somewhere else, he would probably have to stop them. And the other members of Tyranny, upon seeing that Ye Xiu had captured Royal Style's healer, would of course have to cooperate to take out the healer.

On Happy's side, Ye Xiu had already prepared for them to receive the healer even before he went to grab him. Once he threw the healer over there, a barrage of attacks fell upon the healer. Under this fierce assault, how long could a healer last? Royal Style's rescue team couldn't make it over in time and Misty Rain's attack strategy relied on distance, so they didn't have the power to charge in.

In the midst of chaotic battle, Gentle Angel fell. Tyranny's members were pleased, but none of them noticed that in the crowd of Happy members around the fallen player, someone plucked an item from the ground beside Gentle Angel.

Tyranny was in the dark, but Royal Style was clear on the situation. Right now, they had neither healer nor shard, and they suddenly unleashed the ferocity of a team that had nothing to lose. But Tyranny's experts were experienced with this sort of sudden shift in tempo, and this change didn't throw them off. They were temporarily beaten back by Royal Style, but soon enough they stabilized and counterattacked, defeating another Royal Style player, Xu Huiliu's Striker.

Royal Style was being thoroughly routed, and Misty Rain faltered as well, as the pressure of the attacks on them increased. Their long-ranged attacks simply had no way of countering the explosive power of Happy and Tyranny.

"It's time, charge!" Ye Xiu ordered. This time, he wasn't mounting a sneak attack, Lord Grim was playing a direct attacker. Together with Tang Rou's Soft Mist, they launched an assault that would deal the death blow to Misty Rain.

With Tyranny's attacks restricting their movements, Misty Rain no longer had enough room to maneuver. The long-range attackers couldn't do anything as Ye Xiu and Tang Rou's characters closed the distance. Their formation was instantly broken apart.

"Beautiful. Working with you guys is great! You haven't let me down!" Ye Xiu praised loudly. When Happy attacked, Tyranny's coordinated support had been the key to knocking down Misty Rain; without them, it still would have been possible for Misty Rain to defend.

"Shut up, will you!" Tyranny, of course, didn't need any of Ye Xiu's praise.

"Keep working hard!" Ye Xiu called. On Happy's side, their attacks were clearly targeting one character, Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain. After they had blown apart Misty Rain's formation, the other players were seemingly forgotten.

But Chu Yunxiu wouldn't be going down that easily. With a Teleport, the Elementalist instantly escaped from Happy's attacks, travelling to a place where it'd be the most difficult for Happy to readjust their formation and continue attacking.

But as soon as Windy Rain reappeared, a Satellite Beam fell from the sky. This was an attack made by correctly predicting the exact location at which Windy Rain would teleport to.

Chu Yunxiu immediately realized she had fallen for the trap. Happy had known that she would try to teleport to escape, and they had purposely left that opening for her to jump to. And the Launcher's extremely long range allowed her to instantly cover any corner of the battlefield.

Caught by the Satellite Beam, Windy Rain couldn't move, and two shadows suddenly appeared by her right and left.

Lord Grim and Deception, two Shadow Clones. Even though they couldn't travel as far as a Teleport, it was an instant movement technique too, and there was no faster way to close the distance to an opponent.

Afterwards, Windy Rain was grabbed by Lord Grim, and with another Fling, was sent to where Happy wanted. Misty Rain's three Sharpshooters pounced on them in an attempt to save their captain. Li Hua directly used a Shadow Dance with his Dark Forest, acting like a whole army of troops to try and disrupt Happy.

"Help please!" Ye Xiu shouted, of course not to Happy, but to Tyranny.

"You hold your position, throw Windy Rain over here!" Tyranny answered.

This sentence was really a lucky hit. Tyranny of course didn't know about the shard held by Windy Rain, but in the current situation, sending Windy Rain over to their side was just one logical option. After all, even though the teams were allied, they could still take damage from each other, so executing a combined attack would require extremely careful coordination. For example, when Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had stolen away Gentle Angel, he had to hide behind the Hundred Blossoms display, unlike the Tyranny members who could dive directly into the lights and shadows.

As soon as Tyranny proposed this plan, they prepared to receive the target, but when they looked over, they saw that Lord Grim and Steamed Bun invasion were still fiercely engaging in battle with Windy Rain! Besides these two characters, the others didn't have Fling! It seemed that tossing a character over wasn't very convenient for Happy.

There was no other option, Tyranny had to change their plans. It was just a small thing, not enough to pose any difficulty for them. To supplement Happy's attacks without disrupting their rhythm - that was something they could do.

Under Happy and Tyranny's partnership, the situation stabilized. Windy Rain was caught in between the two teams, and her health bar was plummeting. The three Sharpshooters and the Ninja persevered in their attacks, and Chu Yunxiu coordinated with them as she fought back, but in the end they still were unable to rescue her.

No solution!

After fighting to this extent, both Misty Rain and Royal Style wanted to retreat. If they continued fighting, they would all die here and that would be the end, but if they retreated now and preserved their health, there would still be a bit of hope left.

Both teams wanted to withdraw for now, but now Tyranny was making things difficult. They still didn't know about the shards, so they just wanted to wipe out the two teams entirely. Although they were currently partnered with Happy to crush their opponents, they were still calculating their chances as they compared the states of their two teams. Tyranny had a healer, while Happy didn't. Although Tyranny had supported Happy in their attacks, Zhang Xinjie hadn't let a single heal fall upon any of Happy's members, even though there was nothing in the system stopping him from doing so.

After fighting Misty Rain and Royal Style, Tyranny and Happy would inevitably turn on each other. But one side had a healer while the other didn't, which alone was enough to tip the scales. After defeating those two teams, Tyranny was prepared to seize this opportunity to take care of Happy as well.

Tyranny's ultimate goal was the total annihilation of all three other teams, a much more ambitious goal than the others. Royal Style and Misty Rain wanted to retreat now, but Tyranny wasn't about to let that happen. They would bite down hard, and not let go.

So they caught Royal Style, but there was a hole in Happy's trap for Misty Rain. Just as they killed Windy Rain, the other four members chose to retreat.

"Where are you running!" Ye Xiu yelled. "Give chase!" As he spoke, he led Happy to furiously pursue the retreating team.

"This guy did that on purpose, didn'the?" Seeing this, Tyranny's players began to discuss among themselves.

"It's clear, he's defending against us…" Zhang Xinjie sighed. He hadn't given Happy's side a single heal. Looking back, that must have made their intent too obvious.

"That guy's just too sneaky." Zhang Jiale shook his head.

"I say… Happy's already gotten away with all of the shards, why are you guys still being so kind to them?" Royal Style's three players couldn't last much longer. Once they saw that Misty Rain's members had run, and Tyranny was still attacking them, they were helpless. Tian Sen had no idea that Tyranny still didn't know about the shards; he thought that Tyranny was trying to shake a shard out of these three players. But the issue was, their team's shard had already been dropped by Gentle Angel! Thinking about how Tyranny was wasting their time, but was in such a relaxed mood, Tian Sen couldn't resist any longer and exposed the truth.

"Shards? What shards?" After Tyranny's five heard this, they were startled.

"Fuck, no way?" Tian Sen was shocked. These Tyranny brothers still didn't know what was going on?

Tian Sen quickly explained the situation in the dungeon. Once Tyranny heard this, of course they understood what had happened. They had been duped by Happy.

"Hurry and give chase!" Han Wenqing ordered, and Tyranny turned their fire.

Chapter 1117: Catching Dark Forest

"Hurry and give chase!" Han Wenqing ordered. Royal Style's three players let out a breath for it seemed like they were saved. They could wait for Tyranny and Happy to fight it out, and maybe it'd be another devastating battle, providing them with an opportunity.

But soon enough, the three realized that they had misunderstood.

The "hurry" in Tyranny's statement included killing them.

Then again, it made sense. Tian Sen admitted that their shard had already been stolen by Happy, but Tyranny had no way of verifying that this was the truth unless they killed all three of them to see if any of them were still holding a shard. They had already been fighting for so long that it wouldn't take very long for them to kill three players.

Royal Style thought that they could relax, but ended up being the first victims of Tyranny's rage at Happy.

Tian Sen was helpless, Chen Wanhe was helpless, He Weitang was helpless. The three players fell, and Royal Style was officially wiped out.

Tian Sen had been telling the truth when he said that they didn't have a shard. Their shard was indeed on Gentle Angel, who had dropped it to Happy.

To this, Tyranny was somewhat regretful, but they weren't annoyed. Royal Style had already been beaten down, but letting them go free would definitely have come back to bite them. Killing them now prevented that possibility from happening in the future.

Now, it was time to chase after Happy.

Happy had claimed they were going to kill Misty Rain, but Tyranny now knew that it was just as likely they had just used the opportunity to escape. Although they didn't know who on Misty Rain held the shard, just from looking at Happy's attack pattern, they were able to guess that Windy Rain had held it. Now that Happy had their shard as well, would they continue to cause trouble for Misty Rain?

Happy wouldn't, but on the other hand, Misty Rain probably wouldn't just let Happy go. Misty Rain couldn't fight against the Tyranny-Happy alliance, but if it were just Happy, Misty Rain had a better chance. Just because they lost a player didn't mean that they couldn't fight. If that were true, then they might as well just withdraw from the game altogether.

Tyranny had been duped, but that was only because they lacked information. Once they understood how the event worked, the logic was as simple as one plus one. After taking care of Royal Style, they would chase in the direction that Happy and Misty Rain had fled. They would hope that these two would fight bitterly, leaving a chance for them to defeat them and take the shards.

Tyranny's thought process was entirely logical.

Misty Rain ran, Happy pursued. After Misty Rain discovered that Happy was the only team chasing them, they suddenly changed their course of thought. Happy had taken quite a bit of damage when killing Gentle Angel and Windy Rain. It was the same situation as when they had killed Tang Hao's Demon Subduer.

It was unfortunate that Misty Rain didn't have a healer, so it was very difficult to recover health during battle. Happy didn't either, but they had Ye Xiu's Lord Grim, who could serve as a healer in a pinch. It would be more disadvantageous for Misty Rain to drag this out longer.

So Misty Rain suddenly stopped running. They turned and began charging back the way they had come.

But this didn't catch Happy by surprise. They entered battle mode smoothly.

"Attack Dark Forest." Ye Xiu had already issued orders in the team channel, so Happy's five members focused all of their attacks onto Dark Forest without holding back.

"They figured it out?" Seeing how he was clearly singled out as the target of attack, Li Hua's heart beat faster.

Yes, Ye Xiu had figured it out. On Misty Rain's side, Chu Yunxiu's Windy Rain hadn't been the only player with a shard. Li Hua's Dark Forest held one as well. Misty Rain had already obtained two shards, which also explained why Tyranny had been unable to find one. There were only five shards, and they were all claimed by four teams. How could there be any left over for Tyranny?

Dark Forest had a shard? Ye Xiu couldn't be a hundred percent certain, of course, but after careful evaluation of battle, he made this judgment, and now, it was time to test his theory.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist was the fastest, separating from the others as she launched her attack. Li Hua frantically controlled Dark Forest to dodge, but unexpectedly, the target of Soft Mist's attack wasn't himself. She travelled right past him with her attack, landing in the midst of the three Sharpshooters. Happy was focusing their attacks on Dark Forest, but they couldn't ignore the three Sharpshooters completely. They still had to give them the necessary attention to stop them.

Steamed Bun accompanied Soft Mist on her path of attack.

Although Tang Rou's forcefulness and Steamed Bun's strangeness weren't enough to directly take down the three Sharpshooters, the chaos they caused was definitely too much for the Sharpshooters to quickly break free. While the two Happy players kept the Sharpshooters busy, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Mo Fan surrounded and prepared to take down Dark Forest.

Ninjas specialized in assassinations and sneak attacks, so they were normally relatively difficult to catch. But it was a shame, for Happy also had a Ninja on their side.

Mo Fan's technique might not be as polished as Li Hua's, but his scrap-picking experience made him particularly skilled in several areas. For example, when tracking a target, not only was he incredibly patient, he was able to focus all of his attention, make good decisions, and maintain precise control of his actions.

Tracking someone while scrap-picking required picking them out from the midst of a chaotic crowd. Right now, however, it was just one opponent to track, and this was an incredibly simple task for Mo Fan.

Li Hua was the number one Ninja in Glory, so he quickly sensed Mo Fan's skill, and didn't underestimate him just because he was a rookie. And then there were the other two opponents, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, the most highly-skilled partners in Glory. Li Hua didn't dare take them lightly; he wanted to withdraw.

This… was perhaps the greatest criticism the Glory world had toward Team Misty Rain: when facing difficult situations, they didn't have the fierce spirit to keep pushing, they would always reveal a thread of weakness. This had become an iconic characteristic of their team.

Ninjas had many escape techniques, and as the number one Ninja, Li Hua's skill in this area was unquestionable. Immediately, Dark Forest tossed a Smoke Bomb, releasing a thick cloud of purple smoke everywhere. Dark Forest vanished in its midst, but he wasn't finished yet. The opponent could no longer direct catch him, but Li Hua didn't rely on his own movements to change coordinates and escape. Instead, using the smoke cover, he simply used a Shadow Clone Technique, hiding his false body in the smoke, while his real body…

His real body was also in a cloud of purple smoke.

Li Hua wanted to cry. This cloud of purple smoke wasn't his, this was the smoke from a Smoke Bomb dropped by Deception. Li Hua couldn't tell where it was dropped, he only knew that he was swallowed within. Originally intended as a technique for escape, this time it was used as a technique to prevent the opponent's escape. Right now, Li Hua had no idea what his surroundings were, and he didn't dare to randomly move around. What if he took two steps out and fell right into Lord Grim's arms?

However, this was also only temporary.

As the number one Ninja, after the Smoke Bomb finished exploding, Li Hua was able to judge from the smoke's thickness where exactly the bomb had been placed. From that, he knew which direction would be the fastest way to travel out of the cloud of smoke.

But, this could all too easily be a trap. Taking the shortest path, Li Hua felt that he was bound to be caught by Happy.

Walk in the opposite direction, then? But what if it was reverse psychology?

Fine! There were more than two directions, so he would take neither the shortest nor the longest, but instead a direction chosen at random - Happy couldn't predict randomness, could they?

Indeed, Happy had no way of predicting a randomly chosen path. After Deception tossed the Smoke Bomb, they surrounded the cloud entirely, the five characters forming a circle. No matter where Dark Forest exited, they could immediately attack him. Although it wouldn't be enough firepower to directly kill him, it would at least prevent his escape.

So when Dark Forest finally emerged from the smoke, a sword was already flashing toward him.

Your defense isn't enough!

This was Li Hua's immediate judgment. If he was only being attacked from one angle, even if it were Ye Xiu, he believed that he could escape. Unfortunately, just as the sword was about to land, Li Hua heard an explosion above him. Lifting his head, he saw a Stinger explode in the air, sending countless bits of shrapnel raining down towards him.

Dancing Rain.

Su Mucheng.

Su Mucheng of course was not the only Launcher in the Alliance, but she was absolutely the best at executing this type of supportive attack. Her timing and control were outstanding, resulting in this surprise effect.

Su Mucheng was a true expert of restriction. She restricted not just the actions of one player in particular, but the entire battlefield. Her playstyle took full advantage of the Launcher's excellent range.

If the player's skill wasn't up to par, then even if the playstyle were the same, the demonstrated power and efficacy would of course differ. Su Mucheng was the number one in Glory at this Screen Cannon style.

Excellent Era had been relegated this year, and the Pro Alliance had almost forgotten the power of this Screen Cannon. In fact, shortly after Ye Xiu retired, it seemed as though Su Mucheng had weakened greatly. Those who didn't understand thought that Ye Xiu's retirement had affected Su Mucheng's state of mind, but those who understood knew that this restriction style, meant as a coordination with one's teammates, also in turn required the teammates to coordinate with the restriction, seizing the opportunity to kill.

Su Mucheng could coordinate with her teammates, but the return coordination she received was lacking. Because of this, it naturally seemed as though her power was lacking.

This sort of perfect partnership and coordination, how long had it been since they'd seen this? Li Hua didn't have time to consider this question, because he was about to be played to death by this partnership.

The partnership between one close and one far successfully immobilized him, and a second later, Mo Fan's Deception arrived as well. In a 1v3 situation, Li Hua couldn't find an escape route, and it wasn't Misty Rain's habit to explode with power in the face of struggle. The three Sharpshooters tried to help, but Happy already had Li Hua firmly under their control, and didn't mind suffering some damage.

Kill!

At this moment, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun both turned their attacks on Dark Forest as well. Misty Rain lacked a healer, and Ninjas weren't a durable class, and there was no escape route, and there was no way to pull off a sudden explosive turnaround. At last, Dark Forest fell, and, as Ye Xiu predicted, he dropped a shard.

"Retreat!"

Happy had obtained all five shards, so they had no reason to continue fighting with Misty Rain's three remaining Sharpshooters. Ye Xiu immediately directed his team to withdraw.

Chapter 1118: Split Up

Happy wanted to run. That was their current goal, but Misty Rain still had three players left and they weren't easy to escape from. Fortunately, there was a bit of internal conflict going on outside the game between the three remaining Misty Rain players.

Lu Yining had been crowned season eight's Best Sixth Player. He was a very dependable player, but right now, his position in Misty Rain was somewhat awkward. He was likely to leave this summer. And the ones to push him into this situation were Shu Keyi and Shu Kexin, the two sisters.

It wasn't possible for Lu Yinning to not have any opinions about this matter. Not only were Shu Keyi and She Kexin new rookies, they were also quite arrogant. It could be said that Lu Yining didn't have any good feelings towards them.

At the moment, Misty Rain was fighting to improve their team's hardware. Lu Yining was about to leave. His participation in this event had been forced to begin with. He just didn't want his emotions to ruin his reputation. Misty Rain was in a difficult situation right now, but hoping for Lu Yining to cooperate with Shu Keyi and Shu Kexin to turn this situation around was quite optimistic.

When Happy retreated, Shu Keyi and Shu Kexin tried their best, shooting at them as they chased. For these sisters, a defeat in this dungeon and to Happy at that felt like deja vu. In last year's Christmas event, the two sisters had planned on using the leaderboards to make a name for themselves. Unfortunately, they were defeated by Ye Xiu multiple times in succession. In the end, even though they had been noticed by the pro scene, the results didn't meet their expectations.

This time, they had come out to strengthen their team. Misty Rain's luck was quite good. They encountered two minibosses and obtained two shards, making them the team in the lead. However, they were once again thwarted by Happy.

They only had three players right now. Besides Happy, there was also a powerful opponent like Tyranny glaring at them like a tiger watching its prey. The two sisters had been a part of pro scene for half a year now. They knew how powerful the pro teams were and no longer had the naive confidence in thinking that they could challenge Tyranny by themselves. They didn't have any confidence in challenging Happy either, but they couldn't swallow their anger. They had to at least try.

Bullets flew.

The two Sharpshooters fired their guns as they chased after Happy. Lu Yining was in no mood to fight, but he had to at least show a bit of effort. As a result, he also shot at Happy as he ran, but he clearly wasn't being very diligent about it.　　

The two sisters quickly noticed his listless attacks.

"Can't you try harder!" Shu Keyi expressed her dissatisfaction.

"Hmph." Lu Yining replied with his nose. Sure enough, he tried harder. He tried even harder to sandbag.

The two sisters saw this. He was deliberately opposing them! There was nothing they could do though. They had heard the rumors going around in their club and knew Lu Yining definitely didn't have any favorable opinions towards them. The two were helpless. They hadn't specifically joined Misty Rain to kick Lu Yining from his position. Everyone played the same class, so it would be hard to avoid competition between them. Someone's spot had to be taken, so someone would naturally have to leave. The two sisters felt like Lu Yining's dislike for them was unprofessional.

The two obviously weren't going to compromise. With their personalities, it would only serve to make them work even harder to let the team know that they had made the correct decision. Shu Keyi complained to Lu Yining, but all it did was make that guy respond even more negatively, so she stopped talking.

Ignore him! We'll do it ourselves!

The two sisters abandoned Lu Yining and attacked Happy even more fiercely. As for Happy, under Ye Xiu's lead, they continued to run while constantly harassing Misty Rain's players.

For them, Misty Rain was no longer a threat. Their only threat was the biggest threat in this dungeon, Team Tyranny, who were probably going after them right now.

Tyranny's misfortune had been Happy's fortune. Because of their good luck, they were able to avoid fighting their biggest threat. Their luck was gone now though. Tyranny must have figured it out by now. Even if they didn't, after beating Royal Style, Tyranny would still chase after them.

So they couldn't stop. They had to keep running!

As for Misty Rain at the rear, Ye Xiu didn't care about them at all because they weren't running from Misty Rain in the first place. Misty Rain just had to have three Sharpshooters though. It was very annoying. The sounds of their gunfire echoed in this underground cavern. If Tyranny wanted to chase after them, they could do so just by following the sound of gunfire.

In the end, Happy had to guard against Tyranny, only Tyranny.　　

Thus, as Happy ran, Ye Xiu took any opportunities that came up to counterattack. If these three tails could be removed, then it'd be best to remove them.

However, the Shu sisters weren't stupid. They realized the crux of the issue. The two had a much clearer understanding of their skill now. Trying to steal the shards with just the two of them would be like trying to steal the sky. In this situation, they needed to rely on Tyranny's help and fish in troubled waters. Happy was running away as fast as possible not because of their fear for the two sisters and that cheerleader, but because of their fear for Tyranny.

The more scared their opponent was of something, the more they needed to help that something. The sisters immediately adjusted their plans. They stopped chasing Happy as closely as before and started being more on the defensive. However, they weren't going to let Happy escape from them either.

Ye Xiu immediately saw through this change. As a result, he promptly made a decision: "Steamed Bun and I will stay. You three go find the Ghost King. Hurry!"

Team Happy split up.

Su Mucheng led Tang Rou and Mo Fan along with the five shards to figure out how to find the Ghost King. Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun stayed behind to block off the passage.

Fortunately, the underground passage was narrow, which made sealing it off that much easier. Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun took the initiative to attack the two sisters.

The two sisters were surprised. They clearly hadn't expected Happy to split up. Even though their side had three players, this underground passage was narrow, making it very difficult for anyone to circle around them. What's more, Lu Yininig was still being very uncooperative with them. The two sisters had almost forgotten that their side had three people.

"Steamed Bun, you take the left. I'll take the right." Ye Xiu instructed. With his sinister eyes, he had noticed that Lu Yining was intentionally sandbagging. Even if Team Misty Rain frequently dropped the ball in tense situations, it wouldn't so bad that anyone would sandbag. Ye Xiu thought about it and guessed that it was probably unrelated to in-game matters and rather some sort of conflict in the team. As a result, Ye Xiu didn't pay much attention to Lu Yining. Their priorities should be the two sisters. The synergy between those two sisters was quite impressive. There were even people in the scene that predicted these two sisters to be Glory's future Best Partners. Truthfully speaking, Ye Xiu agreed with this view too.

Steamed Bun followed orders. He immediately charged out, while also chatting with Ye Xiu: "Their names seem very familiar."

"They should feel familiar to you." Ye Xiu said.

"Really? Bro, have we met before?" Steamed Bun asked excitedly as he charged towards his opponent --- Shu Kexin's None Dare Attack.

Lower Your Head and None Dare Attack were two male characters. The two sisters had never attempted to hide their genders. Who would have thought that Steamed Bun would forget about them so cleanly. His impression of the two of them were practically zero.

Shu Kexin completely ignored Steamed Bun and attacked him fiercely.　

Steamed Bun might be talking, but his playing wasn't weak. Steamed Bun Invasion twisted and turned. He dodged two shots and suddenly attacked with a Powerful Knee Strike, striking at None Dare Attack.

Ye Xiu wasn't slow either. Lord Grim had started attacking from afar using his umbrella's Gun Form. Mid-range and close-range skills poured out endlessly. Shu Keyi's situation was clearly more difficult than Shu Kexin's.

In these consecutive intense battles without any healers, potions were Misty Rain's only way to heal. But better potions had longer cooldowns. In a pro-level confrontation, relying on potions wasn't reliable. Misty Rain's three players didn't have much health left. And Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun were no longer escaping and instead attacking them proactively. Happy had a cheerleader healer Lord Grim, so their situation was slightly better. In this battle, Happy had the advantage. Lu Yining had to face an opponent now and he responded relatively seriously. It was just that their situation wasn't good. He wasn't able to turn the situation around. As he fought and fought, he concluded that it was impossible to win, so he turned around and ran. However, he still gave out a warning and shouted "I'm retreating."

This was clearly a formality. He wasn't being targeted, so if he wanted to retreat, he could just retreat. But those two sisters had their throats gripped by Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun and were being beaten up! Lu Yining quickly retreated, not even attempting to help protect his teammates.

The two sisters nearly died from anger, but they weren't the types to blame the gods and accuse others. The two tried hard, struggling to break free from their opponent's attacks.

In the end, Steamed Bun wasn't always the most reliable. He messed up and Shu Kexin's none Dare Attack escaped. But unfortunately for Shu Keyi, trying to escape from Ye Xiu and trying to escape from Steamed Bun were two entirely different matters. Shu Kexin obviously wasn't Lu Yining, who ran away on his own. After escaping from Steamed Bun's clutches, she tried to save her sister. But Shu Keyi, who was fighting Lord Grim, knew better how difficult it would be and decisively rejected it: "Forget about me! Run away first and look for an opportunity later!"

Even though the two were sisters, they neatly broke away. There was none of that cheesy drama like "If you're going to die, I'll die with you." After hearing her sister's opinion, she didn't hesitate to turn and run. Ye Xiu obviously wasn't going to let Lower Your Head go and killed her.

"Ya ya ya ya!!" Steamed Bun let None Dare Attack go accidentally. He felt very ashamed and wanted to redeem himself.

"Recover first." Ye Xiu yelled for him to stop.

Lu Yining escaped. Shu Kexin escaped. But she didn't go find Lu Yining. She wasn't placing any hopes on this guy no matter what.

The two characters ran one behind the other. They kept on running around randomly. They turned around and saw that Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion wasn't chasing after them, but there were people ahead of them. Tyranny's five had finally arrived. Lu Yining was running at the front. Before he could greet them, he heard someone from Tyranny say with a voice filled with gratitude: "Over here!"

And then he was killed.

Tyranny was a very decisive team!

Chapter 1119: Catch Up

Misty Rain's two might have ran, but they had been counting on coming back when Tyranny and Happy erupted in conflict so that they could mop up the remains. Unfortunately, they had met Tyranny head on as they turned. There hadn't even been a greeting before Lu Yining's Something To Hide was wiped out.

Shu Kexing's None Dare Attack had been slower, allowing her to live for marginally longer. Seeing the five from Tyranny lunge predatorily, Shu Kexing felt that being over there with Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun was probably better.

"Neither of them have any." Tyranny lamented. They had killed another two, but the ground was still clear of items. They had already asked Royal Style about how this dungeon worked.

Even though Royal Style had been wiped out by Tyranny, everyone was a pro player. If they couldn't accept one loss, then everyone in the Alliance would be sworn enemies with each other. Pro players were able to distinguish between on field and off field situations. Thus, after Tyranny wiped out Royal Style and turned to ask them about Ghost Lair's situation, Royal Style didn't hide anything and told them all they knew.

The list of online characters made things even clearer. Wind Howl and Royal Style had all been kicked from the competition and had left the dungeon. Misty Rain's members were still alive, but could they still succeed in this dungeon?

Tyranny had swiftly ran in the direction that Misty Rain and Happy had gone, soon hearing the sounds of gunshots and following them. That was when they saw Something To Hide and None Dare Attack running towards them. Tyranny didn't show many mercy, crushing them at once. If they let them live, it would just come back to bite them. Tyranny wouldn't back down at all even if it was Happy in front of them.

Having dealt with the two, Tyranny continued to advance. They hadn't gone far before they saw Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion sitting in the tunnel ahead eating bread and drinking juice!

"Someone's here!" Seeing Tyranny, Steamed Bun immediately jumped up off the ground.

"Stay calm, we can recover a little more health and mana!" Ye Xiu was much more nonchalant, allowing Lord Grim to continue eating, his health and mana continuing to rise.

Steamed Bun had always listened to his boss and hastily had Steamed Bun Invasion take out food to continue eating. Seeing the two like this, Tyranny slowed their steps. There was a fork in the road further ahead. Were the other three members of Happy waiting there in ambush?

Tyranny had gone through battle after battle, hurrying over in pursuit after defeating Royal Style. They hadn't the time to sit down and use food to recover their health and mana like Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun, so they weren't in an optimal state. Seeing that Happy seemed to be plotting something, they might not be scared, but they kept their guards up as they began to move themselves into more tactical positions.

Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was a ranged fighter. Seeing how Ye Xiu noticed but ignored their approach, continuing to recover health and mana, he couldn't let this go on and shot at them.

Lord Grim immediately got up and dodged, and his recovery process was interrupted. Zhang Jiale's skills continued to fly over, using his Hundred Blossom's style to pave a way for Tyranny's charge. Ye Xiu didn't dawdle either, getting Steamed Bun to follow him as he turned and ran.

Tyranny couldn't afford to be slow. Regardless of the possibility of an ambush, they had to press forward. But that was when they saw Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly split up at the fork in the road, one swerving left, the other swerving right.

"This…" Tyranny's players weren't sure how to react. They hastily led their characters to the fork in the road and took a look. There was a left path and a right path with one figure running down each. As for the other three members of Happy? Who knows where they were...

Tyranny had already gained an idea of what Happy was planning. They had split up, Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun blocking Misty Rain's way and getting the other three to go ahead. So, something as important as the shards would definitely be with the other three. However, Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun had split up as well. Left or right, which would lead them to the other three?

Logically speaking, Ye Xiu was the core of their team, so Steamed Bun was more likely to be bait. However, on the other hand, Ye Xiu might have made himself bait because he was the core of the team. But then, thinking from another direction...

Stop. This sort of reverse thinking would never end. With Ye Xiu's schemes, it could be either. Thus, there was no way to solve this problem with logic. They just had to chance it, it was a fifty percent chance.　

"Let's pursue Ye Xiu!" Zhang Jiale suggested. He had voiced what everyone had been thinking. In that moment, their thoughts had converged.

"Wait…" Zhang Xinjie suddenly spoke up. "If this is what we're thinking, then Ye Xiu might be using this to lure us away."

"So we chase Steamed Bun Invasion?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"So we're going to start guessing how far he's planned ahead again?" Zhang Jiale said.

Zhang Xinjie paused… True, hadn't they just decided to not try and guess Ye Xiu's line of thought? But how come they felt like their thought process would be used upon coming to a decision?

"Let's go after Ye Xiu." In this crucial moment, it was Captain Han Wenqing who stepped forth.

"What if we're wrong?" Lin Jingyan asked.

"Then at least we can vent by beating him up." Han Wenqing replied.

Immediately, everyone perked up. This reason was a great boost to their morale. Han Wenqing was a truly talented captain, able to boost everyone's morale with just a single sentence!

The five immediately swerved left in pursuit. Their hesitation had cost them, but it was a good thing that Han Wenqing was able to settle things quickly. The five of them could, at least, still see Lord Grim's figure. This guy occasionally turned to use Aerial Fire to propel himself backwards as he ran, clearly keeping an eye on what was behind him.

Since Tyranny wanted to catch him, they wouldn't just race him. They were pro players. If they relied solely on their movement speed to catch someone, then that was just competing with their equipment. A pro level pursuit would involve skills as well, either to increase their movement speed or to use attacks to hinder their target.

In Tyranny's formation, there were two ranged attackers. Zhang Jiale's Spirfire and Qin Muyun's Sharpshooter naturally carried the task of hindering Lord Grim's movement. The two raised their guns and shot, different skills speeding forth. Lord Grim was forced to continuously dodge as he ran and this naturally impacted his movement speed. After all, he wasn't faced with normal players anymore, but pro players, including an experienced God like Zhang Jiale.

As Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun's Gunners shot and ran, Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan's two Fighters raised their speed and charged. Lin Jingyan could play dirty, but when it was required and when it was time to go all out, he wouldn't hesitate either. Brawler Dark Thunder directly activated a Powerful Knee Strike, flying forwards. Skills that involved lunging or jumping forth like this moved much faster than normal sprinting. Han Wenqing's Desert Dust had also activated Cloud Body, his character bounding forwards rapidly with buffed speed.

Ye Xiu might be a God, but his current opponents weren't normal players. It didn't take long for Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan to catch up under Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun's control.

Against this old opponent, Han Wenqing was merciless. He didn't wait for his character to completely catch up before activating a high-level skill. With a Soaring Tiger, Desert Dust lunged at Lord Grim feet first.

High-level skills like this that came out of the blue were easy to dodge for pro players, but Ye Xiu knew that under Han Wenqing's control, Soaring Tiger was a move that could vary in many ways. He would have to be extremely careful when dodging. However, there was also Lin Jingyan to consider, and the combination of the two could end up trapping Lord Grim completely with one strike. Thus, against this high-level skill, Ye Xiu didn't bother dodging.

Clang!

The sounds of their clash rang out.

Ye Xiu might not have dodged, but he wouldn't just take the skill head on. Lord Grim brought up a sword horizontally as he was about to be struck, blocking the blow with a Blade Master's Guard.

The damage had been greatly reduced and Soaring Tiger's knock-down effect was neutralized. However, Lord Grim was still kicked back. Ye Xiu used this momentum to go into a roll. Meanwhile, Desert Dust had been thrown up even higher by this kick and came crashing back down at Lord Grim with a Thousand Ton Drop.

Thousand Ton Drop was a skill with Super Armor. Even a powerful skill like Dragon Breaks the Ranks wouldn't be able to knock this attack away. At most, the two sides would neutralize each other and both would take damage. In addition, normal Super Armor was able to neutralize most attack effects, but had a weakness to grabs. Grabs could break Super Armor. However, Thousand Ton Drop was an exception. The Super Armor given by this skill couldn't even be broken by a grab and grabs would be neutralized. The only kind of skill that could be used to break the Super Armor from this skill were skills that specialized in breaking Super Armor. For example, the Brawler's Inject Poison.

Unfortunately, Lord Grim didn't know any of these kinds of skills. Even though he had access to all the low level skills of all the classes, low level skills were for beginners that allowed players to experience the style of the class, but they wouldn't go too deep into things. Most of the contents of that class would be accessible after classing. Thus, Lord Grim had never learned any skills geared towards breaking Super Armor. Faced with Thousand Ton Drop, he didn't have any way to counter it, so he could only avoid it.

Thus, Lord Grim used Charge!

He dodged and took the initiative to attack at the same time, faced with Tyranny's entire team while alone, no less.

Ye Xiu's choice of action was completely unexpected for all five members of Tyranny. Lin Jingyan wasn't prepared at all and the Charge had been directed at him, throwing him out at once. However, Lin Jingyan was no punching bag. As he was knocked away, he also used Sand Toss.

Ye Xiu hastily turned his view. Lord Grim's head turned and dodged the blinding effect of the Sand Toss. However, a Grenade from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms then arrived in front of him. It was quite a ways away, having completely missed. But Ye Xiu knew that this Grenade wasn't used to deal damage, it was a bloody Flash Bomb that inflicted Blind.

"Have you all no shame?" The Flash Bomb went off under Ye Xiu's accusing yell. Although being on a team meant that you wouldn't be inflicted with effects like this, the moment the Flash Bomb went off, the flash filled their screens with white light and they could barely see. But, when their vision returned, they were met with the sight of Lord Grim holding the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella open and blocking his own view with it. Sand Toss from behind and Flash Bomb in front, but he hadn't been blinded at all.

"Have you no shame!!" Zhang Jiale bellowed in anger.

Chapter 1120: Switching Accounts

Using the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, Ye Xiu dodged this seemingly unbreakable blind, but he was still surrounded. Although Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder had been sent flying by Lord Grim's Heroic Charge, Han Wenqing's Desert Dust had already landed heavily on the ground, directly charging toward him with a Ferocious Tiger Flurry.

Another direct powerful attack.

A 1v1 would be a rough battle, but Han Wenqing wasn't fighting by himself right now. Although he himself hadn't done any set-up for this powerful attack, he had his teammates. Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale's blinding partnership hadn't succeeded, but when he used the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella to block the flash, he also blocked his own line of sight. By the time he could close the umbrella again, Desert Dust's fists were already waving before him.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry, a Level 70 attack, it was a skill that could be controlled after activation. Users of different skill levels could affect the power of this attack. Han Wenqing's skill as a Striker didn't need to be mentioned, and the Ferocious Tiger Flurry was exactly the kind of powerful attack he preferred with his playstyle.

Ordinary controls had no way of keeping up with the rapid flurry of punches and kicks from this skill; it was impossible to continuously dodge all of them. The only possibility was to escape out of the attack range, but this was also difficult, because Ferocious Tiger Flurry was simply too fast. Lord Grim closed his umbrella, the fist was in front of him, it seemed that Ye Xiu had no way of countering, Lord Grim was hit!

Lord Grim was instantly sent flying backwards, but Han Wenqing immediately knew that something was wrong. Ferocious Tiger Flurry was a series of attacks in succession; what was the point if the opponent was sent flying after the first punch? Lord Grim was sent so far backwards partly because of Ye Xiu's own controls - he borrowed the power of this punch to put some distance between himself and his opponents.

It was too naive to think that Ye Xiu had no way of reacting to this attack!

But it was also too naive to think that he could completely dodge Ferocious Tiger Flurry with that!

Desert Dust leapt forward and instantly closed the gap between himself and Lord Grim. The punches and kicks still flew toward his body, ready to kill.

Hit!

In one punch, Lord Grim was blasted to pieces. But was Lord Grim that fragile? Of course not, it was Shadow Clone Technique! In that split second during which he pulled away, Ye Xiu sped through the motions and completed the skill. The false body was left behind, while Lord Grim's real body flashed away.

Fighting against the entirety of Tyranny by himself? Ye Xiu wasn't that silly. No matter what, his goal was to run, and he was trying every method he could. He had no chance of winning, not unless the power went out at Tyranny and everyone went offline at once...

Unfortunately, running away wouldn't be easy. Space was limited in this underground dungeon, unlike the open air spaces where he could run and hide in any direction. Right now, there was rock surrounding him, as though trapping the fleeing Ye Xiu in a cage. It wasn't long before Tyranny caught up to him again with their long-range coordinated attacking strategy.

"You don't drop your equipment in this dungeon, right?" Ye Xiu was already thinking about what would come next. Judging from previous battles, aside from shards, players didn't drop anything else. Given the drop rates in the Heavenly Domain, this outcome was very improbable unless it were true that no items could be dropped in this dungeon.

"You'll know once you die!" Tyranny wouldn't be merciful to Ye Xiu just because of this worthy. This time, their encirclement was more complete than before. Even the Cleric Immovable Rock, who didn't have much battle power, was a blocking presence that limited the paths available to Ye Xiu. Tyranny accounted for all possible locations that Ye Xiu could teleport to with his Shadow Clone Technique.

"Okay okay, I surrender," said Ye Xiu.

"So what?" Zhang Jiale, not pausing in his attacks. This scum had to be dead before they could relax. If they just stopped their attacks when he announced surrender, he would certainly take advantage of that opening.

Tyranny's old generals were unfazed by Ye Xiu's trashtalk. "Go die!" As Zhang Jiale shouted, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was just about toss a grenade at Ye Xiu's feet to deal the final blow, but suddenly, the screen flashed - a QQ chat window popped up out of nowhere.

It said: Lord Grim has poked you.

"Shameless!!" Zhang Jiale almost spat out blood. By the time he switched back to the game, Lord Grim was already gone. This poke wasn't any sort of game-changer, it just interrupted Zhang Jiale's final attack, but Lord Grim was still taken out by Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder.

"What happened?"

Killing Ye Xiu should have been an exciting thing, but Tyranny's members found that Zhang Jiale was currently wearing a murderous expression. They all turned to ask what happened, only to find that Zhang Jiale had opened QQ chat on his computer and was furiously banging out paragraphs denouncing Ye Xiu's use of out-of-game interference tactics.

"You didn't mute?" Tyranny's members sighed, and at the same time were quietly relieved that they had all muted QQ.

When Lord Grim died, he didn't drop anything, showing that he really hadn't been carrying the shards. Tyranny didn't have time to stand around here and chat. They still had to find the other four members of Happy, and it was possible that they already used the shards to do something.

"Let's split up and search!" Zhang Xinjie suggested. After killing Ye Xiu, everyone felt a sense of relief. Before, they were wary of splitting up lest they fall into some kind of trap, but they now felt a little braver.

"Yes, let's split up!"

Tyranny divided their members into two groups, each taking one path. One path continued along their current route, while the other turned back to take the path along which Steamed Bun had escaped.

However, Ghost Lair's tunnels weren't so simple. After splitting in two, they ran into more forks in the road, and Tyranny still didn't have a single clue that would lead them to Happy. They could only continue splitting up, until all five were acting alone, increasing the number of paths they were checking at once.

"Found them! They've already started killing the Ghost King, hurry and come!" At last, Lin Jingyan was the first to find Happy's four players, and they were currently engaged in fierce battle with the Ghost King. Once the Ghost King was killed, then everything was over. But Lin Jingyan was alone, he didn't dare go up alone to attack. He could only sit and anxiously wait for his teammates.

"I'm close by, almost there!" Zhang Jiale answered. After wandering for so long, everyone had gained a sense of the layout of the dungeon, and Zhang Jiale anticipated that he could arrive quickly. Indeed, after less than two minutes, Zhang Jiale could hear the sounds of the boss battle.

"Where are you?" Zhang Jiale sent a message to Lin Jingyan.

"You've arrived?"

"Yeah."

"Us two will go first!" Lin Jingyan said.

"You stick to Su Mucheng, I'll harass the other three." Zhang Jiale laid out the plan.

"Okay," agreed Lin Jingyan.

"Go!"

The two characters charged forward, and following the play, Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder headed toward Dancing Rain, while Zhang Jiale took advantage of his attack range and began to harass the other three.

Facing against three rookies, Zhang Jiale was confident in his abilities. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms closed the distance, and his Hundred Blossoms cover enveloped the three at once. This was a high-level playstyle only found at the professional level, and Zhang Jiale knew that these rookies, lacking experience, would have their heads spinning under this interference.

"You came pretty quickly, huh?"

But at this moment, Zhang Jiale suddenly heard someone speak from the lights and shadows.

This voice, it was Ye Xiu, but how was he here? Zhang Jiale was frozen, as though struck by a grenade, but in the next second, he wanted to cry.

How could he not?

After all, this wasn't an official match, just an in-game event. Lord Grim died, so Ye Xiu calmly switched to another account and continued playing. It was as simple as one plus one.

But such a simple idea had been overlooked by Tyranny. Even the detail-oriented Zhang Xinjie had forgotten this possibility, after growing accustomed to his professional background. For these pro players, the possibility of such a tactic didn't even exist in their minds.

Ye Xiu was still here. Suddenly, the plan of having just the two of them run interference seemed a lot less feasible!

This is bad!

Zhang Jiale was so bold and reckless only because he was confident that the rookies couldn't handle his Hundred Blossoms style, but now… there was a Ye Xiu!

As soon as he realized something was wrong, a silhouette appeared out of the light and shadow. The rookies were disoriented, but Ye Xiu accurately determined Dazzling Hundred Blossoms' position from the pattern of attack and instantly attacked in his direction. And Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had indeed been standing a little too close. By the time Zhang Jiale wanted to dodge, Soft Mist was already in front of him.

Of course it's a Battle Mage…

Zhang Jiale had no tears left, no path of retreat. He was sent flying by Soft Mist's Dragon Breaks the Ranks, slamming into the wall, and was then battered by several Chasers. And then, that Ghost King sent an attack at Soft Mist. Soft Mist twisted and dodged, and the attack sent by the boss wasn't some direction-changing Chaser. It landed upon Hundred Blossoms' body.

Once Lin Jingyan knew Ye Xiu was here, he also knew they were in trouble. The two of them had only dared to attack by themselves because they knew that aside from Su Mucheng, everyone here was a rookie. Although they wouldn't be able to take them in a fight, they could still cause some chaos without too much difficulty. But Ye Xiu had switched accounts and run over here. Trying to interfere with him would be like kicking a steel board.

I have to run!

Lin Jingyan immediately made this judgment. He detached from Su Mucheng's side and began to run. Su Mucheng counterattacked instantly, and the powerful blasts landing upon Dark Thunder's backside truly made him pathetically embarrassed.

Meanwhile, after Zhang Jiale was slammed into the wall, he didn't dare land directly. Ye Xiu was still there, eyeing him! This guy, not only could he use his own attacks, he could use his aggro to lure the Ghost King over here. The intelligence of an NPC was incomparable to that of a god. It should have been on Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan's side, three against Happy's four. But now, under this direction, it was like a summoned monster at Ye Xiu's command, launching the fiercest attacks at Zhang Jiale.

"Can't hold, retreat for now!" Lin Jingyan shouted.

"What do you think I'm trying to do?" Zhang Jiale was depressed. Of course he wanted to run, but now he was stuck at the corner of a wall, surrounded by enemies.

"How much health is left?" Ye Xiu asked him.

Chapter 1121: The Troubled Lin Jingyan

To save or not to save, that was the question!

Lin Jingyan was uncertain what to do in such a situation.

Currently, Dark Thunder could easily run away, but Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had been trapped in a corner and was doomed. However, was he alone enough to save Dazzling Hundred Blossoms from the four members of Happy who had Ye Xiu in command? Lin Jingyan doubted it.

"Forget about me! You run first!" In this crucial moment, it was Zhang Jiale who made the decision for him.

"Huh?" Steamed Bun was confused. "How come he's like Misty Rain's little girls?"

Zhang Jiale was enraged. How dare they mock his heroic and sacrificial act!

"He really is like them," Ye Xiu said.

"Die!" Zhang Jiale didn't know that some of what he had just said really had been a repeat of what Misty Rain's sisters had said, taking it as mockery from Ye Xiu and Steamed Bun, and wanted to risk it all in one final wave of attacks. But the four, in addition to the attacks directed over from the Ghost King, instantly suppressed him.

　

"Rest in peace!" Ye Xiu said as Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was finally defeated.

　　

On the other side, Lin Jingyan had already ran for it with Zhang Jiale's heroic decision. If they were both wiped up just now, Han Wenqing and the other two probably wouldn't have an easy time fighting once they came over. Yet now, he had managed to escape and could take this chance to recover a little, By the time the other three arrived, they would be fighting four on four and had a good chance of winning. The current Happy really didn't have a healer anymore, not even a cheerleader healer.

　

Dark Thunder hurriedly ran for it, settling down to one side to eat and drink to recover while keeping an eye on the situation.

After killing Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Happy didn't seem to have the intention to pursue him, turning back to the Ghost King.

　

This Ghost King was immense in size, with curled horns protruding from its head and red eyes. It dealt physical damage with a rock-shattering swing of its claws, and magic damage with swift blasts of energy from its mouth. It was clearly a powerful foe. However, Happy clearly wasn't unfamiliar with this Ghost King anymore. They had figured out the Ghost King's strategy, to the point where Ye Xiu could use it as a summons.

All the different monsters that the system controlled were nothing to pro players. After all, the online game was immensely popular amongst the general populace and tailored to normal players. No matter how hard it would get, it would be easy to adapt to for pros.

　

"Will they make it in time?" Lin Jingyan's original worries returned. This wasn't a problem of if they could win or not, but if Tyranny's other players could arrive in time. Han Wenqing and the other three had gone in a completely opposing direction from Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan in the very beginning. Then, the three had split up even further as they searched, so they were currently very far from one another.

Looking at the Ghost King's health and then asking after the other three's positions, Lin Jingyan found that they really might not make it in time.

　

He had to do something.

Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder crept out again. If he faced them head on, then he would lose for sure. However, if he stayed idle, that wouldn't be good either. He could only cautiously circle over. He had to find a way to do some damage, even if it meant directing a few attacks to himself, that would still help to lower their DPS.

Dark Thunder came closer, and Happy's four ignored him.

Currently, he was definitely within Dancing Rain's attack range, at least, but Dancing Rain didn't even send a single missile towards him. Happy's four focused on attacking the Ghost King.

Closer, even closer...

　

He continued to creep closer until, finally, some of his skills were in range.

Happy's four continued to ignore him.

Lin Jingyan didn't have the time to spare for further consideration. He was already here, so he should at least try.

Thus, Dark Thunder raised his hand and threw a Brick, aiming at the back of Soft Mist's head.

Soft Mist dodged to the side and the Brick flew past. Lin Jingyan was about to follow up with a second attack to completely mess up Ye Xiu's rhythm, but then he saw his Brick smash into the Ghost King.

　

Lin Jingyan coughed blood.

Bricks weren't the strongest skill, but this strike enlightened him to Ye Xiu's possible intentions.

This guy… First he lured the Ghost King's attacks and dodged, resulting in the Ghost King's attacks hitting Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Now he was baiting Lin Jingyan's attacks and then dodging, letting the attacks hit the Ghost King.

　　

Damn you! You think I'm your summon!?

After Lin Jingyan finished coughing blood, he still had to figure something out.

Dark Thunder began to reposition himself as Lin Jingyan tried to find a position where Soft Mist wasn't directly between him and the Ghost King. Otherwise, if his attacks missed, they'd hit the Ghost King.

However, Ye Xiu didn't give up either. Soft Mist followed Dark Thunder's movements, keeping him behind her.

　　

Lin Jingyan wanted to cry. He was circling around from some distance away. The radius of his circular path was so long while Soft Mist's was so short. He had to take several steps, but the other only needed one. He still hadn't managed to throw the other off after so long.

Of course, Soft Mist wasn't Lin Jingyan's only possible target. Happy had four. No matter who he attacked, it would be enough to cause chaos and pull down their DPS. However, the problem was that the only target Dark Thunder could reach right now was Soft Mist.

Dancing Rain didn't need to close in to attack and stayed far away, sending missile after missile over. If Dark Thunder wanted to attack her, he would have a to walk quite a bit to get there.

Steamed Bun and Deception were currently behind the Ghost King. That meant that those two, the Ghost King, and Soft Mist stood in a straight line. Then, when Ye Xiu repositioned himself, the two would cooperate. With that, they were constantly hidden behind the Ghost King. With Dark Thunder circling around, he didn't have an angle to attack. Even if he did, a Brawler didn't have such a long attack range.

"What accurate calculations!" Lin Jingyan felt pretty helpless and could only say something to try and distract them. Then, Dark Thunder came closer. He couldn't not come closer. At this distance, he was being completely suppressed.

After getting closer, the radius of his path was much smaller. Lin Jingyan didn't believe that he couldn't succeed here.

Turn, move!

Dark Thunder's figure swerved, beginning to move around again. As expected, Soft Mist followed his rhythm, turning.

　

No matter what, Soft Mist's circular path had a smaller radius than his, so keeping up was easy. However, could you be certain that this continuous circling wouldn't impact your DPS?

This was the first problem Lin Jingyan threw at Happy. Logically speaking, at a pro level, maintaining DPS while moving about wasn't a problem. It wasn't hard to keep up.

　

However, there was a second problem.

This time, Dark Thunder didn't keep a set rhythm to his circling. Sometimes he'd go left, sometimes right, sometimes quickly, sometimes slow. This wasn't done randomly either. Lin Jingyan was keeping a close eye on Happy's attack rhythm and picking the most debilitating moments to move.

This problem was much harder to solve. Happy's members had to keep a good grasp on their rhythm as well.

Ye Xiu could probably do this, but Steamed Bun and Mo Fan couldn't always keep up under the changing rhythm, occasionally tripping up on their mechanics. Happy's DPS rhythm was finally being affected. To outsiders, all Lin Jingyan was doing was circling around. He wasn't attacking at all. Only other pro level players, with their experience, would be able to understand the debilitating effect this had on Happy's attack rhythm.

"Looks like you're asking for it!" With a yell, Soft Mist whirled around suddenly.

Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder hurriedly darted away like a rabbit, but then realized that Soft Mist was still attacking the Ghost King and hadn't pursued him at all.

Tricked again!

However, Lin Jingyan was in a good mood and wasn't frustrated at this at all, immediately darting back over. He still kept his distance, cautious. He didn't dare get too close, if he was really caught by the other, then that wouldn't spell anything good for him. Though it seemed like he was just circling around, this was quite a pain for Lin Jingyan as well. He had to observe the three's attack rhythm while keeping an eye on Dancing Rain in the distance. He had to disrupt Happy's attack rhythm while also carefully protecting himself. He didn't know how long he would be able to last. This wasn't an easy task; why else would he wait for Zhang Jiale in the first place? He would deal with this alone if he could. He had waited because he knew that the risk was rather high. Now, he had been forced to this point and carried out his task with 120 percent. Currently, it had some effect, but only a little. Happy's attack rhythm was only being weakened, but not completely disrupted. Under this sort of harassment, their DPS wouldn't be affected all that much. Lin Jingyan didn't know if it was enough. He was currently rapidly trying to come up with more ideas.

　

"You again!!" As he was deep in contemplation, a loud yell sounded beside his ear. Lin Jingyan, startled, darted away again sunconsciously. But it turned out that Ye Xiu was just bluffing. Soft Mist hadn't moved at all.

Lin Jingyan didn't know if he should cry or laugh. Even he wasn't used to this sort of bluff. This was because pro matches didn't have voice, so there wouldn't be this sort of jump-scare of a distraction. The effect of the same words sent into the chat was incomparable with a yell on voice. If it was just a message sent to the chat, Lin Jingyan would focus more on Soft Mist's movements instead of acting with what he heard and subconsciously running.

Lin Jingyan, feeling rather helpless, once again had Dark Thunder run back over. Yet he hadn't even began circling when he saw Soft Mist's figure swerve to the side.

Huh?

Lin Jingyan was stunned for a moment. They weren't in line anymore; he could attack!

He hadn't even gotten the chance to attack when a black shadow sped in front of him. Some sort of skill from the Ghost King had arrived.

　

He hastily had Dark Thunder dodge and when he raised his head again, another black fireball was heading his way.

Was this a counterattack against him?

Thinking this, Lin Jingyan once again dodged the fireball. When he looked up again, Soft Mist's spear had arrived.

When he wasn't launching an attack, Ye Xiu had erupted into meaningless yelling again and again, but when he was actually charging over, he was completely silent.

Lin Jingyan didn't dare to face the other head on and hurriedly retreated. This time, however, Soft Mist gave chase. As for the Ghost King, it changed targets and lumbered towards Dancing Rain.

"The aggro target switched!" Lin Jingyan was shocked, only just realizing that Happy had been doing something more during their quiet DPSing.

Chapter 1122: One Man Can Hold the Pass

Without an aggro-establishing skill like the Knight's Provoke, it was impossible to suddenly switch the target of the aggro. Even OT required that certain conditions be met. Otherwise, if it were as simple as your damage surpassed mine so the aggro immediately transferred, then two characters could simply take turns attacking and ping-pong the boss back and forth until it died.

The aggro system wasn't designed so foolishly. To cause OT, the aggro had to surpass a certain percentage. Because of this, the fact that Dancing Rain had managed to suddenly pull away the aggro meant that they had prepared for this long in advance.

Dancing Rain was leading the boss away just like this, closely followed by Steamed Bun Invasion and Deception. Yet Lin Jingyan couldn't do a thing to stop them, because Ye Xiu was right in front him.

In Ye Xiu's hands, Battle Mage Soft Mist definitely wasn't an opponent that Lin Jingyan could just easily blow past. In the blink of an eye, Ghost King and Happy's three players vanished into one of the tunnels, while Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder continued to be beaten down by Soft Mist's chained attacks.

For him, the important thing was to track where the Ghost King was being taken, but now, in order to accomplish that, he first had to defeat Ye Xiu.

For Lin Jingyan, this wasn't an entirely impossible task. After so many years in the professional scene, the two had met on the battlefield multiple times, and Lin Jingyan did have some victories. But every battle was extremely difficult. Although it was possible that he could defeat Ye Xiu, he definitely couldn't just quickly kill him with a chaotic flurry of slashes.

What's worse was that Ye Xiu had the initiative right now, and Lin Jingyan was on the defensive. Lin Jingyan didn't think he had the ability to defeat Ye Xiu in this current situation - just continuing to defend would be difficult enough.

No good would come from continuing this fight.

Lin Jingyan understood this clearly. So the only thing he could do was to recklessly charge through Ye Xiu's blockade, to see where Ghost King went.

Just as he thought this, Ye Xiu suddenly stopped attacking.

Soft Mist jumped back several times, retreating away.

Lin Jingyan was surprised. As he watched, Ye Xiu controlled Soft Mist to stop right in the tunnel.

The area where they had been fighting the Ghost King was a relatively wide and open space, like an underground tomb chamber. But this tunnel at the end of the chamber wasn't so wide. Seeing Soft Mist stand right at the entrance of the tunnel and completely blocking the way forward, one proverb flashed to the front of Lin Jingyan's mind: One man can hold the pass against a thousand enemies.

"Hehehe. What now? Guess you can't pass." Ye Xiu said gleefully.

"Ye Xiu you shameless bastard!!" From Dark Thunder's side came a somewhat distant shout. Ye Xiu, with all his experience, immediately knew that this was the sound of someone sitting next to the player yelling into the player's headset.

"Which pro player is such a sore loser?" Ye Xiu asked.

He could even distinguish the owner of the voice. It was Zhang Jiale!

Zhang Jiale was already eliminated from this dungeon, but he still watched closely from Lin Jingyan's screen. Seeing this situation, he immediately knew that things were bad. Even if they waited for Han Wenqing and the others to arrive and they were able to kill Ye Xiu with the advantage of numbers, after that, they had no idea where the Ghost King went and they'd have to start their search all over again. Happy would probably have enough time to kill the Ghost King before they found them again.

Zhang Jiale this time really became the screenwriter.

Lin Jingyan tried to rush Ye Xiu a few times. Ye Xiu didn't try to compete with him, he just parked himself right in the tunnel and prevented him from passing. Every time, the effort was fruitless, and Lin Jingyan's own health was almost depleted.

Then, Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, and Qin Muyun arrived. In a 4v1, the outcome was as expected. This time, Ye Xiu didn't continue to run. He blocked the tunnel with all of his life, but was eventually pushed over.

But now, where was the Ghost King?

The four continued to run forward, but they very quickly arrived at another fork in the road, shattering their hearts.

"Give up!" Ye Xiu sent a message to them in the global channel.

As long as it wasn't over, Tyranny would never give up. They split up to search, but in the end, all they found was a system announcement.

Team Deception successfully killed the Ghost King.

The announcement was broadcast to the whole world. The players who were still online, after seeing this announcement, were in an uproar.

Although they didn't earn the ability to participate in this bonus event, they at least knew that all of the participants were professional teams and players, including the Four Heavenly Kings of Tyranny.

They also didn't know what had happened in Ghost Lair. But in the end, the team that successfully killed the Ghost King was Deception's? Team Deception, wasn't that just Team Happy?

Was Happy really this strong?

Everyone was discussing this outcome.

Of course, in the eyes of the ordinary players, a grassroots team like Happy was relatively weak. The fact that they had managed to vanquish Excellent Era was, after all, deemed a miracle.

But after defeating Excellent Era, Happy was able to get another victory in this competition, beating even Tyranny… A miracle was called a miracle because it was extraordinary. Something that happened often couldn't be called a miracle.

Happy defeated Excellent Era, and now defeated Tyranny in this competition?

And not just Tyranny, but also Wind Howl, and Misty Rain, and Royal Style… These teams couldn't be dismissed either.

Everyone was mulling over the implications of this; even the media reported on it.

Over the summer break, there were no battles to be written about, so there were much fewer topics of interest. Weekly esports newspapers that relied primarily on news about the Glory professional scene would shrink their publications during this time. But even now, everyone was still looking for stories to report on.

The biggest news during the summer was news of transfers - reporters would jump on this treasured news, reporting on completed transfers as well as the barest hints of rumors. But this sort of news wasn't enough to support the paper. After all, unlike the ten-per-week regularity of professional matches, news of transfers was spontaneous and sporadic.

So the media looked to other places for news, and the in-game world of Glory was a natural choice. The weekly esports newspapers would often have a section about the in-game gossip, and during a time where there weren't matches to report on, nor other interesting news, the in-game section expanded.

The eleventh server, and the Heavenly Domain. With a few million players, there were countless topics of gossip springing up every day. As long as you had the patience, there was enough to report on - even if the weekly newspaper was changed to daily, there was enough material.

However, as a professional esports media outlet, Esports Home still hoped to find some high-end material.

Pro players spending the summer break working or training in-game certainly counted as high-end material. In past summers, there were plenty of pro players who had been discovered in game, and the papers were as diligent in their reports as ever.

And this year was even more exciting, especially with this summer's event. The pro players of the various teams all picked up their accounts and entered the game, which was a rare sight to be seen.

Thus, this week's esports weekly papers of course focused on the performance of the pro players during the Ghost Parade event. The reporters swiped their account cards and entered Glory, contacting the guilds, or directly contacting the pro players, and tracking their progress.

And tonight, there was even an easter egg unlocked. Suddenly five teams were thrust into direct competition, and the reporters anxiously waited outside for the outcome and to ask what happened.

The one who finally killed Ghost King was Happy? The reporters' professional intuition told them that there was a story behind this full of twists and turns, and they all grew excited.

They paid attention to the five teams in the dungeon, and those that had the pro players added as friends could track the progress of the teams by seeing when these players went offline.

Because the pro players immediately logged off upon exiting Ghost Lair, the reporters had no way of interviewing them in-game. Outside of the game, the most convenient was to use a chat method like QQ. All of these teams had dedicated reporters that followed them, and these reporters all had the QQ's of the various players on the team. However, it was one thing to send a message on QQ, and it was another to see if the player was actually available and would reply.

In the end, this was just an in-game event, not some explosive news, and there was still plenty of time before publication, so the reporters weren't anxious in waiting. If they could contact the player directly then great, if not, they would find other avenues to get news.

So very quickly, reporters discovered that Fang Rui had just made a new post on Weibo.

This Weibo was sent from his phone, timestamped after he had logged off from the Ghost Lair.

Just four words in the post: The weather has changed. And then, a sighing emoji.

Below the post, a whole crowd of fans had gathered in the replies, but they weren't able to find too much to discuss, just some comments like "Fang Rui make sure not to leave your clothes out in the rain" and such.

But reporters were perceptive, and would certainly ponder over what they saw. Especially the reporters following Wind Howl, they lived in the same city as Fang Rui. Seeing this Weibo, those reporters quickly pulled up weather reports, only to find that the weather was stable, with clear skies and bright sunshine forecasted for the next several days.

Even if it was some prediction made from analyzing the night sky… The reporters looked out their windows into the darkness, but there wasn't anything out of the ordinary!

Then, looking at the sighing emoji, the reporters began to have a faint feeling of the meaning behind this post.

The reporters patiently flipped through the comments on the post. There was a lot to look through; after all, Fang Rui was a star of a pro player and had many fans. Not long after it was posted, the comments and replies were already in the hundreds. This actually wasn't even as many as it could have been - given the obscurity of this post, many people didn't know what to say and just didn't reply.

The reporters patiently flipped through. Since Fang Rui was a god of playing dirty, his fans were naturally fans of dirty playing as well. In the numerous strange replies, there were more than a few dirty and vulgar comments, which wasn't unexpected.

But after flipping through several pages of comments, the reporters soon found another clue.

One fan also seemed to have perceived that Fang Rui's mood was different from normal, and posted an ordinary, "Fang Rui, what's wrong?"

In the end, it was this comment that earned Fang Rui's reply.

Five words: My love has been exhausted.

Chapter 1123: Brawler and Thief

Cheng Siyan, Esports Home's reporter in City N, was the team reporter for Team Wind Howl in the Glory scene.

After seeing the comment "my love has been exhausted," Cheng Siyan felt even more shocked. She immediately checked several pages of comments and saw many puzzled reactions from fans. However, Fang Rui didn't further explain his comment.

If his comment was related to Glory, could he be planning on retiring?

Cheng Siyan jumped up in fright at this conjecture.

Fang Rui had joined the Alliance in season five. Many outstanding players had appeared that year, but because it happened to be after the influx of players from the Golden Generation in season four, season five seemed weak in comparison.

Among the pros that had been chosen for All Stars, apart from Fang Rui, there was one half to Void's famed Ghostblade duo, Wu Yuce, and the current number one Glory player, Zhou Zekai.

These three had become famous during their early years too. They, along with the Golden Generation, were at the height of their careers. No matter what had happened with Fang Rui, he shouldn't be having any thoughts of retiring, no?

Cheng Siyan shook his head ferociously, getting rid of such a crazy thought.

My love has been exhausted. If this comment wasn't directed towards Glory, could it be towards his team? Or his personal life?

Glory's pro players were all at the prime of their youths. Encountering love troubles wasn't anything too unexpected. Cheng Siyan was familiar with Team Wind Howl, though. She had never heard of Fang Rui setting foot into a relationship. After getting rid of this thought, the only other possibility was the team.

Fang Rui no longer loved his team?

Was this… a sign of his departure?

Cheng Siyan was surprised.

As Wind Howl's team reporter, she knew more about the changes happening in the team than anyone else. Tang Hao's addition to the team and Zhao Yuzhe's rise gave the team vitality and drive. However, as a professional, she could also see that Fang Rui's position had been weakened because of the changes to the team's strategies as a result of those two's playstyles. She had pointed this out in an article and had hoped for Wind Howl to make adjustments. But Wind Howl had started the season explosively and also collapsed explosively. This issue hadn't been properly taken care of.

In the new season, Wind Howl had signed on new players. People paying attention to this issue were waiting to see what changes Wind Howl would make to their style next season. They most likely hadn't thought that the resolution to this problem would actually be to let go of Fang Rui.

If Fang Rui truly was unable to assimilate into the team, he could only accept this decision. But the problem was that as Wind Howl's team reporter, Cheng Siyan hadn't seen Wind Howl try to do this though. All she saw was Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe showing off their playstyles without restraint, while Fang Rui worked tirelessly to chase after them.

He failed to catch up, so he was being let go?　　

If that was the case, Cheng Siyan could completely sympathize with Fang Rui's "my love has been exhausted."

Transfers were undoubtedly the highlights of the summer for reporters. A transfer for an All Star like Fang Rui was a highlight among highlights, so as soon as she realized this possibility, she definitely wasn't going to stay idle. But basing her news off of a few words on Weibo wasn't reliable. She needed to find more data.

Cheng Siyan tried sending Fang Rui a text but didn't get a response. After hesitating a bit, she took out her phone and gave a call. However, Fang Rui had turned his phone off.

She couldn't get in touch with the person directly involved. Since relying on a few Weibo words to contact Wind Howl for an official response would be somewhat excessive, Cheng Siyan continued to read the replies on Fang Rui's Weibo and pondered over what she should do.

Suddenly, she realized that Fang Rui's Weibo had been posted after the Ghost Parade Easter Egg event. This shouldn't be a coincidence. Perhaps something had happened during the course of this event that had affected him to the extent that he would post "my love has been exhausted." If she could understand what had happened in this event, maybe she would be able to get some clues?

Who to ask?

Cheng Siyan looked at her friends list on QQ. She was friends with practically everyone on Team Wind Howl, but asking someone on Wind Howl might end up being a situation where the person on the spot is baffled, while the spectator sees more clearly. What about the other teams? Cheng Siyan thought to herself. Chu Yunxiu? Su Mucheng?

Female pro players were in the minority, and it wasn't too different for Glory news reporters either. As rare species, she had a pretty good relationship with these two Gods. These two just happened to participate in the Easter Egg event too. Cheng Siyan immediately messaged them.

Chu Yunxiu seemed to be offline already though. As for Su Mucheng, she replied back promptly and explained what had happened in the Easter Egg event.

Because of their good relationship with each other, whenever Cheng Siyan asked a question for more details, Su Mucheng didn't decline. When she heard about the direct confrontation between Happy and Wind Howl, Cheng Siyan became excited. This time, she had indeed asked the right person.

Cheng Siyan didn't want to miss any of the details of this battle. Su Mucheng also knew that Cheng Siyan was Wind Howl's team reporter, so she wasn't surprised. After Tang Hao's Demon Subduer was killed in the skirmish, they quickly retreated and then hid as they watched Misty Rain and Royal Style trap Wind Howl. The conflict between Zhao Yuzhe and Fang Rui had taken place after Demon Subduer died, after Happy had already retreated. As a result, Su Mucheng didn't know about it. But Su Mucheng still remembered Zhao Yuzhe charging at them solo during their retreat as well as Fang Rui's Doubtful Demon being the only remaining member left, so Su Mucheng obviously talked about those.

Cheng Siyan hadn't directly heard what she had wanted to hear, but she was familiar with Team Wind Howl. The series of events, from Zhao Yuzhe pursuing Happy alone to Wind Howl stopping their pursuit to Fang Rui being the only survivor from the encirclement by Misty Rain and Royal Style, gave her a lot of clues.

She was certain that something had happened between Fang Rui and Zhao Yuzhe.

Because she understood Wind Howl's players. If she had to comment on Zhao Yuzhe, to put it nicely, he showed a lot of initiative; to put it negatively, he was short sighted. In that situation, he would choose to pursue the enemy, but Fang Rui, who was the master at playing dirty, would definitely err on the side of caution. Fang Rui also had a better understanding of Ye Xiu's skill. In that situation, he definitely wouldn't chase after the enemy rashly.

Their captain, Tang Hao, wasn't there. Even though Fang Rui was Wind Howl's vice-captain, the number two, because of his difference in idealogy, Zhao Yuzhe, who aligned with Tang Hao's playstyle, didn't recognize Fang Rui's methods at all. Zhao Yuzhe disagreed with most of Fang Rui's orders and did as he pleased. Thus, it would be hard to avoid a conflict. And in this conflict, Tang Hao would most definitely favor Zhao Yuzhe. After all, their ideologies were similar. The long-time veteran Fang Rui was almost like an alien to them.

Cheng Siyan let out a deep sigh.　　

She understood what Fang Rui meant by "my love has been exhausted."

Fang Rui had probably been trying to establish a connection with Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe the entire time, but he was never able to get a response. It was just like that phrase: I treat you well, but you treat me with indifference.

He hadn't only attempted it once or twice. Fang Rui was unable to synergize with Tang Hao or Zhao Yuzhe over the entire last season. Even after their defeat in the playoffs, Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe still refused to make any changes.

Maybe this was a form of perseverance, a form of confidence in their playstyles. However, Fang Rui had been hurt because of their persistence. Discouraged and downhearted, besides leaving, what other choice did he have?

Club Wind Howl didn't seem to have any opinion on this matter. They remained indifferent. But in reality, in the clubs, the captain had authority on these issues. Tang Hao's position on this problem was equivalent to the club's positoin. Unfortunately, this was the outcome for Fang Rui. Tang Hao insisted on his intrinsic playstyle and didn't try to fit it with Fang Rui's playing dirty. Only Fang Rui tried his hardest to fit in with the team. However, the results were poor. His value could not be utilized optimally.

"The weather… really has changed.." Cheng Siyan murmured to herself. Brawler and Thief. Demon Subduer and Doubtful Demon. After Fang Rui entered the team, Wind Howl had established this duo nicknamed the Criminal Partners, which had received quite a lot of attention. Even though they failed to make it into the finals, Wind Howl frequently made it to the playoffs. Their strength was not that of a bottom team.

But now, it was all over. Lin Jingyan had left. Fang Rui was about to leave. The Thief class didn't seem to appeal to Tang Hao's tastes. Wind Howl probably wouldn't introduce a new Thief player. Brawler and Thief, the Criminal Partners, were going to fade away wordlessly just like this?

Cheng Siyan also didn't know. She didn't have first-hand knowledge from the people directly involved, but she was already saddened. Even though she knew that this choice would be favorable for Team Wind Howl's growth, the invested fans wouldn't react to this resolution rationally. The Criminal Partners were the symbol of Team Wind Howl's core. And now, this partnership would be breaking off. It was as if Hundred Blossoms no longer had Blood and Blossoms, or Void no longer had their dual Ghostblades, or Blue Rain no longer their Sword and Curse. It would always feel strange.

"Why did it turn out like this?" Cheng Siyan didn't make any more inquiries about what else happened in Ghost Lair. She was already too lazy to write about this content. She believed that there would be many others who would write about that. Right now, she was only concerned about Team Wind Howl. She was already preparing to personally pay a visit and ask tomorrow morning.

Who would have thought that the next morning, before Cheng Siyan could even leave the door, she received a phone call about the huge news. Cheng Siyan was stunned. She thought that Fang Rui leaving the team had happened overnight, but it turned out that it was news of Team Seaside's Zhao Yang retiring.

Chapter 1124: Weibo War

Zhao Yang was a pro player who had debuted in the third season. He had been highly regarded upon his debut, but had lost to Wang Jiexi for the season's title of Best Rookie. But, he had still managed to be voted into the All Stars for seven years in succession, starting from the year of his debut. He was, unarguably, the number one Qi Master in Glory.

This glory belonged to Zhao Yang, but what stood out most about him was that he had managed to be voted into the All Stars for seven years, yet hadn't played in a single playoffs match in seven years.

Out of all the All Stars, the only player that had never made it to the playoffs was Zhao Yang. Seven consecutive years of making it into All Stars spoke lengths of Zhao Yang's strength. Seven consecutive years of not making it into the playoffs spoke lengths about Team Seaside's strength.

People weren't willing to give them the label of 'weak team' because of their All Star player. In truth, Seaside was quite far from those teams that drifted about the relegation zone. They were solidly mid-tier, always just steps away from the playoffs.

Because of this awkward situation, plenty of people tried to entice Zhao Yang to other teams, but he stayed, leading Seaside over and over again in an attempt to charge into the playoffs. Seven years of hard work, seven years of disappointment, results that were beyond average, Zhao Yang had been suspended in such a situation for seven whole years, and now he was finally exhausted. He hadn't switched teams to try again, bur instead gave in to defeat and announced his retirement.

Zhao Yang's career as a pro player hadn't been short of mockery. There was little need to talk about Wang Jiexi, who had debuted in season three with him and was considered the most successful pro player second to Ye Xiu. To most people, there was nothing to compare, what with Zhao Yang having never even experienced a single playoffs.

Most people were more willing to compare him to Yang Cong.

Captain of 301 Degrees, the number one Assassin of the Alliance and also a third season debutant. Yang Cong was different from Wang Jiexi and Zhao Yang though. At first, Yang Cong hadn't stood out at all, but as he grew and developed, he slowly gained acknowledgement, and with him, 301 Degrees also grew as a team.

　

This team was full of players who, like Yang Cong, weren't eye-catching, but had a great grasp of the basics and trained themselves up step by step. They lacked natural talent, but made up for it with their diligence. They weren't a powerhouse, and didn't really have any sort of solid identity as a strong team, but they often managed to slip into the playoffs and could cause quite some trouble for any powerhouse.

In comparison, Zhao Yang, who held everyone's expectations, had never drawn any doubt about his skill, but he had never managed to bring his team up to a breakthrough. And Seaside also had terrible management as a club, having managed to experience all the problems a club could experience: financial troubles, workplace politics, etc. It was impressive that they had managed to hold on for so long. However, Zhao Yang was leaving now and no one would expect anything more from this team. Even though they had an All Star level account, Boundless Sea, that they had put all their resources into making, Seaside's chaotic management meant that even an All Star account wouldn't be enough to attract any talents.

Zhao Yang's retirement press conference was very peaceful, and his career had been one entire awkward situation without anything worth commemorating. In the end, even Zhao Yang himself could only use "at least I got here and tried my best," to comment on his seven years as a pro. After that, it was just the necessities like Seaside thanking him for all his hard work and what not.

Another talented player left, but like his career, his departure didn't have much of an effect on the Alliance as a whole. What people cared about most would always be the fight for the championship, and Seaside had never been a part of that. Their weakening would only let those in danger of relegation sigh in relief.

　

Since there weren't any significant repercussions, Cheng Siyan ignored it after looking over the gist. It wasn't like she would be doing any of the interviewing regarding Zhao Yang's retirement. Cheng Siyan prepared to contact Fang Rui, but opened up Weibo beforehand, only to stare in shock at what she saw. The Weibo post by Fang Rui had exploded.

Cheng Siyan had analyzed and guessed, coming to the conclusion that Fang Rui might want to leave. But she needed more resources before she could act on this because she was a news reporter. No normal person would need to show this form of integrity. After making their guess, they could just announce it freely, and then gossip.

What was different though, was that many pro players were also participating in this irresponsible gossiping.

"What's wrong?" This sort of sincere and plain inquiry came from Fang Rui's once teammate, Lin Jingyan. As old partners, they had quite a close relationship, and would naturally show more worry for the other at times like this.

However, most of the comments were full of mockery, just to rile things up for entertainment.

"What's wrong, shameless Fang? Has your shamelessness reached the point where Wind Howl can no longer endure it and has to get rid of you?" Void's Wu Yuce, a player who had debuted the same season as Fang Rui, sent a not-so-sincere and caring question.

　

"Senior Fang Rui's style really doesn't quite align with Wind Howl's current style!" Samsara's Jiang Botao used Wu Yuce's question to formulate his own comment. Though he had only debuted a year after Fang Rui, he still politely called the other senior.

"Wind Howl's high paced and efficient fighting style has placed constraints on the effectiveness of dirty play." The opinion from Tyranny's Zhang Xinjie was professional and concise, and after that, he didn't say a single extra word.

"Tch, what's with all the useless chatter!" Huang Shaotian expressed, but his comment didn't end there. To avoid the 140 character word limit that was contraining him, Huang Shaotian had only used that as a title for his lengthy article that he attached to the comment.

Cheng Siyan subconsciously clicked into the article and was hit with exclamation marks that took up a third of the article. Cheng Siyan skimmed a few lines before calmly closing the article. There was no need to read pure trash talk, and that "tch, what's with all the useless chatter" of Huang Shaotian's was the most irritating thing in sight.

From Gods to rookies, there were many pro players who joined in with the discussion. After commenting, they also reposted and commented on each other's comments. Cheng Siyan had naturally followed all the pro players with Weibo and ended up getting her screen flooded by said pro players. The number of posts were still increasing by the minute. It was clear that these guys had gotten stirred up upon seeing Fang Rui's post in the morning. Just think of the hand speed they had; with every passing second, several new Weibo posts would appear. Cheng Siyan couldn't keep up at all.

However, she refused to give up.

The pure trash talk that most pro players sent were worthless. Cheng Siyan wanted to see if any members of Wind Howl were joining in with the discussion. For a while, she had completely forgotten that she had planned to contact Fang Rui, the one who had started all this. But, as she continuously refreshed the screen, a Weibo post suddenly jumped out at her.

"You don't have a future there. Why don't you pack up and come to Happy?"

Weibo poster: Ye Xiu.

Cheng Siyan was stunned. As for the reason, it was clear upon looking at Ye Xiu's Weibo account. Ye Xiu's Weibo account had been verified with his ID and had been created for a long time now. After so many years, his followers had rose to tens of millions. However, Follow: 0. Weibo: 0.*

That meant, Ye Xiu hadn't used his Weibo at all since its creation. He had maintained his air of mystery and didn't appear in public in any form or manner.

However, after establishing Happy and winning the Challenger League, Ye Xiu began to tread into this territory. He accepted interviews and attended press conferences. In the past, he would've never done any of these. Now, was he even using Weibo?

For a moment, Cheng Siyan didn't even care about the contents of Ye Xiu's post, immediately heading for the comments section where everyone was dumbstruck, half of them asking if his account had been hacked...

However, the pro players had already begun rapidly reposting and trash talking Ye Xiu's post. The discussion surrounding Fang Rui had cooled down drastically. This reminded Cheng Siyan of a boss spawning. Only a boss spawning would immediately draw all aggro, no?

"Holy crap, who on earth is this? Let me take a look!" Void's Li Xuan managed to get the first kill in trash talking.

"Old Ye knows how to use Weibo? How long have you been learning? This is actually Mucheng, right? Mucheng, I see you!" Chu Yunxiu was the second.

But she soon got a response back, Su Mucheng having reposted and commented on her Weibo: "I'm over here!"

"The great Ye Xiu has given his Weibo virginity that he's been protecting for all these years to Fang Rui. True love needs no explanation." Team Thunderclap's Dai Yanqi courageously came up to tease Ye Xiu and immediately gained a wave of attention.

"The truth…"

"Exposed…"

"Repost ten thousand times and your true love will become a reality, come on, everyone…"

"Holy shit, if true love comes, then will Happy get yet another All Star?"

The topic suddenly swerved back to the main road and everyone suddenly realized that this was an important question. Everyone had always looked at Happy as a grassroots team, a new team, a weak team. But now, they had Ye Xiu, they had Su Mucheng. That was already two All Stars. If Fang Rui really went, then that would be a three All Star player team. How many teams like this were there in the Alliance? Even if their characters weren't the strongest, how many would dare leble them as a weak team?

"Compared to Happy, Tiny Herb is the real best option." Wang Jiexi, who hadn't been seen at all during the trash talking, suddenly popped up then.

"Are there even any spaces left in Tiny Herb? Why not come to our Thunderclap?" Xiao Shiqin suggested.

"Come to Void, Void needs more shamelessness," Li Xuan added, but his comment came with mockery. It was clear that he was just here for fun and not really here to recruit. Fang Rui was a good player, but they couldn't just try and take home every talent that seemed good. If you were going to take someone home, he or she had to be useful. If you were doing it for ornamental purposes, you might be willing, but Fang Rui might not!

Cheng Siyan was completely dumbstruck. By now, the only words that were actually relevant to Fang Rui were the nine words, "The weather has changed, my love has been exhausted." However, under this Weibo post, a recruitment war had erupted. Of course, there were plenty that were just there to trash talk or just for fun, but some teams truly could give Fang Rui a stable place on their team.

Chapter 1125: Confirmation

Everything on Weibo was pure nonsense…

Cheng Siyan zoned out for a while before she came back to her senses. Everyone was just playing around, how could she possibly find what she wanted? This gave her a good reason though. If she had only relied on the nine words that Fang Rui posted on Weibo, then it would be inappropriate for her to ask for confirmation from Wind Howl. But because of the disturbances caused by the pro players, this matter had developed to the point that tens of thousands of Glory fans were talking about this topic. If she didn't seek any information from Wind Howl, she wouldn't have the nosiness a qualified reporter should have.

As a result, Cheng Siyan directly called Club Wind Howl. However, they denied knowing anything about Fang Rui's Weibo and asked her to wait for them to talk with Fang Rui.

This seemed like a response to evade the problem, but that was the actual situation at Club Wind Howl.

Fang Rui's Weibo had been posted late in the night, so the ensuing chaos had taken place in the morning. Wind Howl had only found out then too.

Wind Howl progressed very quickly with their investigation. First, they asked Fang Rui about the situation. His current situation in the team wasn't a secret, so they understood.

After that, they consulted team captain Tang Hao for his opinion, who didn't compromise at all. He didn't have any intentions of forcing Fang Rui away, but he would definitely not give up on his playstyle. Fang Rui hoped he could bring out more of his abilities, but so did Tang Hao. According to Tang Hao, catering to Fang Rui's style wouldn't allow him to perform to the best of his abilities, which was why he wasn't willing to back down.

The club realized that things wouldn't be working out. Since Tang Hao and Fang Rui weren't compatible, they had to sacrifice one of them. Wind Howl made their decision instantly. Tang Hao was their ace they would be relying on for the future, so it was obvious that he couldn't leave. Although Fang Rui had been in the team for several years and was at the peak of his his career, he still had to operate around Tang Hao as the ace. If he couldn't bring out his worth then they could only say sorry to him.

In the end, the boss of Wind Howl personally went to chat with Fang Rui and told him he was allowed to leave. As the number two in the team for the past five years, Wind Howl gave him the respect he deserved.

Fang Rui wasn't surprised about the outcome. After all, this problem hadn't just been a one-time issue, but one that had lasted throughout the entire last season. Neither of them were able to work it out during that entire time. This was probably the final hammer.

"I understand, I completely understand. You don't need to say any more." Fang Rui smiled and didn't listen to the boss' explanation any further. He knew that the club was without a choice as well.

"Alright!" The boss of Wind Howl didn't insist on explaining. "Wherever you want to go, we'll try to make things as convenient as possible for you."

"Hm… let me think about it!" Fang Rui spoke.

"That's fine, we have time." The boss of Wind Howl said.

Indeed, they had time. The transfer window had only opened for half a month. Apart from Excellent Era's large clean-out so far, there were no heavyweight transfers.

Where should I go?

After coming out from the boss's office, Fang Rui was depressed.

He had expected this outcome, but that didn't mean he was ready for it. He actually had to leave Wind Howl, the team he had played on for five years.

Perhaps, five years was only a small part of a person's life, but for many pro players, it might very well be all of it.

Fang Rui believed his situation wasn't bad because the five years that had passed were only a phase in his career. He only needed to find somewhere else and start a new chapter. But where should he go?

Fang Rui thought to himself as he grabbed out his phone. He didn't check his phone since last night, so when he turned it on, someone happened to give a call. He checked his phone and realised it was Cheng Siyan, the team's reporter from Esports Home. Fang Rui predicted what she would ask, but there was no point in hiding from a forthcoming reality. He picked up the phone.

"Are you really leaving?" Cheng Siyan finally waited for Fang Rui to power on his phone, and ended up hearing the exact news.

"Yeah! I'm leaving…" Fang Rui said. His eyes started to look around again.

"Where are you planning to go?" Cheng Siyan asked.

"I haven't decided yet..." Fang Rui said.

"There were a lot of teams inviting you on Weibo!" Cheng Siyan half-joked. The trash talk on Weibo shouldn't be taken seriously.

"Weibo?" Fang Rui was at loss.

"What, you haven't checked it yet?" Cheng Siyan asked.

"Nope!" Fang Rui said.

"Go have a look, it's very… interesting." Cheng Siyan could only come up with this word. "Even Ye Xiu commented on your Weibo."

"Ye Xiu?" Fang Rui was shocked.

"He invited you to Happy!" Cheng Siyan said.

"Happy?" Fang Rui started to ponder.

"Go have a look!" Cheng Siyan said.

Team Happy was scrolling through Weibo instead of playing the game in the morning, which was a rarity for them. But in reality, Ye Xiu left after casually leaving the playful message. Guan Rongfei, who hadn't slept for the whole night, had something important to discuss with him!

Happy still needed to collect their reward for killing the Ghost King from Ghost Lair!

Since they could pick their own materials as their reward, it was obvious that they would ask for the opinion of Guan Rongfei, the senior in charge of Happy's logistics. Since Guan Rongfei was most interested and passionate about the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, he was resolute in selecting materials to upgrade the umbrella. However, in order to upgrade Myriad Manifestation Umbrella to Level 75, Guan Rongfei's plan needed him to only use rare materials. The consumption was excessive, so he was hesitating on which materials to pick and prioritize.

They didn't immediately log out last night because they were waiting for Guan Rongfei to reach a conclusion before collecting the prize. After they had waited for half an hour, they couldn't help but return to their rooms to rest. But after they had returned in the morning, they found Guan Rongfei in front of the computer in the exact same position as last night. His screen was filled with documents and the ground was covered in drafts. This guy didn't know which method he should use to treasure this rare prize of self-selected materials, so he even went as far as to stay up the whole night.

What was even more tragic was that he still couldn't come up with a conclusion after staying up all night.

"Rest for now, we're not in a hurry." Ye Xiu said. They still had a lot of time left to collect their reward.

"Shush shush, I'm about to have an idea." Guan Rongfei stared at the screen and ignored Ye Xiu's suggestion.

Ye Xiu could only leave. After that, Su Mucheng happened to find some gossip as she casually scrolled through her Weibo. Ye Xiu went to have a look and also wrote something.

Ye Xiu posting on his Weibo immediately became an even hotter topic than Fang Rui's transfer. In comparison, the news about Zhao Yang's retirement became even colder. After many of the pro players shared the news along with a few lines of blessings, nothing else was said.

After all, retiring was an emotional event. What made it worse was that Zhao Yang's career was quite tragic. Even if a person was extremely dirty, shameless, or inhuman, they wouldn't have the energy to ridicule Zhao Yang.

Although they were opponents onstage, they were still friends outside of the match. It didn't matter whether one was close or distant, when he retired, it meant a permanent departure. They would never see this person on stage again in the future. During this time, everyone shared the same emotions.

Goodbye!

You'll be missed!

Blessings!

Good luck!

Apart from these words, what else could be said?

That was why Fang Rui's four-word post and five-word reply on his Weibo were able to stir up such a big reaction between the professional players. Even if he were going to transfer, who hadn't witnessed this before? When had something like this ever caused so much excitement on Weibo?

This situation was in fact an excuse that allowed them to shift their attention as well as let out their emotions. Perhaps retiring was even more saddening for them than death. None of them wanted to retire, nor would they want to see anyone else retire. Unfortunately, this was a point in life in which each of them had to face. It would happen sooner or later, just like how everyone's life would eventually wither away.

As a result, everyone messed around with Fang Rui. When they discovered Ye Xiu had posted, they also started to mess with him too. However, Ye Xiu was called over by Guan Rongfei, who said he had an idea and wanted Ye Xiu to give advice.

"Go ahead," Ye Xiu said after he came over.

"These." Guan Rongfei handed a piece of scratch paper to Ye Xiu, which had his requirements written illegibly and spaced out. The reward for this extra event was to have each of the five members select five materials, as well as a piece of Orange equipment. In total, that would be 25 materials and five pieces of Orange equipments. What Guan Rongfei had been trying so hard to plan was obviously the materials. What surprised Ye Xiu was that he even spent a whole night thinking about it. If it were up to him, he would have picked materials with higher priority. It shouldn't be this hard to pick, right? But when Ye Xiu received and looked over the messy list written by Guan Rongfei, he couldn't understand his reasoning.

"I think these should be enough," Guan Rongfei said.

"Enough? What's enough?" Ye Xiu couldn't understand.

"I want to do an experiment," Guan Rongfei said.

"Experiment?" Ye Xiu said.

"Hm… an important experiment that will determine my plan for the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella. Only if this works can the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella continue with the established plan. If not, I'm afraid I will need to make adjustments," Guan Rongfei said.

"What experiment? You've never mentioned it before." Ye Xiu said.

"You'll know soon enough," Guan Rongfei said.

"Then what am I supposed to look at?" Ye Xiu asked, holding up the ragged piece of scratch paper.

"Look? Who told you to look? Take the list of items and bring me the materials!" Guan Rongfei said.

Ye Xiu's face darkened. After all this time, this master hadn't called him over for advice, but rather for him to go over and get the materials.

"Right, I'll collect the rewards. Are you about to start?" Ye Xiu said.

"No no, I have to rest for a while. Collect it and leave it there for now, I'll deal with it at night. This must not go wrong." Guan Rongfei ended up talking to himself when he reached the end of his sentence. He then left without looking at Ye Xiu.

This wasn't the first day that Ye Xiu had met him, so he wasn't surprised by his attitude. He took out the list of items and collected five materials for each of the five characters who participated in yesterday's battle. After he collected them according to the list, he transferred them all to Lord Grim's account for safekeeping. They were upgrading the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, so it was obvious that they would be using Lord Grim's account.

After that, new information about Fang Rui came out. After Club Wind Howl had finished sorting out the internal problems, they officially announced and confirmed that Fang Rui would be leaving the team this summer.

Chapter 1126: Boundless Sea

The news was released on Team Wind Howl's official Weibo, so the pro players who were currently active on Weibo were the first to know.

Fang Rui was really going to transfer?

Everyone was stunned. They were just joking around earlier, who would have thought that the news was actually true?

Transfers were a different kind of departure. Even though it wasn't a permanent farewell like retirement was, but to be teammates one day and opponents the next wasn't a pleasant feeling.

Professional spirit, professionalism. It sounded simple, but everyone was human, and what kind of human didn't have emotions? The so-called professionalism was, at its core, simply the ability to control and control one's emotions.

Perhaps some people might enjoy leaving their original team and leap towards the future. But Fang Rui, everyone believed, was not that kind of person. Everyone saw and understood the problems between Fang Rui and Wind Howl. He only left out of helplessness. He personally felt wronged, and the team also felt that it was a pity too.

So as soon as the news was revealed to be true, people couldn't joke any longer.

After seeing that this news was confirmed, Chen Guo suddenly became nervous.

"Can we get him to our team?" Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu didn't know whether to laugh or cry. "You can't just toss a good vegetable into our basket as soon as you see it! You have to see if it fits in or not. After all, we're not a recycling station."

Recycling station… A recycling station is for trash, okay? This is an All Star we're talking about here! Chen Guo resisted the urge to complain aloud.

"We don't need his dirty playing?" But as soon as the words left her mouth, Chen Guo stopped. She looked at Ye Xiu. And then she looked over at Wei Chen, who was casually dangling a slipper from one foot as he sat in front of his computer, smoking a cigarette.

Happy might lack many things, but dirty play certainly wasn't one of them.

What was the point in getting Fang Rui over here? Compete to see who could be the most shameless? Make a team that had shamelessness as its core playstyle, once and for all?

Just thinking about organizing a team like that, Chen Guo couldn't help but shiver. Let's just pass on him, she thought.

But after Ye Xiu finished, he immediately went back to join in on the fun.

Because the news was confirmed, the Weibo war that had entertained countless fans had suddenly quieted down. But in this calm, Ye Xiu, theat man with ten million followers, zero following, and one post, suddenly made his second post.

"So you're really transferring? Happy is absolutely your best choice. Team of champions, master of kings!"

Fuck!

You just couldn't resist?

A team that just emerged from the Challenger League was a "team of champions, master of kings"? Then what did that make everyone else?

"Tiny Herb, winner of two championships." Wang Jiexi wrote in an entirely neutral tone. Now that Excellent Era was no longer in the Alliance, two-time champion was an extremely impressive accomplishment.

"Samsara, winner of two championships in a row." Jiang Botao's follow-up was immediate. Repeating Wang Jiexi's words but adding "in a row" immediately made this accomplishment seem that much greater.

"Tiny Herb wasn't able to defend their title because they lost to the number one team in the universe, Blue Rain!" As expected of the master opportunist Huang Shaotian, he seized the chance to interject with his extraordinary hand speed. Blue Rain's sole championship, originally seemingly weaker than the others, was suddenly lifted in importance.

"Tyranny has your oldest and most familiar partner." Zhang Jiale also joined in on the fun, playing the emotion card because of Lin Jingyan's presence in the team.

"Yup, really quite old…" Then someone below immediately came out of nowhere and made this reply. Zhang Jiale was so mad he wanted to spit blood, but it was just an ordinary player, how could he get into an argument with someone like that?

In an instant, Weibo was suddenly lively again. But it was still unclear as to which, if any, of these teams were serious in their comments.

Because of Fang Rui's skill and status, if he transferred to another team, there was no way he would just be a substitute. He himself wouldn't be willing, and it would be a waste for the team.

His arrival would require his new team to undergo a huge readjustment, and this wasn't something that could be clarified in just a few words. When a team invited a new player, they would first perform thorough analysis and observation of the player. As Ye Xiu said, it wasn't a matter of tossing all the good vegetables into the basket, you had to see if you could use this vegetable to create a suitable taste.

After Fang Rui's confirmed transfer, there were immediately people pulling him this way and that, but it was impossible to gauge their sincerity.

Those that were actually interested in Fang Rui were likely gathered in intense discussion among the entire team. This was no small matter.

After people chattered on Weibo for a while longer, it finally quieted down once and for all. To make a deal right here right now was obviously impossible.

Fang Rui was going to transfer, but where he would end up wasn't something that could be decided in a short amount of time.

However, as Chen Guo watched Ye Xiu rile up the other pros, she suddenly started wondering again. Other teams had managers and bosses and many departments, all of which would need to be consulted for a matter like this. But Happy wasn't so complex and didn't have so many workers. She, the boss, was the "tossing good vegetables into basket" type of person as Ye Xiu put it, and the others like Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were just rookies and didn't have much to contribute on this end. So for issues like this, Ye Xiu was essentially the sole decision-maker, with Wei Chen occasionally giving his opinions from the side.

The other pro players were just playing around; their words didn't have any weight. But Ye Xiu wasn't the same, because in practice, he held the same power in Happy as Lou Guanning did in Heavenly Swords. They were each a pro player, but also the decision-making boss.

"This Fang Rui, do we want him or not?" Chen Guo asked.

"We don't," Ye Xiu said, smiling as he shook his head.

"Wouldn't he raise the ability of our team?" Chen Guo asked. All this time, she was trying to learn more. Although her ability at playing Glory probably wouldn't improve, she wanted to increase her knowledge and analytic ability to be a competent leader of Team Happy.

"He would," Ye Xiu said. "For a player with his skill, as long as you give him enough freedom, he would raise the ability of any team. But for us, his relative value is too low. An All Star player, and we'd have to get him an All Star account, how much investment would that take? And there's the price of his contract, too. If we did this, we'd be putting all of our eggs in one basket. There's no need for us to be stuck on this one tree for so long."

After hearing this, Chen Guo understood. In the end, it came down to the fact that Happy didn't have enough funds. The 5 million award from winning the Challenger League was already split among all the players, and as for the other funds from broadcasting and sponsorship deals and such, Happy currently had around 12 million in usable funds. Wei Chen also had 18 million himself, and he had said that this was his investment in the team and available to use. But neither Chen Guo nor Ye Xiu wanted to use Wei Chen's personal money.

12 million...

Since Fang Rui was already confirmed to be leaving Wind Howl, then even though he was an All Star, the price wouldn't be too high. But if Fang Rui were to come, he would have to have a suitable account. If they also wanted to get the All Star character Doubtful Demon, then 12 million might be barely enough, if that. And there was no way that Fang Rui would be like Ye Xiu and the others, who played without caring about income. He would definitely want a competitive contract. Fang Rui currently had an annual salary of 650,000 with Wind Howl, since he was still in his prime. He wasn't being transferred because of declining skill, so there was no reason for him to shrink his contract. With all of that, even if Happy were to tap into Wei Chen's 18 million, getting Fang Rui over would really put Happy into a predicament. Happy also had daily expenses, and all of its existing members still had to sign competitive contracts. Wu Chen needed a salary for managing the guild too. And there was still the issue of a lack of a stadium, which Happy had yet to resolve.

"Then what are you still causing this ruckus here for?" After thinking over all of that, Chen Guo knew they wouldn't be able to get Fang Rui. But she also didn't believe that Ye Xiu was just doing this all for fun - this guy always did things with a purpose.

"Haha. Let everyone have some fun together!" Ye Xiu said.

"And then?" Chen Guo wasn't discouraged. Ye Xiu definitely had an ulterior motive.

Indeed, on Ye Xiu's screen was a page displaying news of Zhao Yang's retirement. "We can think about getting the character Boundless Sea."

"Boundless Sea, Qi Master? Do we need it?" Chen Guo was surprised.

"It's at least more reliable than trying to get Fang Rui," said Ye Xiu.

"Would Seaside let the account go just like that?" Chen Guo asked. Boundless Sea had special significance to Seaside. It was like One Autumn Leaf and Excellent Era, or Vaccaria and Tiny Herb. The value of such a character wasn't just in the power of the character or its equipment - this was a team's soul and core. One would have to buy the other party's feelings and memories with this account as well, and the price for that would only ever be high, never low.

"I think there should be a chance," Ye Xiu said.

"Why?"

"If Seaside still had strong aspirations, I think that they wouldn't have had Zhao Yang retire just like this," said Ye Xiu.

After all, Wang Jiexi and Yang Cong, who had debuted the same year as Zhao Yang, were both still fighting. But a team without aspiration would let their core player retire; a team without aspiration, similarly, wouldn't needlessly cling to their core character.

Ye Xiu understood this. While others were still discussing as to which Qi Master player Seaside would recruit to replace Zhao Yang, he was pondering as to how to obtain Seaside's core character for Happy.

"Mm… what if other teams think the same thing and try to compete for it?" Chen Guo asked. Transferring accounts wasn't as complex a process as transferring players, since there were no personal preferences involved. Accounts weren't alive, the clubs could sell them wherever they wanted. So if there was competition, the price would just go up. This was therefore a difficult issue for Happy.

"Haha, think about it," Ye Xiu laughed. "Among the current powerhouse teams, which ones have Qi Masters on their main roster?"

Chen Guo blinked. With this question, the first team that popped into her mind was actually Excellent Era.

Player Guo Yang, character Qi Breaker, a first-string member of Excellent Era. Chen Guo had been a fan of Excellent Era, so she was of course familiar with him. But then...

"Wind Howl and Blue Rain." Ye Xiu answered for Chen Guo. "Last season, of the eight playoff teams, only these two teams had Qi Masters in their rosters. Wind Howl's Qi Master was from Excellent Era, this wasn't a class they originally had. He didn't integrate well over the past season, he often couldn't contribute much, so it's more likely that Wind Howl would give up on their Qi Master. As for Blue Rain, their Qi Master Receding Tides is fairly strong, so they might want to buy some equipment that they don't already have off Boundless Sea. But they probably wouldn't directly incorporate Boundless Sea into their team, that sort of base level change isn't their style."

"So that's to say, we don't have any big competitors when it comes to Boundless Sea?" Chen Guo said.

Chapter 1127: Guan Rongfei’s Experiment

The news about the two All Stars meant that this day was fated to be no ordinary day. However, for many, business had to continue as usual. Today was the seventh and last day of the Ghost Parade.

Since luck was crucial in the Ghost Parade, everyone's ranking fluctuated. However, due to the immense difference in the skill level between pro players and normal players, the effects of luck between the two were eliminated. The daily and overall rankings were dominated by pro players.

The last day.

On the overall rankings, Deception still held the first place. Those who managed to rank at the top of the overall rankings had great luck over all six days of the event. Out of over a hundred pro players, the only two who had continuous good luck was Mo Fan at first place and Zhang Jiale at second. As for the pro accounts after them, they had two or three days of bad luck, resulting in a large gap between their scores.

It seemed that the first place overall would be one of these two. However, the current situation had Zhang Jiale almost crying.

Second! Second again! He was second even in an online event; what kind of fate was this? Zhang Jiale was close to vomiting. Why did this world taunt him like this?

Zhang Jiale clenched his fist, sat in front of his computer and waiting for the last day of the event to start. But, something like luck couldn't be changed just by being diligent!

At exactly seven PM, the event began. On the last day, the number of ghosts had reached an unprecedented peak, and the players were immediately thrown into anxious hurrying.

Zhang Jiale wanted to get first place, so Tyrannical Ambition would naturally provide him with support. For example, from the very beginning, they had arranged for helpers around Dazzling Hundred Blossoms who would help him find ghosts.

　

With help, Zhang Jiale had gotten off to a good start. However, after that wave, the effects of his helpers had weakened, because they also relied on luck to find ghosts. Having more people didn't mean having better luck. Though spreading out would increase their chances, as they spread out further and further, it became impossible for Dazzling Hundred Blossoms to run between them.

In the end, he still had to rely on himself. Zhang Jiale had Dazzling Hundred Blossoms dart about before slowly coming to a realization that he had been overtaken with bad luck.

His search for ghosts was extremely unsuccessful. Zhang Jiale could only hope that Deception was having an equally difficult time, but when he took a look at the ranking, Deception was still above him and had gained an even larger lead.

Apart from raising a monster, there was no other way to turn the tides.

Tyranny had a monster-feeding team, carefully and quietly preparing to raise one. They didn't need it to be anything amazing, just enough to send Dazzling Hundred Blossoms to first place. However, the guilds all knew to be aware of this sort of thing, so it was very hard to hide one. In the end, Zhang Jiale received a message saying that their monster had been found and they had been forced to kill it. It was better than feeding it to their opponents.

There was nothing more he could do.

Looking at the rankings, Zhang Jiale sighed. His luck was really quite abysmal today. In the daily rankings, he hadn't even managed to squeeze into the top five. On the other hand, Deception was sitting comfortably at third place, fortune still in his favor.

There was really no helping with something like luck.

The number of ghosts was continuously decreasing. After the easter egg had been triggered yesterday, the guilds all hoped they would get another chance. Thus, the competition for ghosts was even more intense. What mattered first and foremost wasn't if they could find all the ghosts, but maintaining a spot in the top five, or else they wouldn't even have a chance.

At ten that night, the number of ghosts fell to a two digit number and by then, the top five positions were stable already. Deception was still third, and everyone could tell that this was a guy whose luck had persisted for all seven days, much to their envy. Apart from him, the first, second, fourth and fifth were Blossoming Chaos, Angelica, Firebird Messenger, and Combat Form respectively.

Blossoming Chaos was Yu Feng and Angelica was Xu Bin, two All Star level players.

Firebird Messenger was Thunderclap's Dai Yanqi, the runner up for Best Rookie of the eighth season, and an Elementalist like the one who had ended up with the award, Zhao Yuzhe.

As for Combat Form… this character had appeared in the top five for the first time, but had been noticed long ago by everyone. After all, the skill difference between normal players and pro players was very apparent. This person was definitely pro level.

Not many were familiar with this character, but everyone knew that this was a young man from the old Excellent Era called Qiu Fei.

Excellent Era had already fallen, so why was he still here?

No one would hold in this curiosity for a full seven days. They had gone to check when they first started wondering. It was then that they had found out that Excellent Era was still there.

Excellent Era had survived, but it no longer held any of its previous splendor. The new owner clearly didn't have all that many funds, and the Excellent Era he had bought was basically just a skeleton. However, there were two very clear points to this. Of the original players of Excellent Era, he had managed to keep the young man called Qiu Fei as well as his Battle Mage Combat Form. In addition, he had managed to retain Excellent Dynasty.

This Excellent Era was clearly not a powerhouse anymore, but they didn't seem to be nearly as weak as a grassroots team. Just what Excellent Dynasty could accomplish alone was impressive. The players remaining in Excellent Era were extremely united and loyal, especially after the dire situation they had gone through. They would work hard to bring Excellent Era back off the ground.

Maybe it wouldn't be long before they would face Excellent Era on the battlefield again. That was what many people thought, but no one voiced it.

The number of ghosts continued to decrease at a slower and slower rate. In the past, pro players would have logged off by now. What little was remaining wouldn't be able to do much to their score. However, now that they knew of the existence of the easter egg, the top five pro players would stay for longer, until the event ended.

By 11:23, the number of ghosts paused at three.

There was three left, thirty-seven minutes left! The top five had already started forming parties, yet as time ticked by, the number three never changed. Even until the end, when midnight struck and the event ended, the easter egg quest had never been triggered.

On the final overall rankings, Deception stood at first place, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms at second. However, the halo of second place clearly overpowered first place. This was because Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was Zhang Jiale, the guy who had gotten who knew how many second places. Although everyone knew that Zhang Jiale would be upset at this result, many people still came to lament over it. However, Zhang Jiale had already logged off by then.

Everyone had claimed their daily ranking prizes daily. The overall ranking prizes on the last day were, naturally, the best. The number one Deception had obtained three pieces of level 75 Orange equipment, fifteen rare materials, thirty Fuji Heaven Stones that could be used to repair the durability of level 75 weapons, a fifty point skill book, and a significant amount of gold.

The other characters also gained rewards proportional to their final rankings.

However, currently, at Team Happy, Ye Xiu didn't have the time to spare for these rewards, because after sleeping a whole day, Guan Rongfei had finally come back. Ye Xiu hadn't forgotten that this guy had said he needed to conduct an extremely important experiment.

"Have you gathered all the materials?" As expected, that was the first thing Guan Rongfei asked.

"Everything's been prepared." Ye Xiu followed him to the R&D room. Guan Rongfei didn't stop him. The others were curious but had the clarity of mind to not follow them inside, whispering to each other outside.

"What sort of experiment is it?" Seeing Guan Rongfei sit and turn on the laptop, Ye Xiu couldn't help but ask this.

"I'm trying to create a bonus effect," Guan Rongfei said.

"What effect?" Ye Xiu was stunned. The effects on a piece of equipment would naturally determine what use the equipment had. In creating Silver weaponry, usually, the players themselves would ask for the effect they wanted and then the R&D team would go about trying to create it. Of course, rookies probably wouldn't have this sort of treatment and could only do their best to adapt to the current equipment and accounts in the club. However, Ye Xiu, no matter what, had the right to dictate what sort of equipment he had. Thus, the current situation was rather strange. Guan Rongfei was dead set on creating an effect, but Ye Xiu didn't know what it was. None of the effects he had suggested before required so much.

Twenty-five pieces of rare materials!

　

"Lowering the level requirement." Guan Rongfei didn't bother to act mysterious and gave Ye Xiu the information he wanted.

"Lower the level requirement?" Ye Xiu naturally understood what this effect was, but, "Why would we want…"

"I'm going to upgrade the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella directly to level 80!" Before Ye Xiu finished his question, Guan Rongfei gave him his answer.

"Upgrade to level 80?" Ye Xiu was dumbstruck. Apart from someone like Guan Rongfei, very rarely did people manage to surprise him so.

Currently, characters only went up to level 75. If the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was upgraded to level 80, then it would be impossible to equip. Thus, it needed the effect of lowering the level requirement. This effect was rather common on usual equipment, but the pro circle had probably never looked into creating such an effect. This was because this was an effect used while still levelling up. For characters that were at max level, it was useless.

However, Guan Rongfei said that he could create level 80 equipment when the level limit was still 75. Then that effect would naturally be key.

"You're crazy, how is that possible?" Ye Xiu was simply surprised, but he had no doubt that it was possible because he believed in Guan Rongfei's ability. If the other brought it up, then there was a possibility.

　

"It's impossible for other equipment, but not for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella," Guan Rongfei said.

"Why?"

"This is something I've researched for a long time, but I haven't managed to find a way to realize it on any piece of equipment. I've realized that what was preventing any breakthrough was the fact that there were too few materials used to make the equipment, so it doesn't have the ability to create such a powerful effect. However, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, this extremely complex piece of equipment can't be compared to normal equipment. After careful study of the materials, I believe that the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella can breakthrough to level 80. However, before that, I have to test out creating the effect of 'lowering the level requirement by 5' with level 75 materials."

"Alright! Go ahead!" Ye Xiu handed over Lord Grim's account card. Guan Rongfei logged in and went directly for the equipment editor. He was much more familiar with the operation of the equipment editor than Ye Xiu.

"I'm going to start now." After that last sentence, Guan Rongfei focused on operating the editor.

Chapter 1128: Former Teammate

Ye Xiu and Guan Rongfei shut themselves in the R&D room. Although no one else went to watch, they were all very curious as to what the result would be. So, even though Ghost Parade had ended, everyone lingered in the training room.

After tossing around some random guesses without much success, everyone quickly started talking about what had happened today.

"Seeing him stirring up all that ruckus, I thought he wanted to try and get Fang Rui over here. But in the end, it turned out he was after Boundless Sea," Chen Guo said, with a bit of resentment at Ye Xiu's sneakiness.

"Boundless Sea? The Qi Master?" That caught Wei Chen's attention, and he glanced over at Su Mucheng. After hearing Chen Guo speak, Su Mucheng also lifted her head, and it looked like there was something on her mind.

"Yeah! He said that the current strong teams wouldn't be interested in Boundless Sea, so it'd be easier for us to compete." Chen Guo said.

"Is that the only reason?" Wei Chen smiled.

"Is it not?" Chen Guo was puzzled.

"Weren't you an Excellent Era fan in the past?" Wei Chen asked.

"Huh?" Chen Guo was thrown off by this seemingly unrelated question.

"A fan of Ye Qiu?" Wei Chen continued to ask.

"Um…" Chen Guo's reply was vague. Now that she was familiar with Ye Xiu, if she admitted this, wouldn't that boost his ego? Chen Guo didn't want to make him even more arrogant! But she had no way of denying the reality of her past.

"Then when Excellent Era won three championships in a row, don't you know who the partner standing by Ye Xiu's side was?"

"Huh?" Chen Guo had to think. In reality, by the time she had become a fan of Excellent Era, their dynasty had already ended. And the first player she had liked wasn't Ye Xiu, but Su Mucheng. Her support for Ye Xiu and Excellent Era didn't come until after she had become a fan of Su Mucheng.

Of course, as a fan of Excellent Era, she couldn't completely forget about Excellent Era's golden age of three championships. With Wei Chen's reminder, she suddenly remembered.

When Excellent Era won three championships in a row, Team Excellent Era did not yet have Su Mucheng. They didn't have Dancing Rain, nor did they have a Launcher.

However, One Autumn Leaf didn't fight alone. In that era, standing by his side were his reliable teammates, and the one that was mentioned the most was a player named Wu Xuefeng. And this player's class was Qi Master, account Qi Breaker.

All of this suddenly surfaced in Chen Guo's mind.

One Autumn Leaf, Qi Breaker, the partnership that had dominated the Alliance for three years. Launcher? That only came after. The first character who had stood beside the Battle God was a Qi Master!

Wu Xuefeng retired after Excellent Era's three championships. Chen Guo, who had only become a fan afterwards, had only heard mention of his name. But even just hearing about this was enough to get one fired up. Ye Xiu intended to get a Qi Master, and Chen Guo now felt the significance behind that.

"Is Wu Xuefeng returning?" Chen Guo was excited. The partnership that had swept the Alliance for three years, if it could be recreated, then how thrilling would that be? But Chen Guo had forgotten, the character that Ye Xiu now controlled was no longer the Battle Mage One Autumn Leaf.

"Him? Probably not!" As a first-generation player, Wei Chen of course knew Wu Xuefeng personally.

"Why not?" asked Chen Guo.

"Not long after retiring, he went abroad. Never heard any news about him again," said Wei Chen.

"Maybe Ye Xiu contacted him?" Chen Guo said.

"Even if he did, you shouldn't be too excited. That guy's even older than me! Otherwise why else would he retire? Although he was very lucky, he had Ye Xiu beside him. His slipping condition was completely hidden by Ye Xiu's continual improvement. Damn, if I'd been in Excellent Era then, maybe I also could have stumbled upon three championships." There was a trace of envy and indignance in Wei Chen's words.

Chen Guo processed this information. She didn't say anything at first, but instead searched up Wu Xuefeng's name on the Internet. Chen Guo realized that she knew very little about this former Excellent Era player. When speaking of Excellent Era's championship days, people generally only talked about Ye Xiu and his One Autumn Leaf, and Chen Guo was like everyone else, only paying attention to the Battle God.

There wasn't too much information online about Wu Xuefeng. After all, the Alliance was still being established during that period and hadn't reached the level of influence it had now. Back then, the Glory pro scene was very small. However, the development of the Glory Alliance was incredibly rapid, which was evident from the increasing amount of news from each season as the years progressed.

Season 3, another championship, establishing a dynasty, there was much discussion about these topics. But as for topics about Wu Xuefeng, Chen Guo didn't see the respect given to a hero. More people discussed his luck, the luck of becoming Ye Xiu's helper.

"If I'd been in Excellent Era, maybe I also could have stumbled upon three championships."

Chen Guo discovered that Wei Chen's statement just now was a popular sentiment back then. Even an ordinary player dared say this. This was a great compliment to Ye Xiu's strength, but it was disrespectful toward Wu Xuefeng and the other members of Excellent Era. Sadly, Chen Guo searched for quite a while, but couldn't find an honest and reliable analysis.

"It wasn't like that." At this moment, Su Mucheng's voice came from right next to her. Chen Guo turned her head, and saw that Su Mucheng was also looking at the archived news on the screen.

"Wu Xuefeng was an outstanding player," Su Mucheng said. "Without him, Excellent Era wouldn't have won its three championships."

"Ye Xiu said this?" Chen Guo asked.

Su Mucheng nodded.

"Then would he come back?" Chen Guo asked, pointing at Wu Xuefeng's name on her screen.

"Don't know." Su Mucheng shook her head.

No one knew. And the one who had the most direct interactions with Wu Xuefeng, aside from Ye Xiu, was of course Wei Chen.

"That guy…" After being asked, Wei Chen began to search through his memories. "He was truly a guy who relied on his brain and not his hands to fight matches. That might be the reason why he maintained his condition better than I did, even though he was clearly older than me!" Wei Chen gave his serious opinion, which showed that his "if I'd been in Excellent Era" statement was just his automatic trash talk. He didn't disregard Wu Xuefeng's personal contributions to Excellent Era's success.

"He used his brain?"

"Experience. Awareness. Accurate judgment. Precise technique," Wei Chen said.

"Then why did he retire?" Chen Guo asked.

"Please, his condition was only a little better than mine! His age was hanging right there. To be able to play those three years was already his limit," Wei Chen said.

After he said that, Wei Chen crouched in front of the computer. "There should still be some old match videos of him online!"

There really weren't many recordings from matches that had occurred years and years ago. But Excellent Era was at the peak back then, so their matches were more likely to be recorded and thus comparably easier to find now. Wei Chen soon found one, and Chen Guo realized that it was actually a video she had watched before. But just looking at the title of the video, it was obvious that this video wasn't saved to remember Wu Xuefeng.

Ye Qiu, One Autumn Leaf. It seemed as though the Excellent Era of that time period had left behind only these two names. And Chen Guo had been the same, only paying attention to the Battle God's playing and completely forgetting about the Battle God's teammates. Was there some stand-out performance in this match? Chen Guo had no recollection.

The video quickly began playing. Although the quality wasn't very good, Chen Guo still immediately found One Autumn Leaf. But what about Wu Xuefeng's Qi Breaker?

"Hm, seems like he's not in view right now…" Wei Chen said, regretful.

Soon, the two teams in the video began launching attacks. Excellent Era's opponent in this match was a team formerly at the summit, Royal Style.

Peaceful Hermit!

Chen Guo quickly discovered another God-level character. The scythe in his hand flashed with the light and fire of vanquishing demons. A Spirit Guidance was used, and a twisting arc flew into the midst of Excellent Era's formation.

Open battle!

Chen Guo became entirely engrossed in the God-level faceoff between One Autumn Leaf and Peaceful Hermit, until Wei Chen suddenly pointed at the screen and shouted, "He appeared! Right there!"

"Ah?" Chen Guo shook herself as though awakening from a dream, and remembered why she was watching this video in the first place.

Qi Breaker finally appeared on screen. He was currently moving around constantly, his body occasionally vanishing from view. Because the video was entirely focused on Ye Xiu and One Autumn Leaf, the camera didn't move to follow anyone else.

"How sneaky!" This was Wei Chen's appraisal of Qi Breaker's changing position.

"Did he also play dirty?" asked Chen Guo.

"Not exactly." said Wei Chen. "His playstyle was whatever suited the situation best."

The screen still showed the fight between One Autumn Leaf and Peaceful Hermit. But suddenly, Peaceful Hermit flew horizontally, out of view.

The camera immediately swiveled to follow, and so Chen Guo saw that Qi Breaker had used a Cloud Grasping Fist to abruptly pull Peaceful Hermit away from the middle of his fierce battle with One Autumn Leaf.

"Fuck, what a pig of a teammate!!!" A scrolling comment** suddenly appeared onscreen.

"He interrupted One Autumn Leaf's attack rhythm, how overbearing!"

"His brain must be underwater."

Before the fourth comment could appear, Wei Chen turned off the scrolling comments. "A bunch of idiots," he scoffed. "Just now, if Qi Breaker hadn't pulled Peaceful Hermit away, One Autumn Leaf would have been in trouble. Did you see it?"

Chen Guo felt her face redden, because she hadn't seen anything at all. In that moment, her thought process reflected the sentiments of the scrolling comments. She also thought that Qi Breaker's sudden Cloud Grasping Fist had interrupted Ye Xiu's rhythm. If you wanted to coordinate then just directly attack, why pull Peaceful Hermit out of One Autumn Leaf's attack range?

"So you see, he always appeared when he was most needed. Truly a reliable helper." Wei Chen continued to give his analysis.

"To get Boundless Sea, I think… Wu Xuefeng wouldn't come back, Ye Xiu's probably thinking of finding another helper!" said Wei Chen.

"Oh, then who?" Chen Guo asked. Ye Xiu must have given some thought as to who to ask!

As she was thinking, she suddenly heard two loud shouts from the R&D room.

"Shit!"

"Fuck!"

Neither Ye Xiu nor Guan Rongfei were the type to lose control easily. What happened? Everyone immediately crowded around to look.

In the R&D room, Ye Xiu and Guan Rongfei were staring at the computer screen, wordless.

On the screen, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestation Umbrella was flashing through its various forms, but the lowest line on its list of stats didn't change.

Equipment Required Level -4…

Chapter 1129: Many Monks But Not Much Gruel

Glory equipment was separated every 5 levels. Characters weren't though, so lowering the equipment required level didn't necessarily have to be by 5. From the effect bonuses on current equipment, lowering the equipment required level between 1 to 5 levels was possible.

But Guan Rongfei was upgrading the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Apart from lowering the equipment required level by 5, any other effect was useless. It meant that this upgrade was a failure.

"What exactly went wrong?" Guan Rongfei muttered to himself. He had checked all of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's forms. Every single form had this effect, and all of them lowered the equipment required level by 4.

At this moment, Chen Guo and the others had gathered here, asking what had happened.

Ye Xiu explained. No one cared about the experiment's failure. All of them were shocked. Level 75 was the level cap, but Guan Rongfei had wanted to produce a Level 80 equipment. What sort of imagination did this guy have?　　

"Look at my Death's Hand!" This was the first thing Wei Chen said after recovering from his shock.

"No. Apart from the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, it isn't possible." Guan Rongfei shook his head. He didn't seem to care about the discussion that everyone else was having. He had already buried his head back into research again.　　

Ye Xiu and everyone else quietly left the room. After regaining their composure, they began expressing their regret towards this failed experiment.

"The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella isn't ruined, is it?" Chen Guo asked.

"No." Ye Xiu said. It could be considered as a fortune among misfortune. The experiment failed, but the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's intrinsic functions hadn't been ruined. There was just an extra useless effect.

"How reckless! Why'd you directly start with the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella? Experiment with other equipment first before trying to do something like lower the required level!" Chen Guo said.

"That step had been completed long ago. The current focus is to get all of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's forms to have this stat. This step has been completed too actually. It's just that a problem occurred with the stat effect itself." Ye Xiu said.

"Then it'll definitely be possible at Level 80?" Chen Guo said.

"This… before we can ascertain that we can get this stat bonus, it's not convenient to test. If not, if we get it to Level 80 but there was only a reduction of 4 levels, how am I supposed to use it?" Ye Xiu said.

The experiment had failed.

When Ye Xiu and Guan Rongfei saw that the equipment required level had only been lowered by 5, they also felt grieved and frustrated. But the two quickly regained their calm. After all, there were many positives gained from this failure.

They couldn't help with this matter, so they quickly shifted the topic to the Qi Master.

"Wu Xuefeng? We haven't stayed in touch after he retired. I don't know!" Ye Xiu dispelled Chen Guo's guess. Sure enough, he had no intentions of looking for this old general to return.

"Then after we get Boundless Sea, who are we going to find to use it?" Chen Guo asked.　　

"We have to choose very carefully. Do you guys have any suggestions?" Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo coughed blood: "Don't you already have an idea?"

"Did I say that?" Ye Xiu was puzzled.

"..."

"Don't make things up!" Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

"I…"

"Let's analyze the current Qi Masters in the pro scene." Ye Xiu said.　　

Chen Guo understood. This transfer would be a transfer starting from scratch, from character to player.

"We have to get Boundless Sea first though." Ye Xiu said.

"What if we get Boundless Sea but can't find anyone?" Chen Guo couldn't help but ask.

"That shouldn't happen." Ye Xiu said, "An All Star character should be very attractive to pro players. Seeing the current circumstances in the pro scene, I don't think it will be too difficult to snatch an outstanding Qi Master player."

"What do you mean by circumstances?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"Many monks but not much gruel." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly. She didn't continue asking about it. She was also trying to consciously train herself to be a better boss.

Many monks but not much gruel?

Chen Guo pondered over this phrase. Soon, she started to understand what Ye Xiu meant.

Among last season's top eight teams, there were only two Qi Masters. What's more, Team Wind Howl's Guo Yang wasn't in an important position on the team either. In the playoffs, the only active Qi Master was Team Blue Rain's Song Xiao.

Getting into the playoffs and fighting for the championship title was the dream of every pro player. But for Qi Masters, the current circumstances weren't good for them. Including the retiring All Star, Zhao Yang, the Qi Masters were on weak teams without any hopes for the playoffs. And in the powerhouses, none of them had any open positions for Qi Masters.

Zhao Yang had been fighting with Seaside for seven years. Admittedly, a part of that was because of his stubbornness, but a part of that was also because he didn't have many good choices.

This was the current situation for all Qi Masters. Even if they were outstanding players, they were being held back by weak teams. They may want to join a top team, but the top teams didn't have Qi Masters, so there was no opening for them.

Most pro players might not look too highly upon a new team like Team Happy, who lacked resources. However, Qi Masters didn't have any better choices. And perhaps Happy might truly have a bright future.

Thinking of all of this, Chen Guo felt like she had improved greatly. She at least understood that transfers weren't like buying vegetables at the supermarket. It was a lot more complex than that.

Three days later, while everyone was still focused on Fang Rui, the All Star character Boundless Sea was bought by Team Happy for 5.5 million. Everyone was shocked.

They weren't surprised that Happy could take out this sum of money. After all, winning the Challenger League earned them a good amount of money. A price of 5.5 million was relatively cheap for an All Star character, but when considering the current circumstances for Qi Masters as well as Team Seaside's current situation, it was a reasonable price.

After Zhao Yang retired, news related to Team Seaside quickly came out.

Fans would always be proud because of their All Star player or character in their team, but they would never think that sometimes their All Stars would be the burden of their team.

Team Seaside was in this situation. They were a small team. Whether it was a contract for an All Star player or creating an All Star character, it was a huge investment for them. And ever since their start in season three, they had always been doing their utmost to keep up this investment.　　

They had once been proud because of their All Star player and character, but they gradually realized that as they maintained this pride, the growth of the team became more and more unbalanced. A single skilled player and character wasn't enough to help them win more. When they tried improving their other players and characters, they discovered that because of Zhao Yang and Boundless Sea, they no longer had the resources to invest in anything else.

In a nutshell, Team Seaside was a small team with a big team's mindset. They had insisted on this unsuitable management style for seven years. They had hesitated and paced back and forth. It wasn't until this summer, when a new manager took office in Team Seaside, was a decision finally made. Seaside had decided to free themselves of this burden and take the path that a small team should be taking.

Zhao Yang had been let go, so he decisively chose to retire.

Boundless Sea had been sold. Seaside had invested too much into this character, and they didn't plan on continuing. If they weren't going to continue investing into Boundless Sea, there wasn't much point in keeping it. It would be better to sell it to strengthen the rest of the team.

Zhao Yang's retirement, Boundless Sea's sale. Behind those were changes to Team Seaside's management. Ye Xiu didn't know about all of this, but he had at least gotten a general sense of Seaside's position from Zhao Yang's retirement. As a result, he immediately acted and happily took in Boundless Sea.

Seaside obviously wanted to sell Boundless Sea for the highest price possible. However, the top teams in the Alliance weren't interested in a Qi Master, and the small teams were uncertain. The unwavering Happy suddenly stood above the crowd. After some negotiation, an agreement was quickly reached.

Boundless Sea transferred to Happy!

As soon as Happy acted, they grabbed an All Star character. For fans, it was very exciting news. But soon afterwards, doubts about Happy's management style sprouted up, questioning whether Happy would become the next Seaside.　

Two All Stars and a bunch of characters to upgrade. Happy was a grassroots team. Their burden had been very heavy to begin with. Even so, in this situation, Happy actually bought an All Star character. Did they have the resources to maintain such a top-tier character? Would Team Happy become like Team Seaside? Would they become a grassroots team that walked the path of a powerhouse until their demise?

However, the day after Boundless Sea joined Happy, Happy announced that Boundless Sea's Silver weapon, Mirror Moon, had been upgraded to Level 75.

Everyone was once again shocked!

Team Seaside hadn't been able to do it after half a season, yet Happy had done it in just a single day.　　

The people doubting Happy clearly hadn't done a thorough investigation. For example, the club guild leaders definitely wouldn't have given such naive evaluations because no one knew better than them that even though Happy's resources as a whole were certainly lacking, in terms of high-end resources like materials, Happy was quite rich. Ever since the Level 75 update, Happy had obtained the most wild bosses among the guilds.

Happy's situation was completely different from Seaside's. It could even be said that taking this path to the peak was the most suitable for them. Boundless Sea allowed Happy to avoid the initial stages of character creation, which was exactly where their deficiencies lay. On the other hand, directly upgrading a good character to the top was exactly where their resources lay.

However, upgrading a Level 70 Silver weapon to Level 75 in a single day wasn't just an issue of ample resources. It seemed like Team Happy had someone very capable at creating Silver equipment.

Was it Ye Xiu?

Just when everyone made this guess, another report came out. Excellent Era's R&D God had been taken in by Happy after Excellent Era disbanded.

Everything was clear now.

Excellent Era's R&D team was obviously very proficient with Qi Master equipment. Qi Masters had been a part of their main roster. At Happy, Boundless Sea seemed to be blessed by the heavens. The only thing the character lacked was an outstanding player. Suddenly, the entire Glory scene started helping Happy look for a Qi Master.

Chapter 1130: Candidates

"DId he decline?" Su Mucheng asked, after seeing Ye Xiu sigh and close his QQ chat window.

"Yeah." Ye Xiu nodded his head. His tone was filled with regret.　　

Among the current Qi Master pros, the first person Ye Xiu looked for was Guo Yang, who was originally part of Excellent Era. After Excellent Era had been relegated from the Alliance, Guo Yang had joined Team Wind Howl.

There was no need to question the skill of a player that had been part of Excellent Era's main roster. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng used to be his teammates. They already had good synergy with each other, so Guo Yang would have a much easier time assimilating into Happy compared to any other candidate. As a result, even though Chen Guo wasn't too pleased with it, she had to admit that in theory, Guo Yang was their best choice.

Unfortunately, Guo Yang very resolutely declined Ye Xiu's invitation. Compared to Happy, he looked more favorably upon Wind Howl's future. Although he wasn't in an important position at Wind Howl right now, Fang Rui's departure had been confirmed. When his old Excellent Era teammate Liu Hao joined the team, Guo Yang felt like the day he had been waiting for had finally come.　　

"Happy? No thanks!" Guo Yang wasn't interested in Ye Xiu's invitation. Even though Boundless Sea was certainly very enticing, Guo Yang felt like that alone wasn't enough to convince him. He had once been part of a powerhouse. The character that he had used previously, Qi Breaker, had been top-tier too, so his standards and ambitions were high. He didn't just want a good character. He wanted a team of powerful teammates and a team of powerful characters. Wind Howl suited him. As for Happy, he didn't feel like he needed to run away to a new team. So what if you had Boundless Sea? I'm not some small fry who hasn't seen the world.

"Why not try Song Xiao?" Guo Yang said to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu could only close his chat window after seeing this recommendation. He could obviously tell that Guo Yang was being sarcastic. Song Xiao's position in Team Blue Rain was solid. He had a powerful character and his future at Team Blue Rain was bright. There was no reason for him to try out Team Happy. As a result, Ye Xiu hadn't put Song Xiao as a candidate.

But with this recommendation, it was clear that Guo Yang felt like his situation was the same as Song Xiao's. To him, Happy was being delusional asking him to join. Thus, there was nothing more to say. Wind Howl had made it to last season's semifinals. Their momentum was going strong. Transferring from this type of team to a new team didn't make any sense. Ye Xiu had thought that he had a chance because Guo Yang didn't have too important of a position in Wind Howl, but Guo Yang seemed to be optimistic about his future at Wind Howl, so there was no point wasting any more time with him.

Zhao Yang had retired. Song Xiao wasn't an option. Guo Yang had confidently declined. There were only three more Qi Masters in the Alliance: Team Heavenly Sword's Ning Yuan, Team Parade's Zhao Bin, Team Radiant's Sun Haowen.

These three guilds had superb relationships with Happy in the game. However, the team was an entirely different matter. Team Heavenly Swords was an exception. Lou Guanning was very kind to them. If they really asked Heavenly Swords for a trade, it wouldn't be too difficult, relatively speaking. But the problem was that Team Heavenly Swords was a team made up of friends. Lou Guanning's group of friends firmly occupied their spots on the main roster. Even if Zhou Zekai, Huang Shaotian, Wang Jiexi, etc. came to Team Heavenly Swords, the only spot for them would be as the sixth player.

As for Ning Yuan? Ye Xiu had no idea where Lou Guanning found him. He had most likely been invited to meet the minimum requirements to form a team. An entire season had passed, and he had never appeared on stage. Unless Lou Guanning's friend group had all their hands broken, he would probably never go on stage. If Happy actually asked, Ye Xiu reckoned that Lou Guanning would probably just gift him to them. Lou Guanning didn't care. After all, the chances of all five friends breaking their hands were very low.

How could Happy dare to use this type of player though? This person was a substitute with no future at Team Heavenly Swords, yet this person was still calm and composed. It looked like he knew very well that he was just there as a stopgap. He didn't have any excessive thoughts. Just from this middling ambition alone, no one would want to place their team's hopes on him.

Team Parade's Zhao Bin and Team Radiant's Sun Haowen were from bottom-tier to middle-tier teams. It was hard not to overlook them. These two didn't have anything that would make people's eyes light up. They were still better choices than Ning Yuan though.　

However, if Happy wanted to be the champions, getting a player "better than Ning Yuan" was far from enough!

Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu. She didn't know what other plans he had. Going from their theory of many monks but not much gruel, the outstanding Qi Master players were probably buried by others. But from the looks of it, they were buried so deeply that there weren't any suitable candidates in the pro scene. Maybe the outstanding Qi Masters were buried in the game because no team needed them?

Or there was an outstanding seedling at some club's training camp?

Like Excellent Era?

Ye Xiu should be very familiar with Excellent Era's training camp. Excellent Era had a Qi Master as part of the main roster, so if an outstanding Qi Master seedling was found, it was very likely for Excellent Era to keep him or her. Excellent Era may have disbanded, but it wasn't like these outstanding seedlings disappeared. This should be another possible solution.

Chen Guo trusted that Ye Xiu hadn't just started coming up with plans after buying Boundless Sea. When he decided to get Boundless Sea, he probably had ideas in mind. Guo Yang was their first choice. He had declined unfortunately, but it wasn't likely that Ye Xiu put all his eggs in one basket.

What next? Chen Guo didn't ask. She quietly walked to Ye Xiu's side. Chen Guo was able to maintain her composure better than in the past. She wouldn't panic before she got a clear understanding of the situation.

Ye Xiu was scrolling through his QQ friends list, but after scrolling for awhile, Chen Guo was finally starting to get nervous.

No way… we've reached a dead end? There are no more choices?

Just when she was worrying, she saw Ye Xiu turn his head to the side and ask Su Mucheng: "Do you have Song Xiao as a friend?"

"Song Xiao? Isn't he pretty unlikely?" Su Mucheng said. Cheng Guo was dumbstruck. Hadn't they already crossed out Song Xiao as a candidate? Did Ye Xiu have a way?

Even though Su Mucheng was puzzled, she still told Ye Xiu: "I don't have him, but he's in the chat group."

"Oh, right." Ye Xiu mumbled. He found Team Blue Rain's Receding Tides in the pro player chat group and messaged him, but he didn't get any response back. Then, Chen Guo saw as Ye Xiu scrolled through his friends list and found Troubling Rain.

Huang Shaotian. Song Xiao's teammate in Team Blue Rain.

Chen Guo was feeling dizzy. Then, she saw Ye Xiu type: "Is Song Xiao there? Have him check his QQ."

"Song Xiao? Why are you looking for him? If you're looking for him, why are you asking me? F*ck! No way! What are you doing? What do you want? Are you trying to get Song Xiao to join? Are you drunk? Why would Song Xiao be interested. You should ask Guo Yang. You guys know each other. He's at Wind Howl, and he's not doing too well either." Huang Shaotian replied promptly. Chatting with him was very fast-paced. As for whether asking him would save time, only a wise man knew. For example, take his recommendation. Let alone Ye Xiu already trying, in reality, the pro circle had already discussed it and felt like Guo Yang was very suitable for Happy.

"Let's cut the nonsense. Is he there?" Ye Xiu didn't act like someone asking for a favor.

"Tch, it looks like you're dead set on him. Hold on." Huang Shaotian typed. Not long afterwards, he sent Ye Xiu an invite. He had formed a group and added Song Xiao into it. However, he was also there, watching on the side.

Ye Xiu cut to the chase and happily stated: "What do you think, Song Xiao? Are you interested in coming over and becoming a champion with us?"

"Hahahaha, champion? This probably isn't even your biggest selling point, right? Song Xiao, keep listening." Huang Shaotian said.

"Happy has a great environment. It's very quiet." Ye Xiu said.

"F*ck off f*ck off f*ck off!" Huang Shaotian spoke first.

"Haha, I was almost tempted!" This time, Song Xiao replied too. Of course, "I was almost tempted" meant he hadn't been tempted. It was another rejection. His words still stabbed at Huang Shaotian's heart though. Huang Shaotian was quiet at the moment. Ye Xiu was wondering whether those two were fighting right now.

Of course, Ye Xiu hadn't looked for Song Xiao for fun. He had wanted to give it a try. The discussion in the chat group wasn't a very serious one. In reality, in his private chat window with Song Xiao, he was still trying to persuade him.

"Think of Happy's chances of winning the championships. Maybe you'll feel interested afterwards." Ye Xiu said.

In terms of pure resources, Happy indeed couldn't compete with Blue Rain. But what they did have was the possibility of shocking the world. Maybe he was the type who sought novelties and was willing to give it a try?

"Haha, I'm kinda looking forward to it, but I still think Team Blue Rain has better chances!" Reality proved that Song Xiao was rather practical and wise. He didn't seek novelties.

"You're not interested in creating history?" Ye Xiu said.　　

"History?"

"Just think, a new team winning the championships! Wouldn't that be exciting?" Ye Xiu said.　

"Uh, I think I'll pass!"

"Young people have no drive these days! They're so depressing!" Ye Xiu said.　　

"I'm feeling quite good where I'm at, really…" Song Xiao said.

"Think about it carefully. If you're interested, contact me any time." Ye Xiu said.

"Honestly, there's a tiny part of me that's tempted, but I'm still more afraid that I'll regret it." Song Xiao was a nice person. He didn't hide his real thoughts, but because he made it clear, he didn't drag on his refusal. He was a person who was confident in his decisions.

"What a pity…" Ye Xiu expressed his regret, but he didn't pursue it any further.　　

"Another refusal." Ye Xiu shook his head and sighed.

"That shouldn't be surprising though, no?" Chen Guo said. She had to admit that when Ye Xiu talked about the possibility of creating history, she thought it might have been possible. Words like that were truly moving.　

"Yeah." Ye Xiu said. His mindset had been that he might as well try.

"What now?" Chen Guo finally asked.

"Hm…." Ye Xiu replied. He clicked on the chat group that he hadn't closed yet and clicked on someone.

"Dirty Fang, have you ever thought about changing classes? What do you think about Qi Masters? There's one waiting just for you!" Ye Xiu typed into the new chat window.

Chapter 1131: Persuasion

"Are you joking?" Fang Rui was also online, so he quickly replied back to Ye Xiu.

"I'm not joking. I'm serious. Think about it." Ye Xiu said.

"Change my class?"

"Yup!"

"Qi Master?"

"Yeah."

"You're not joking?"

"Of course not!"

"You've got to be kidding me!" Fang Rui sent about 20 emojis to express his confusion and bafflement. It wasn't like no pro had never changed classes before. Quite a few pros had even made breakthroughs after changing classes. However, Fang Rui was an All Star, who had already proven his abilities. He didn't need to make some kind of breakthrough. In fact, he would bear greater risks if he changed his class. The risk would be for both himself and the team he joined, so Fang Rui could only interpret this as a joke from Ye Xiu.

"You're not that unfamiliar with Qi Masters, right?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I can't be unfamiliar with any of the classes!" Fang Rui said. Indeed, this was because they had to know themselves and their enemies well. As a pro player, he couldn't be unfamiliar with any of the 24 classes. In fact, one could say that a pro player could choose a random class and still be more skilled than a normal player. In the eyes of a normal player, every one of the pros was proficient at every class. Of course, Ye Xiu was a grandmaster at an even higher level, who no one else in the league could compare with. That was how he had earned the title "Glory Textbook".

Not being unfamiliar with any class was definitely not a reason for one to change classes.

"You're different. I remember when you started off at Blue Rain's training camp, you were a Qi Master, no?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Damn, you even know that?" Fang Rui was shocked.

"Excellent Era always paid a considerable amount of attention toward Qi Masters." Ye Xiu said.

"I know. I saw a lot of comments that said if you had managed to recruit Zhao Yang, the rookie who joined season three, things might have turned out differently in season four." Fang Rui said.

"Of course, but our monopolization would have destroyed the greatest charm of competition - suspense. In order to let the Glory League develop further, we could only restrain ourselves a little and not upgrade our potential to the limit. What a pity." Ye Xiu said.

"Fuck fuck fuck. Are you serious?" Fang Rui was astonished.

"You're so easy to trick! And you call yourself the master of playing dirty? Looks like I'll have to reconsider if Happy should offer you a position," Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui sent two lines of speechless emojis before replying: "Hurry and reconsider then, stop bothering me…"

"Seems like you have a lot of faith in your future?" Ye Xiu asked.

"It's alright…" Fang Rui wasn't being arrogant. After he confirmed he would be transferring, all sorts of analysis flooded his way. Fang Rui's transferring options seemed numerous. Every strong team in the league, apart from Wind Howl who didn't want him, could offer him a position.

"You want to go to Samsara to form a five All Stars galacticos?" Ye Xiu asked. That would be the most amusing possibility. After Samsara took in Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf, they had four All Star players who were all capable of playing at the frontlines. If they could take in Fang Rui and Doubtful Demon, then the team would have been extravagant enough to make one suffocate. As a team who had the ambition of starting another dynasty, everyone was wondering if Samsara would be so tyrannical.

"Unfortunately, Samsara can't endlessly, no? It's very difficult to support five All Star players. On top of that, Zhou Zekai's contract would be due next summer, so Samsara would pay any price to keep him. Would you compete with Zhou Zekai?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I wouldn't dare." Fang Rui appeared to be calm, this was because Samsara had already expressed that they weren't interested in him. He liked how amusing a five All Star player team would be. Plus, they were a champion team. If he could get in, then it would have definitely been his top choice. Unfortunately, Samsara's response was very straightforward, which might be because of what Ye Xiu had analyzed.

"Team Tyranny has your old partner, Old Lin, and those few are not far from retiring, which would stabilize your position in the future. It seems like a good choice!" Ye Xiu said, but continued. "But even if your position is stable, without those old guys, who would be around you? Would Tyranny still have the ability to compete for the championship title? They are currently gambling with all they have, but their future isn't clear."

Fang Rui didn't rebut, because this was indeed what Tyranny was criticized for the most. Their aging problem was fatal. They lacked an structure that could help them stably transition. Once the few old players retired, then they would have to re-establish themselves. The risks were fairly great because it was possible for the team to not recover from the fall. Ye Xiu was only stating a possibility when he said Fang Rui might have a stable position after the old players retired. It was obvious that Fang Rui would be thinking deeper for his future. He considered that when Tyranny needed to reconstruct themselves from ground zero, they might not need him anymore. Then, he would be stuck in choosing where to transfer to again.

It wasn't a good thing for players to constantly drift around if they aimed for something great. Although there was the saying that if a tree moves, it dies, while if people move, they grow. However, those who move constantly are nomadic, which sounded depressing.

"Moving onto Tiny Herb. After underwent the large adjustments last summer, their player lineup is quite good and they're getting along very well. If they add a new member, they would have to readjust their strategies. I think they would be hesitant to recruit you."

"Then we have Blue Rain. Their ace is stable and their rookie has a bright future, but the departure of a player like Yu Feng also made a clear impact on them. Blue Rain indeed needs a strong player, and it can't be replenished by some new rookie. Unfortunately, this person can't be you. Blue Rain's tactic is giving Huang Shaotian enough freedom. If they add someone dirty like you, by the time the team matches start, two out of five players would disappear. That would leave them with a healer, a handicapped player, and someone random. Unless Team Blue Rain are masochists, they probably won't consider recruiting you."

Ye Xiu finished analyzing the four teams which were undoubtedly, the current mainstream powerhouses. In many people's eyes, the other top eight teams like Misty Rain, Void, and Hundred Blossoms from last season were still a step lower. Wind Howl was currently shifting away from this group, but this was the team that Fang Rui was leaving from.

After Ye Xiu finished his analysis, Fang Rui stayed silent for a long time. A few days had passed since he made his mind to transfer. The conditions Ye Xiu had analyzed were proven in reality. Samsara firmly refused. Fang Rui was personally hesitant with Tyranny, while on the other hand, Tiny Herb was the side who expressed their hesitation. As for Blue Rain, they had a discussion with Wind Howl but gave a vague reply. Apparently, they were contacting another team so they could bring together a large-scale transfer which involved a few other teams. It seemed that Blue Rain wasn't interested in Fang Rui, but wanted to use the marketing effect of Fang Rui's transfer to gain what they needed. No wonder that team revolved around opportunism. They even acted that way in a transfer.

"From what I see now, teams that are not top tier would be a better choice. Team Misty Rain's tactics are pretty unusual. They have long-ranged classes as their main forces, while also relying on skills to weave around to create chaos. Li Hua is currently taking this responsibility. I think you'd be a good candidate because you'd provide more variations and options for them. Moving onto Void, I think Li Xuan mentioned that they needed more shamelessness in Weibo? He wasn't entirely joking, the Ghostblade Duo need another capable helper. Then there's Hundred Blossoms, they are remaking their old path, but they also have a new style. If you join them, you might give them new ideas and help them make a breakthrough. These three were the top eight teams from last season, but apart from them, there is another team that I strongly recommend." Ye Xiu said.

"It's Happy, right?" Fang Rui thought about Ye Xiu's shamelessness.

"Nope, it's Thunderclap." Ye Xiu said.

"Thunderclap?" Fang Rui was surprised.

"That's right, with Xiao Shiqin there, you won't have to worry about not being able to develop your skills. He is someone who can use his tactics to maximize everyone's abilities. Especially with his year in Excellent Era, he improved a lot. Thunderclap currently seems to be no different from before, but I am optimistic about their future." Ye Xiu said.

"What… you're not going to mention Happy?" Fang Rui was confused.

"What? You're interested? See, I knew you would be interested in Happy the most, right?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Interested my ass!" Fang Rui's words were rather disrespectful towards the team, but it was obvious that he was extremely annoyed.

"Firstly, Happy will let you show off your rich experience in changing classes." Ye Xiu said.

"F*ck off, who are you saying is experienced in changing classes?" Fang Rui said.

"You started off as a Qi Master, then Wind Howl recruited you. They originally wanted to train you as a Brawler to succeed Old Lin, but for some reason, you ended up changing into a Thief to partner with him. You've changed classes three times, and you're telling me you are not experienced?" Ye Xiu asked.

"That doesn't count!" Fang Rui yelled. The experience Ye Xiu mentioned was true, but the problem was that he was in the training camp at the time. For a player, the training camp was like a school where everything wasn't set in stone yet, so it was natural for him to make changes. However, when he became an official pro player, he had stayed as a Thief. Fang Rui was only testing out what his best options were when he changed classes at the training camp. It was only when one's class was set and then changed, could it be counted as "changing classes".

"Frankly speaking, Happy is not as weak as you think. Our goal is not low-key at all - we are aiming to be champions! Look at our formation: there's Su Mucheng and me. With your addition, wouldn't we have three All Stars at the frontlines?" Ye Xiu asked.

"What about the others?" Fang Rui asked.

"The rookies are all rising stars. All the big teams kneeled and begged for us to sell them, but they were kicked away." Ye Xiu said.

"Yeah right!" Fang Rui spoke with disdain, but knew that this wasn't a baseless claim. Many teams thought highly of Happy's Tang Rou, but apparently this girl wasn't interested in any other team. A team even threw out a large contract that contained the price completely unfit for a rookie, but she denied the offer without even taking a look.

"I'm not bragging. Even though Happy currently has weak characters, we are gradually improving. As long as we get through the early stages smoothly, we will gain an advantage in our high-end upgrades. We proved this by upgrading Boundless Sea's weapon to Level 75 within a day!" Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1132: Change Classes and Synchronize Your Rhythm to Our Growth!

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui casually discussed. Although it was impossible to know what Fang Rui was thinking, Chen Guo, standing beside Ye Xiu, had been petrified for a while now. It was only after Ye Xiu made this statement, and Fang Rui didn't reply for a while, did she finally come back to her senses.

"What's this all about? Fang Rui?" Chen Guo immediately asked. "Didn't you say earlier that getting Fang Rui would be impossible?"

"Fang Rui as a Thief would be impossible, but if he changed classes to Qi Master, that could be possible," said Ye Xiu.

"Why?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"Because Thieves are more expensive than Qi Masters," said Ye Xiu.

"That's it?" Chen Guo was slightly confused. Happy obtained Boundless Sea for 5.5 million, which was an extremely low price for an All Star account. But Doubtful Demon hadn't fallen that far in status, its price would likely be at least 10 million - the difference was obviously large. But aside from this, Fang Rui's transfer fee and salary would put great pressure on Happy. They would definitely need to use some of Wei Chen's 18 million.

"Don't think so much for now. Right now, the important thing is to convince him." Ye Xiu said.

"Fang Rui switching classes to Qi Master, can he actually do it?" asked Chen Guo.

"I'm not a hundred percent sure either. But Guo Yang and Song Xiao both rejected us, so we have to go for the next best thing and take a slightly riskier route," said Ye Xiu.

"Aside from Fang Rui, what are our other risky options?" asked Chen Guo.

"Those who don't fit us very well, or who aren't as skilled, would be our other riskier options," Ye Xiu said.

"He replied!" The chat window suddenly flashed with a notification, and Chen Guo immediately pointed it out.

Ye Xiu took a look. Fang Rui had typed two words: Go on.

"Dirty!" Ye Xiu first sent this contemptuous reply. This guy didn't bother with engaging in a dialogue with Ye Xiu, he just wanted to hear all that Ye Xiu had to say. But this could be considered a good sign. He was willing to listen, which meant that he wasn't completely resistant to the idea. He didn't think that this was inconceivable. What he needed now was more convincing evidence.

"What else is there to say. Don't you want to be a champion?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Let's be real, who would believe that your Team Happy can win the championships?" Fang Rui asked. After considering Ye Xiu's personality, he hurriedly added, "Aside from Happy yourselves."

"Does belief matter? Then, do you believe you can get the championship?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Of course I believe I can!" Fang Rui, Master of Playing Dirty, responded unusually quickly to this question. But after doing so, he realized that this question could have been a linguistic trap, so he quickly added, "But I still have no way of believing that I can do so at Happy."

"You believe you can win a championship, but as of now you still haven't; I also believe that I can win a championship, and I've won three. Just by looking at this, it seems that my belief is more convincing than yours! And right now I believe in Happy, what about you?" Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui spat blood. What linguistic trap, how low-end! He used his solid, but very much real, three championship cups to smash Fang Rui's baseless confident belief. But this sort of argument was meaningless, it didn't say anything about Happy's actual strength. He really shouldn't get wrapped up in such an argument with this person.

At this moment, Ye Xiu responded with a question of his own. "You know, I've always wondered, why is it, exactly, that no one believes that Happy can win the championship?"

"Because…" Fang Rui typed this word, and then he discovered he didn't know what to say.

Because of what?

A team's strength primarily came from two components: the players and the characters.

Players? Happy had Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, and if they gained Fang Rui as well, in addition to the talented rookies who had earned the world's attention, there was no reason for their roster to be considered weak.

Then, the characters? Their characters were currently relatively weak, but as Ye Xiu already said, as long as they got through the early stages, then once they reached the higher-level upgrades, they actually had an advantage. Fang Rui understood to what he was referring to. The pro players had participated in the fight for wild bosses in the Heavenly Domain after the Level 75 update, so he knew how Happy had dominated all of the other guilds, and therefore the other pro teams. This meant that Happy was rich in the rare materials needed to upgrade Level 75 equipment.

But a character's strength couldn't simply be measured with how many materials were available. The skill of the R&D department and the characters' skill points played a role too. And even if Happy was rich in higher level rare materials, that only meant that later upgrades would be easier. They would still struggle during the early stages.

On this end, Happy was in a rather confusing situation. At first glance, it seemed like their character strength wouldn't be a problem, but this appearance couldn't withstand a detailed examination.

After thinking over this carefully for a while, Fang Rui finally replied to Ye Xiu's question.

"Right now, in terms of players, aside from you and Su Mucheng, they're all rookies, and their instability is evident."

"Rookies can be unstable, but don't underestimate the value of a rookie's ability to grow, especially talented rookies." Ye Xiu said.

"In terms of characters, you've definitely gotten a lot of high-level materials over this past year, but do you have enough low-level ones?"

"It's comparably easier to obtain low-level materials. We've already established guilds in various areas to build up our reserves. Even if we lack some things, it wouldn't be difficult to obtain them. We could easily get them from the market." Ye Xiu said.

"Once or twice, maybe, but does Happy have the funds for frequent transactions?" Fang Rui asked.

"Only frequent equipment production failures will use up too many materials. But Happy invited the core of Excellent Era's R&D, and his skill and experience will allow us to minimize waste," Ye Xiu said.

With that, Fang Rui realized that even the issue of the R&D department had been addressed by this guy.

"What about skill points? How are the skill points on your characters?" Fang Rui said.

"Number one in the universe!" Ye Xiu said.

Fucking hell! Straight to the universe! Even if Fang Rui wanted to retort with a "and I'm number one in xx", he couldn't, because there was no bigger environment than the universe. But he'd have to believe those words! But before Fang Rui even had a chance to figure out how to mock that statement, Ye Xiu had already sent an image to him.

"You photoshopped this, didn't you!" Fang Rui cried out in shock.

The image was of a character's skill tree. Where the number of skill points used was displayed, there flashed a domineering "5500."

5500 points. At Level 75, that meant maxed skill points. Wasn't that even scarier than Team Samsara?

"Tch, would I use such low methods?" Ye Xiu scoffed.

"Are there other characters like that?" Fang Rui asked.

"Sign a contract with us, then I'll show you all our secrets." Ye Xiu said.

"Then just tell me in general, around how many skill points the others are at?" Fang Rui asked.

"They're pretty much all like this. 5400 is the lowest, belonging to a character that can't even raise its head in Happy." Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui continued to be shocked. 5400… His Doubtful Demon in Wind Howl was only at 5355, and that was after he'd lucked out with a 20-point skill point from Ghost Parade! Even with that, at Happy that'd be a character that couldn't even lift its head?

"Now do you see how powerful our Happy is? These are all secrets, I shouldn't have told you," Ye Xiu said.

"..." Fang Rui was still recovering from the shock of the skill points.

"Okay… then if Happy has so much potential in all these areas, then I think it's strange, why not also get Doubtful Demon for me to use?" Fang Rui said.

"Good question," said Ye Xiu.

"I hope that didn't stump you." Fang Rui said.

"Nonsense. If that were a difficult question, then there'd be no reason for me to do all of this," Ye Xiu said.

"So the reason is?"

"No money," Ye Xiu said.

Aside from a spitting blood emoji, what else could Fang Rui say?

"No money is just one of the reasons. If we had a lot of funds, we would consider getting both you and Doubtful Demon, but we would only consider it. In the end, Happy doesn't need a dirty Thief, we need more tactical analysis and research. However, if the option of a Qi Master is there, I would absolutely take it. So we got Boundless Sea, and now we shoulder the risk of having you switch classes," Ye Xiu said.

"Because all of the other Qi Master players rejected you?" Fang Rui asked.

"Yup! Choosing them would be the safe option. But if it's you, you might have something they don't. "Ye Xiu said.

"Such as?"

"The ability to grow." Ye Xiu said.

"You want to use me like a rookie?" Fang Rui asked.

"During this season, Happy will continue to grow throughout, whether the players or the characters. This is a factor of instability, but it will also be our weapon. And your change of class will allow you to synchronize with this rhythm of growth. We will constantly develop new content, bringing surprises to everyone again and again. Unexpected - don't you like that word?" Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui of course liked this word, very much in fact. Because "unexpected" truly encapsulated the style of playing dirty.

"Through our unexpected playing, we'll obtain an unexpected victory. And you? Do you want to unexpectedly change classes? That definitely has the sneakiness of your dirty playing!" said Ye Xiu.

"I…" Fang Rui seemed as though he were reaching the end of his deliberation.

"I'll come visit Happy and then decide," was his final decision.

"Welcome." Ye Xiu wasn't too disappointed. A transfer was a player's investment in his future, and that wasn't even considering the risk of changing classes. If the class change was successful, that was a breakthrough. But if it wasn't successful, then not only was it unfortunate, it was possible that when the player tried to change back, he wouldn't be able to discover the old feeling again, and the player's skill would be ruined for good.

For such an important matter, Ye Xiu didn't expect that a decision could be reached with a chat window. Steamed Bun was probably the only person who could make such a life-changing decision so casually, and of course Ye Xiu didn't want everyone to be like Steamed Bun.

"You really convinced him." This result shocked Chen Guo.

"Not just him, I even convinced myself. "Ye Xiu said.

"How?"

"I suddenly feel that having Fang Rui change classes is really an exceptionally wonderful decision." Ye Xiu said.

"You only like the sneakiness of this plan, don't you?" Chen Guo looked at him coldly.

"No, no. Our team is still lacking in many areas, so if we want to obtain unbelievable results, then we need unconventional moves. Later, we'll move slowly, but this time, we'll take this leap!" Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1133: Fang Rui’s First Day at Happy

"Great Fang Rui, welcome! Please go up the stairs through here."

Chen Guo furtively greeted the person, who had just arrived outside of Happy Internet Cafe. She looked back cautiously to detect any signs of movement from the customers in the cafe.

Living up to his reputation as the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui immediately understood and followed Chen Guo nimbly after a quick nod. He was here to watch Happy, he wouldn't want to be watched by others upon arrival.

However, before he headed upstairs, Fang Rui couldn't help but look back. What he saw across the road was completely different from his memory.

Fang Rui wasn't a stranger to this street. He used to come here for the away-games against Excellent Era.

By the time he came again, Excellent Era was no longer there. But across the street, a new team was born in an internet cafe. The thought that this team might become his new home made him emotional over the changes that took place over time.

Fang Rui followed Chen Guo to the second floor of the Internet cafe. He walked past small, individual rooms, the R&D department, the guild department…

Compared to Club Wind Howl, Happy was obviously pitifully tiny. Chen Guo, who was walking in front, felt nervous. She didn't know what sort of thoughts this God would have about the simplicity of Happy. Chen Guo only hoped that this wouldn't influence his first impression that Happy's skills were also simple.

They didn't walk for long before they reached the training room. Chen Guo took note of Fang Rui's expression when she invited him in, but failed to pick out anything.

When Fang Rui entered the training room, he saw familiar faces like Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. They soon finished introducing the unknown rookies of Happy individually.

"So many hot girls."

This was the first thought that came across Fang Rui;s mind upon his visit to Happy.

"So…" Chen Guo forcibly swallowed the word 'dirty' from travelling out. Although it was rather dirty of Fang Rui to only mention the girls, his gaze didn't dwell on them. His opinion remained an opinion; he had come here for actual business.

"Would you like to try the account for Boundless Sea?" Ye Xiu was a lot more direct. He was already walking over with Boundless Sea's account card.

"Isn't this too soon!" Frankly speaking, it was still too much for Fang Rui to change classes. Although he had come over, he was still very hesitant.

"What else is there to do? You've basically finished the tour around Happy." Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo's face reddened. Happy was truly tiny. It only took them one minute to finish touring the place.

Fang Rui ended up being a bit unprepared due to how quick the tour ended. Everything had happened too quickly.

"Drop the formalities and hurry up. We actually need to assess you to see if you have any future with your Qi Master's skills. If you don't, you might as well go back to your Thief!" Ye Xiu said.

This was way too direct. It meant that whether Fang Rui could get in Happy wasn't solely based on himself. Happy also needed to see if he could play the Qi Master well enough. Chen Guo immediately panicked when she heard this. Fang Rui was already a top tier Thief player, so changing classes was completely unnecessary. Now that Ye Xiu spoke with such attitude, would Fang Rui just leave?

"Fuck!" In the end, Fang Rui didn't have such a bad temper. He accepted the account card for Boundless Sea from Ye Xiu after swearing.

He swiped the card and logged in.

"At the same time, you can also experience Happy's strength!" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?" Fang Rui did have such intentions. He looked around at the rookies of Happy with interest. Who would be his first opponent? Then he saw Ye Xiu sitting down across from him.

"What are you doing?" Fang Rui asked.

"Rookie Ye Xiu would like to experience the Great Fang Rui's Qi Master." Ye Xiu spoke deeply.

"Fuck off!" Fang Rui almost flipped the table.

"An unspecialized. Don't you want to experience it?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Uh… then let's play a round!" Fang Rui accepted after a short moment of thought.

The two entered the arena in game. When Boundless Sea logged on, it naturally attracted a lot of attention, but since there was a password set for the room, people could only see where they headed to without being able to enter.

It was obvious that everyone from Happy would be watching, so they all came rushing over. Just when they were about to settle down and enjoy with a comfortable pose, the match finished.

"Mm, not bad." Fang Rui spoke with a calm expression.

"To last for 1 minute and 38 seconds is not bad indeed." Ye Xiu was also calm.

"I haven't played as a Qi Master in five years," Fang Rui said.

"You're lying. You haven't touched it even once in private? Are you that heartless?" Ye Xiu asked.

Fang Rui was at a loss for words. It was impossible for him to not touch the class at all. Putting Fang Rui aside, any pro player would occasionally play the other classes for fun. If they needed to study a certain class in depth, then they would play that class more often.

"Shall I give you another chance?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Can I fight someone else?" Fang Rui asked.

"Sure!" Ye Xiu stood up and left, but Su Mucheng took his place. Fang Rui nearly swore again.

Then he battled with Dancing Rain. Fang Rui lost again, but this time within two minutes.

Although it was true that a pro player would still be a lot stronger than normal players even when playing another class, that was because the pros relied on their mechanics and experience. If they had to fight another pro player with the same mechanics and experience, then the unfamiliarity with an unspecialized class would be magnified. Fang Rui knew very clearly that he had no chance of winning against Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, so he didn't dwell on his loss too much. He only thought that Ye Xiu was too shameless in setting him up to fight strong opponents he could never beat.

Luckily, Su Mucheng retreated after this match and was replaced by Tang Rou. Fang Rui was trembling with excitement and prepared to teach the rookies just how scary top tier players in the league could be, but in the end, the match finished in 1 minute and 20 seconds. The time was even shorter than the match with Ye Xiu.

The speed that a match finished in was closely tied to the player's playstyle and character, so it was insufficient to judge a player's skill according to the amount of time they took to win. Tang Rou obviously wasn't as skilled as Ye Xiu, but her straightforward and bold playstyle made Fang Rui even more flustered. He made Thief moves subconsciously, and only realized he was using a Qi Master when the character made no reactions.

"Hey, this pretty girl is good…" This time, Fang Rui lost the match rather unnaturally. He was a top tier God after all. Even if he was using the Qi Master, he believed he could fight a rookie, but he ended up losing so directly. The rookies from Happy were a lot more fearsome than he had imagined.

After that, it was Qiao Yifan's turn. Ghostblades weren't specialized in fighting 1v1, and adding on the fact that Qiao Yifan was cautious and careful, this round wasn't as violent as the previous three rounds. Under the slow pace, Fang Rui was finally able to reveal some of his fundamentals as a Qi Master. However, the match still ended with his loss after a few minutes.

"Uh…" After losing against a class that wasn't strong in 1v1s, Fang Rui felt even more embarrassed.

After that, it was Steamed Bun's turn. After a chaotic battle, Fang Rui lost in utter confusion.

Fang Rui attempted to say something to liven up the atmosphere, so he cracked a joke with the next person who came to fight. However, this person's face stayed emotionless as he sat on his seat and started the fight.

When Mo Fan came up, he fought silently and killed Fang Rui's Qi Master without saying a single word.

"..." Fang Rui no longer had the energy to say anything. At this time, the person sitting across from him was eagerly chatting with him.

"Can you even win one round?" Wei Chen asked as he sat down.

Fang Rui was gloomy. If he had been playing as a Thief, then he would have the confidence to fight with anyone, but since he was playing as a Qi Master, it felt as if his hands and feet were tied. He had already grown used to a Thief's decision-making habits after many years, so how was it possible to change all of these instantly with ease? He wasn't a textbook like Ye Xiu.

In the new round, Fang Rui was slowly tortured to death by a Warlock with an abnormally long casting range. Who was he? He was a top tier player in Glory! How long has it been since he had been toyed with like that? This loss was nauseating enough for Fang Rui to puke.

Then he looked at the players from Happy, and saw that every one of them was trembling with excitement. Were they there to gain experience from him? And what's up with that four-eyes over there? He was the Cleric, right? Was he going to join in and bully him, too?

Fang Rui was furious. Although the style of playing dirty required one to abandon their pride, the master of playing dirty currently found it difficult to keep his face.

"Who's next?" Fang Rui grumbled.

Luo Ji lifted his hand on the other side and sat down timidly. He glanced uneasily at the companions around him.

"What are you afraid of? He's easy to beat, hurry and fight!" Steamed Bun cheered his apprentice Luo Ji on.

Easy to beat!

Fang Rui glared at Steamed Bun, this guy only won the previous match out of pure luck! It would be hard to determine who would be the victor if they fought for a few more rounds. This rookie was so arrogant to the point that he didn't know how vast the sky was.

Fang Rui thought to himself as he let out all his resentment in this match. Unfortunately, Luo Ji had the lowest skill in Happy, so even if he was considered skilled among normal players, there was a significant gap between him and pro players. It was obvious that he couldn't resist Fang Rui's Qi Master.

"Oh my, I have a chance! This opponent sucks!" Fang Rui thought with high spirits. Then he started crying on second thought. What was wrong with him? Had he fallen to the point where he could only win when the opponent was bad? This was so embarrassing, so shameful!

Fang Rui was able to finish Luo Ji off cleanly, and finally achieved his first victory in Happy.

"Who else is there!" Fang Rui desperately needed to prove himself.

Ye Xiu thought for a while, and then said, "Should we call Ah Ning up to give it a go?"

"Who?" Fang Rui suddenly fell silent with awe, he thought Happy was finally about to reveal their hidden pro.

"The cashier for our Internet cafe. Ah Ning also plays Glory?" Chen Guo asked.

"I think so." Ye Xiu said.

"You, fight me! Yes you, come on, I challenge you to three hundred matches!" Fang Rui yelled at Ye Xiu.

As a result, Ye Xiu sat down once again. Fang Rui spent his first day in Happy duelling with the Qi Master account, a class he hadn't touched for many years. He strove to find a breakthrough, but he ended up being slaughtered by Ye Xiu's Lord Grim every single time.

Chapter 1134: Fang Rui’s Worry

Fang Rui himself never would have imagined that as soon as he arrived, he would be thrust into a rotating battle session against Happy's entire roster.

At first, Fang Rui was truly and thoroughly beaten up. He was unable to immediately change his longtime habits and decision-making, which led to flaws in his Qi Master playing and resulted in defeat after defeat.

However, as time passed, he gradually adjusted to the class, and his win rate steadily increased. Facing the rookies, he was no longer defeated so soundly.

"As expected of the class-changing expert!" Ye Xiu said, standing up. This round, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim lost to Fang Rui's Qi Master Boundless Sea.

"Class-changing expert my ass!" Fang Rui maintained that his earlier classes weren't changing classes, but rather choosing a class in the first place.

With this victory against Ye Xiu, Fang Rui felt as though he had just successfully achieved a major accomplishment. He stretched, and casually glanced at the clock. What he saw made him jump in shock.

Three hours. It had already been three hours.

Fang Rui had completely forgotten the time. His entire heart had been immersed in Glory, his mind had been filled only with thoughts of how to play with the Qi Master in his hands and defeat this whole crowd of Happy players. And during these three hours, Happy had been rotating its members, while he hadn't had any rest aside from the time it took for them to switch.

Fang Rui's ability to adapt to the Qi Master, as well as his energy and focus, were all worthy of admiration. After Ye Xiu stood up, no one went to take his place. Fang Rui looked around, and it seemed like no one else was going to come, so he began to give his commentary on the match that had just ended.

"You made too many mistakes in this match," Fang Rui said to Ye Xiu.

"You're right. After seeing you play so hard, I truly couldn't bear it anymore, so I went a little easy on you," said Ye Xiu.

"Fuck, if you're not satisfied then let's go again!" Fang Rui yelled. This "going easy" wasn't considerate at all, at least pretend to hide it! And it was one thing to throw a match so obviously, but to just directly admit it like that after it was over? Just because he was the master of playing dirty didn't mean he had no dignity.

"Don't be like that, let's eat first and then go again!" Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui stared blankly. Only now did he realize that he really was a little hungry now, it was about time for dinner.

Chen Guo had already made dinner plans for all of them, making a reservation at a nearby, relatively nice restaurant. All of Happy headed over, as well as Fang Rui.

At the table, Fang Rui didn't say much. His appetite seemed fairly normal. After quickly eating his fill, he played around with the straw in his drink.

"You played the Qi Master pretty well, you have a lot of potential!" At this moment, Ye Xiu gave him a high degree of recognition.

Fang Rui rolled his eyes and didn't bother to answer. In reality, Fang Rui knew better than anyone else whether he could play a Qi Master. After all, he wasn't some newbie, and he had played Qi Master very early on. He was very clear on whether or not he could manage it, and the fact that he hadn't immediately turned down Ye Xiu's offer showed that he knew the possibility existed. And he also knew that Ye Xiu could see this as well; there was no way he had pulled him over here just to test him and see how things went from there.

This afternoon of battling was, in theory, to test Fang Rui's ability to change classes to Qi Master. But in reality, it was a way for Fang Rui to see Happy's strength.

Happy's strength surpassed Fang Rui's expectations. Each of the rookies had their own styles, and as Ye Xiu had said, they all had plenty of room to grow. Once they completely matured as players, what kind of power would this team possess?

And over the course of this afternoon, not only did he see Happy's players, he was also able to see their characters. Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea were All-Star characters that didn't need to be mentioned, as they'd be a strong addition to any team. But Happy's other characters were plenty strong as well, each with Silver equipment. Although they couldn't compare to a powerhouse team, they were extremely well-off for a new team.

"How about it, after seeing everything in person, how do you feel about Happy?" Ye Xiu now asked him.

"Mm… not bad," Fang Rui said. He didn't directly say that Happy was approaching powerhouse levels, but from what he had seen, whether the players or the characters, they had all surpassed his predictions.

"Good, then let's talk about your compensation. You saw us, our conditions right now are rather poor, a whole bunch of people crowded in an Internet cafe to train. Ten people at a meal and we only have eight dishes, and no soup. What's your current salary? 6.5 million? Is that before or after tax?"

"Before tax," Fang Rui said.

"It's already that much before tax. Do you have no shame?" Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui was speechless. What was there to be ashamed about? If you're trying to bargain down my salary, then just directly say it! But the problem was, he clearly still hadn't agreed to join Happy! Why were they already talking about his contract? And also, what was this about eight dishes and no soup? Wasn't that just because the rest of dishes hadn't been brought out yet?

The door of the private room was suddenly pushed open. The server entered with a large tray and placed two more dishes on the table.

"This was really bad timing…" Ye Xiu complained. The rest of the table was silent. To use that as an argument, are you treating Fang Rui as someone who can't count? He was clearly right here with all of us when the dishes were being ordered!

But no matter what, Happy still hoped that Fang Rui would concede a little bit when it came to the contract. This point, at least, Ye Xiu made clear to Fang Rui.

"If you have any thoughts, just say them directly! Don't sit there being sneaky." After seeing Fang Rui playing with his drink without saying anything for a while, Ye Xiu spoke up again.

"Damn!" Fang Rui was gloomy. He was just taking some sips of his drink, what was so sneaky about that? Besides, what thoughts could he have? Happy was really not bad, better than he had expected, but something about this still didn't sit well in his heart. He still feared this drastic change, and this fear caused his hesitation. Even if what he saw at Happy surpassed his expectations, his worry still had yet to be eliminated completely.

"I don't know…"

I don't know, that was that. If only he knew, then Fang Rui would have a way of getting rid of the worry in his heart. Happy was clearly better off than he had imagined, and he had even begun to anticipate Happy's future, so why was he still so uneasy?

Was there something about Happy that still nagged at him? The simple accommodations? Fang Rui was never one to care about that. A contract where he'd have to make some compromises? Fang Rui also wasn't one to care too much about money. The identity of being new to the Alliance? To be honest, Fang Rui rather liked this identity, it allowed them to bring more surprises.

He thought and he thought, but he was still at a loss. He didn't know what he was worried about, but he was worried.

The room was quiet. No one even moved to touch the dishes that had just been brought up, and the overall atmosphere was rather cold. Fang Rui, lacking something to say but not wanting the silence to drag on, tossed out a very ordinary question: "How did you all come together anyway?"

"Us?" Ye Xiu blinked, and then casually went around the room, describing all of their backstories to Fang Rui.

Fang Rui had only wanted to lighten the atmosphere, and so he asked a question that could be discussed for a while. To be honest, he didn't really care about the answer. But as he listened, Fang Rui suddenly jolted. He realized what was worrying him about Happy. After Ye Xiu finished his introductions, Fang Rui immediately asked a question that was important to him.

"How many more years do you plan on playing?"

"Me?" Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, you!" Fang Rui said.

"I hope that I can continue to play forever!" Ye Xiu said.

"But we both know that that's impossible," Fang Rui said. "Especially for you, playing an unspecialized, that's a heavy burden on you, and it will definitely shorten the lifespan of your career. The fact that you've been able to maintain this condition up until now is already a miracle in my eyes. But, how much longer can you maintain it? One year? Two years?"

"This… who can say for sure?" Ye Xiu said.

"Then, after you retire, what about Team Happy?" At last, Fang Rui asked the question that had been worrying him all this time.

Every team had its motivation in being established, and this motivation would be the most fundamental force pulling together the members of a team. Just looking at the current Alliance, every team's existence was undoubtedly based on profit. All of the bosses of the teams were trying to maximize their profits, so they concentrated on the expansion and development of their teams. But what about this Team Happy?

This team was pulled together by Ye Xiu after his retirement. It didn't have any major financial backing, and the so-called boss was just the boss of an Internet cafe who was severely limited in power. Fang Rui could sense that the authority of this supposed boss was ultimately less than that of Ye Xiu.

Then what was Ye Xiu's motivation in establishing this team?

It could be anything, but Fang Rui was certain that it wasn't for profit.

Relying on profit to sustain oneself was an uncomfortable feeling. But unfortunately, this was the cruel reality of the world. Only profit was eternal. Aside from that, things like the players' love of Glory, or their pursuit of the championship title, would always fade with the passage of time. And, with their declining condition, the players would ultimately have no way of continuing.

Ye Xiu was unquestionably the foundation upon this team could exist, and Fang Rui would never doubt his support and passion for this game. But even with such a heart, Ye Xiu would leave one day, and this day could come very soon. When that time came, what would happen to Team Happy? Would they have the cohesion that they showed today? Just considering Happy's boss and her financial power, it was uncertain if she could even hold onto all of these talented players. The better Happy performed, the more tragic the scene would be when that day arrived.

Speaking of which, Happy's rookies were already exceptional, and Fang Rui was rather surprised that none of them had been pulled away so far. Happy's financial power couldn't compete with any of the other teams. Was Ye Xiu's presence alone enough to keep them here? Was this guy's personal charisma really that great?

Fang Rui had his doubts. But regardless of his charisma or lack thereof, if this team had completely relied on Ye Xiu to come together, then that only increased the worry in his heart. In this sort of situation, it was truly difficult to predict what Happy's future would look like. If Fang Rui came to Happy, he would be switching classes. He couldn't take such a large gamble on a team that would disperse after Ye Xiu's departure.

"You want to know about Team Happy after my departure?" Ye Xiu said. "Then you'd better ask my boss!"

Chapter 1135: An Entirely New Future

"Huh? Me?"

When such a critical question was suddenly sent her way, Chen Guo couldn't help but panic. True, it wasn't like she'd never thought about this question before. She was always working hard to learn and improve, both in order to lighten Ye Xiu's burden, and so that when Ye Xiu was no longer around, she could still look after this team. But to suddenly have to answer this question right here and right now, she was completely unprepared.

But now, she had no more time.

She sensed the significance of this question, that this was Fang Rui asking about Happy's future. And Happy's future would be the deciding factor as to whether or not he would throw his lot in with this team.

If she, the boss, didn't have an unshakable resolve, then how could the players be at ease?

Chen Guo took a deep breath. It was time to muster her resolve.

"Even after Ye Xiu leaves, Happy will continue forward," she began.

"Oh? How so?" Fang Rui asked.

"If he's willing, we of course will retain him as a coach, or for any position he's interested in." Chen Guo first made plans for Ye Xiu.

"As for the others, I believe that they will have completely matured by then, enough to carry our team," Chen Guo said.

"Oh? Then how can you guarantee that they won't all just leave?" Fang Rui's gaze suddenly sharpened, and became calculating. "There are many temptations in the professional scene. I know that you've already received a few invitations from other teams and declined all of them. But right now, you're still just newbies in the Alliance. In a year or two, if you became All-Stars, champions, your value will reach a peak. At that time, the temptations you'll face will be unimaginable. Money, status, and countless other things, are you sure that you won't be swayed by any of it?"

Fang Rui felt that his speech would pierce straight into the soul, that no one would dare retort. But at that moment, someone at the table said, with utter conviction, "I'm sure."

It was Tang Rou.

What a pretty girl, but right now, in Fang Rui's eyes, she only seemed hypocritical or naive. She didn't even think before opening her mouth and saying "I'm sure." She seemed to have much too high of an opinion of herself.

"The pretty girl sure has confidence, huh?" Fang Rui snickered, and his skepticism was clear in his every word. He was about to teach this arrogant girl something about the real world. "Don't you know…"

"That's nothing!"

But just as Fang Rui was about to give an example, he was interrupted by Chen Guo. Chen Guo of course knew that Fang Rui wanted to give her a slap in the face, but at the same time she knew that he would fail, and that it would be his own face receiving the slap. To prevent Fang Rui from suffering that awkwardness, it was better to explain first.

"She really won't be swayed, really," said Chen Guo.

"Oh?"

"Her dad is Tang Shulin. If you don't know him, then look him up online." Chen Guo, sitting next to Fang Rui, patted him on the shoulder.

This sort of business tycoon wouldn't be a household name, so Fang Rui truly did not know. However, he at least could tell that this was likely a remarkable background, so he didn't argue, immediately searching up on his phone under the table. Not much longer, he sat up straight again and lifted his head. His facial expression didn't change at all, but he lifted his chopsticks. "Come on everyone, let's eat, how come no one's touched these two dishes that were just brought out?"

Everyone laughed, but they didn't call him out.

To talk about money and status in front of Tang Rou, that was like talking about Glory skill in front of Ye Xiu. Wasn't it just throwing yourself against a rock? It was impressive enough that Fang Rui remained this calm in the face of that, so let him restabilize!

Everyone ate quietly and didn't say much. Fang Rui, who had earlier expressed that he had eaten his fill, was clearly eating the most right now. It was as though he wanted to use this food to erase what had just happened. While he was searching online, he already sensed that this pretty girl had an extraordinary background, but when he finally got his answer, his eyes still almost flew out of his head.

"Eat, eat."

When Fang Rui said this, he really wanted to eat the plate itself as well.

Thus, after that, Fang Rui couldn't bring himself to mention anything else about temptation. What if this Miss Tang just waved her hand and bought out the entire Glory Alliance? Then she'd be the one distributing prize money to the various teams! And he had wanted to talk to her about temptation, temptation his ass!

"Ah, Happy is really… too full of potential, ha…" Fang Rui said.

When Chen Guo heard this, she knew that he had misunderstood, treating Tang Rou's background as Happy's background. In reality, these were two completely separate things. Tang Rou was like the rest of them ordinary players, signing a contract to earn her salary. She didn't exercise any power outside of that.

But still, this sort of feeling, the fox pretending to have the power of the tiger, it wasn't a bad feeling at all!

Chen Guo glanced at Tang Rou and saw that she was making a face at her right now! Chen Guo laughed. This was something she very much liked about Tang Rou. When Happy found out that she came from such a high background, it seemed like there was some new distance between her and the rest of them. Even Chen Guo, who had known her the best, hadn't adjusted immediately after finding out.

But Tang Rou faced this unusual treatment directly. She wasn't arrogant about her background, but she didn't try to avoid it either. She wasn't like the many hypocritical ladies who would want the people around her to treat her like an ordinary person. She was herself, the same Tang Rou she always was, who would never run from anything. And so, the barrier caused by her background gradually faded, and everyone saw that Tang Rou was still Tang Rou, nothing had changed! The barrier only came from each person's imagination, and so when everyone saw reality, everything returned to the way it always was.

On the other hand, it was funny and entertaining for these guys around her to watch people be terrified after learning about her background. Such as Fang Rui, who was currently burying himself in his food. There was a long period of time where he didn't say anything, and everyone thought it was just too great.

But Chen Guo was, in the end, a responsible person, so she clarified for Fang Rui.

"Here, Little Tang is just an ordinary player, no different from anyone else," Chen Guo said.

"Mm." Fang Rui nodded. This time, he didn't say anything directly, he hid his true thoughts. Tang Rou was just an ordinary player? That was impossible. It looked like this Boss Chen hadn't truly understood. Her background meant that she was a wildcard, a player that couldn't be controlled by any team, including Happy.

Money, status, and so on had no way of tempting her, which also meant they had no way of controlling her. She belonged to herself and herself alone. As long as she wanted to play, she could keep playing with Happy. But if one day she decided she no longer wanted to play, then who would be able to keep her? What would stop her from leaving? The contract? To forcibly break the contract only required money, and would that be a problem for her?

Her powerful background placed her above the spirit of the contracts upon which society was built. This was somewhat unfair, but it couldn't be helped. For Tang Rou, they could only rely on her personal character, so Fang Rui didn't say anything more.

Ye Xiu chose this moment to open his mouth.

"Happy's future will be shaped by its players. You only want to be a spectator, taking a ride and reaping the profits? That's just too dirty, too shameless! Do you dare come with us to build the future together? Do you dare come with us to face your so-called unimaginable temptations of money and status?"

That's right. He was worried about whether or not Happy could keep its players, but what about himself? If he also became a member of Happy, then when that day came, would he also be swayed? Before doubting others, shouldn't he first strengthen his own resolve? If everyone worked together and created a unified team, there was no need to worry this much. If people left, then more would come to replace them.

That's right. That's how it should be.

Fang Rui slammed his hand on the table. "I'll join Happy!"

"Excellent, welcome!" Chen Guo exclaimed.

"With me here, the championship has nowhere to run!" This dirty player had a face swelled with confidence.

"Good. Then let's talk about the issue of your contract," Ye Xiu said.

"Damnit, can't you let everyone be excited together for three or five minutes?" Fang Rui was depressed. The atmosphere was wonderful, but with talk of money, the feeling was somewhat ruined.

"Excited about what? Are you a rookie or something?" Ye Xiu said.

"So what do you think about my contract," Fang Rui said.

"You see, we're very poor right now, only ten dishes for ten people, and no soup…"

Just as he said this, there was a knock at the door again. "Excuse me, but could you open the door please? The soup is here!"

Qiao Yifan, who was sitting closest to the door, immediately pushed it open, and the server entered with the soup, his forehead coated in sweat. "The door was locked, I hope I didn't interrupt?"

"Don't worry, it's fine," Chen Guo said, and the server placed down the soup and quickly left.

"Shameless!" Fang Rui said to Ye Xiu.

"In any case, we don't have any money!" Ye Xiu slapped the table. "6.5 million is impossible. How about 650,000!"

"Fuck, don't be too rude! I'm an All Star player, after all! If that contract got released to the public, how could I show my face?"

"To everyone else, you can say 65 million!" Ye Xiu said.

"Do you think everyone else is an idiot?"

"Then how much do you want?"

"It's fine if you reduce it a bit, but at least 5 million, don't you think?" Fang Rui said.

"5 million, do you have no shame? Being an All-Star is impressive, sure, I'll toss all my All-Star nominations in front of you like a pile of bones! I could bury you in all the honors I've won! And yet despite my achievements, I have to kneel in front of the boss's door every day and beg to get my pay here at Happy! Who do you think you are, asking for 5 million in front of me?"

Fang Rui was speechless, and then started half crying. "That's not what I meant!"

"You youngsters, always thinking about money money money. Why don't you think about how much glory you'll obtain by joining Happy? That's something that no amount of money can buy," Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui was once again speechless. How was this guy so shameless? He made winning a championship seem as easy as buying a red bean bun. If it were truly a hundred percent guaranteed that they'd win a championship, Fang Rui would be willing to join for no money at all, but of course that could never be the case in competition.

Chen Guo had enough of this nonsense, and finally interjected with her voice of reason. "Right now, we really are tight on money. Aside from your contract, we also still have the transfer fee with Wind Howl, and we don't know what price they'll ask for. This first year, what do you think about 3 million?"

"Compared to that guy, you really are a good person… but this…"

"This is really too low, I know, but after lasting through the first year, we can discuss again next year if we're in a good position. If you're worried, you can write it in the contract, that's fine too."

"Hm… Alright!" Fang Rui finally nodded. After all, he didn't come to Happy to get a high-paying contract, so he had been prepared.

Ultimately, he was here because he wanted an entirely new future.

Chapter 1136: Significant Transfer

Everyone suddenly seemed to gain an appetite, so they ordered a few more dishes and ate with a lively atmosphere. Fang Rui left the next day, and all that was left were the contract negotiations with Club Wind Howl.

When the player had a preference as to where they were going, it generally wasn't difficult to reach a deal. Wind Howl was truly shocked at Fang Rui's final choice, but in the end they respected his wishes. However, they were disappointed when Happy said that they weren't going to buy Doubtful Demon as well.

They had originally planned to sell off Fang Rui and Doubtful Demon together, permanently making the rookies Tang Hao and Zhao Yuzhe the core of their style, and abandoning the dirty playstyle once and for all. Who would have thought that Fang Rui would leave without his character? He actually wanted to change classes to Qi Master?

"You… Are you sure?" There were still feelings between Wind Howl and Fang Rui after so many years. For someone who'd already become an All-Star player, it seemed like there was no reason for him to change classes. It was illogical. Seeing that Fang Rui wanted to do this, Wind Howl had to say something, whether it was for Fang Rui's own interests, or their plan to sell the player and character together.

"I'm sure." Since returning from Happy, Fang Rui was completely certain of his decision.

What kind of poison did Happy brainwash this guy with, to convince him to accept these conditions? Wind Howl, after having their plan messed up, was at a loss as to what to do. But for the sake of the team's image, they had to respect the wishes of the player, especially for an important player like Fang Rui.

Wind Howl then planned to negotiate with Happy, but Happy completely rejected their attempts to sell Doubtful Demon, so in the end, Wind Howl could only start putting up a price. In terms of price, this sort of voluntary transfer sale would never go too high. Additionally, Fang Rui was mediating, so Wind Howl didn't expect to make much money from this. After they talked back and forth, they soon decided on a transfer fee of 4 million.

After news of the transfer was released, the entire Alliance wondered if they had read incorrectly. Fang Rui chose Happy? This was as shocking as when Xiao Shiqin chose to transfer to the relegated Excellent Era last season! Were all the All-Stars taking unconventional routes now?

But no matter what, the transfer satisfied the rules, so Fang Rui's transfer was quickly approved. Now, Fang Rui was officially a member of Happy.

Because there weren't too many issues to be worked out, the transfer was swiftly completed. The media was still in the middle of figuring out which teams were more interested in Fang Rui when the contract was already signed. When the media caught wind of this, Happy was already holding a news conference!

Happy didn't yet have a specialized PR department, so the conference was arranged by a PR company they had found to help. After the news released, the various esports media all came without even being invited. It was a full house, and there were endless requests for private interviews.

Chen Guo, Ye Xiu, and Fang Rui were the three participants in the press conference, and it was completed as planned. Meanwhile, the rights to an exclusive interview were of course given to the reporter Chang Xian of City H's Esports Home.

Chang Xian was ecstatic!

When he had first noticed Happy, he hadn't been thinking about gambling on their growth as a team. He was just a newbie in the industry, how would he have such foresight? He was just doing the ordinary thing, reporting on this grassroots team that had gained some attention. Who would have thought that with this gamble, he had won big? After Happy won the Challenger League championship, Chang Xian felt how fortunate he was. He could sense his status at Esports Home rising, and the editor-in-chief spoke with him in person much more often.

And now, Fang Rui was transferring to Happy! In the summer transfer window, he had obtained the first major exclusive interview since Excellent Era disbanded. Undoubtedly, this interview would be on the front page of next week's edition of Esports Home.

Facing Fang Rui, Chang Xian was slightly apprehensive. He had been with Happy's members for a while now and was familiar with all of them, but that was partly because of their humble beginnings as a team. Chang Xian had never felt too much of a professional atmosphere from them. But Fang Rui was different. Facing an interview, he had the aura of a God. Chang Xian was reminded of when he was just starting out in the industry, and the pressure he felt when he was tagging along with senior reporters to carry their bags. And now, he was facing this aura by himself.

"God Fang Rui, may we begin?" Fang Rui steadied his emotions. He knew, after today, he would be facing countless interviews like this.

Fang Rui was transferring. This was the first big news.

Fang Rui was switching classes. This was the second big news.

At the press conference, when they learned that Fang Rui would be playing with Boundless Sea, the entire pro circle went wild.

What was the reason?

During the press conference, Fang Rui grinned and said, "Because Happy's broke. They can't afford Doubtful Demon, so I could only switch to using Boundless Sea."

Who would believe that?

The number one Thief, an All-Star player, was treated like this after being bought? Even if Happy was willing to waste talent like that, how could Fang Rui agree to such treatment?

Compared to Fang Rui's transfer, his change to Qi Master suddenly became a much more exciting topic of discussion.

"This is truly an unprecedented decision. If I recall correctly, before you, there's never been a top player who chose to change classes like this?" one reporter said.

"What do you mean?" Ye Xiu suddenly interjected, dissatisfied. "Didn't I do that too?"

Silence.

This, how to put it? Even if an unspecialized wasn't a real class, it certainly wasn't the Battle Mage class that Ye Xiu had always played. This was indeed a class-changing player, and he was sitting right in front of all of them. How had they missed it? The reporter who had spoken was filled with shame, while the others asked themselves, why hadn't they realized that Ye Xiu was also a class-changing player?

And the more attentive reporters now realized another point. "I remember, Happy's Qiao Yifan, when he was in Tiny Herb, he was using an Assassin, but now he's changed classes to a Ghostblade."

"You're correct." Ye Xiu nodded.

The reporters glanced at each other. Team Happy actually had three class-changing players. Was this Happy's style, some hidden attribute?

The purpose of the press conference was primarily to deliver news, so the reporters didn't have much time to ask questions. There was simply no opportunity for them to get to the bottom of this situation. And the one who had obtained the opportunity to do so was Chang Xian, with the exclusive interview. He was now rather smug as he asked about the details.

"Why did you decide to change classes to Qi Master?"

"Because of Happy's invitation."

"What kind of invitation was it, that could cause you to make such an important decision?"

"An extremely sincere invitation."

"Um… how sincere?"

"Very very sincere. Look at my eyes," Fang Rui said.

Chang Xian felt like crying. It was no use, he was still too young, too inexperienced! He had no control over this master of playing dirty!

Chapter 1137: Happy the Dark Horse

Having accepted an exclusive interview, Fang Rui naturally wouldn't call the reporters over and just mess with them. After making his jokes, he answered the questions seriously, from personal to team, and explained his reasons for changing classes.

In the following issue of the Esports Home, Chang Xian's exclusive interview naturally made the headlines. This exclusive interview with Fang Rui took the chance to introduce Team Happy's team structure and future plans after the actual interview. This thorough analysis even caught the attention of the pro scene. After reading it, many of the pros suddenly realized that Team Happy's current class combination had many possibilities to it.

Just considering Fang Rui's shocking addition, what class was Fang Rui's most familiar partner? A Brawler! Coincidentally, there happened to be a Brawler in Happy's line up as well. Even though Fang Rui had switched classes to a Qi Master, this didn't mean his familiarity with working with a Brawler would vanish.

Then, consider Fang Rui's class switch. The Qi Master had been Ye Xiu's most reliable ally when he had built Excellent Era's dynasty. After that, the Qi Master had consistently been a core class in Excellent Era's line up. Ye Xiu was very familiar with working with Qi Masters, and Su Mucheng wouldn't be alien to it either.

In addition, Team Excellent Era's ace had been a Battle Mage. Coincidentally, Happy also had one. It wasn't hard to imagine that Excellent Era's traditional strategies would all be realized once more in Happy.

After this analysis, everyone finally realized how agreeable Fang Rui's arrangement to transfer to Happy was, as well as how the arrival of a Qi Master would unite Happy. Now, Fang Rui and his Qi Master seemed like Happy's tactical core, connecting all the pro characters.

But even if he achieved such an effect, he still wasn't the core of Happy. Who was the core? Even an idiot would know it was Ye Xiu. And what class was Ye Xiu? Unspecialized! There was very little high end research done on this class, so no one was certain what role it played in the team competition. This was the foundation on which Happy was built, but it was also the most mysterious. Though Ye Xiu and Lord Grim had appeared quite early on, the people in the pro scene were simply curious. Who would have thought to start researching an unspecialized so soon?

But now, Ye Xiu really did return, bringing his unspecialized and a team that didn't seem weak at all.

If there was anyone that still looked down on Happy before, then they had to change their minds after Fang Rui's transfer. Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui. This was a team with three All-Star level players. If this wasn't worthy of careful consideration, then what kind of team was?

Naturally, Happy's characters would be a little weaker, their facilities wouldn't be as well established, and their finances would also be a little tighter. However, no one dared underestimate them in a match. With three top players, no one would disregard them as a threat.

Grassroots?

A grassroots team with three All-Star level players? No one could continue calling them such. Were they a dark horse? Would Happy be a dark horse in this season? Just like last season's Heavenly Swords?

No… Not even Heavenly Swords was so dark. That was mostly blown out of proportion on purpose. The discussion that arose around them had garnered them more attention from the people. With more attention, there were also higher expectations. Their darkness had been from public opinion.

　

As for Happy? With three All-Stars, no one dared to say that they weren't a dark horse!

　

All the Glory-related forums, all the experts and noobs in the scene, even the pro scene, were discussing what sort of impact Happy might have on this season. Happy had suddenly become much more imposing in comparison to when they had fought in the Challenger League. All this came from Fang Rui's arrival, from Happy's daring in completing such a significant transfer.

This was an attitude, an attitude of the players and of the team.

An All-Star player held Happy in high regard and joined Happy.

Happy dared to spend this money on an All-Star character, an All-Star player.

Happy's goal was the championship title?

There weren't many people laughing now. A team with three All-Stars was a strong team in the eyes of normal players, a team that had a right to fight for the championships. Those who were rational were still considering Happy's flaws from different perspectives, but most people had gotten carried away by their excitement over Fang Rui's transfer.

Happy, champions!

There were people who really did dare yell this sort of slogan. Before now, even Seven Fields and the others, who had been loyal since they had met Ye Xiu in the tenth server, had been too embarrassed to face Happy's goal of winning the championships.

But now, any random Glory player could methodically explain how powerful Happy was to you.

With this transfer, Happy gained the spotlight once more. That was when the Glory game company and the Pro Alliance came knocking. They wanted to begin issuing Team Happy merchandise such as character models, Happy style accounts, etc.. The rights to the creation and sale of these products would given to a third party upon joining the Alliance, so they didn't have to worry about finding someone to work with. As for the profit, all teams would gain the same percentage of the revenue generated. There was little that the team actually had to do. They just had to provide their appearance and then do well in competitions, gain popularity and promote the sales of their merchandise.

In the preliminary plans of the Alliance and the game company, someone as popular as Su Mucheng wouldn't be missing. Even last season, when she had gone to the Challenger League with the rest of Excellent Era, merchandise regarding her and her Dancing Rain were still popular. Now that Dancing Rain had come to Happy with Su Mucheng, the two coming together as a package was a good thing for the merchandise company. For example, the hottest merchandise were character models with Dancing Rain's equipment as a Launcher and Su Mucheng's actual figure and appearance.

　

In comparison, Chu Yunxiu and Misty Rain were in an awkward situation. The player was a lady but the character was a guy, so they couldn't merge the two together. Thus, in the end, they could only sell Misty Rain's character model. As for the player model, those weren't as popular. Everyone preferred the epic appearance of the character model.

No one had noticed this situation at first, but by the time they did, teams like Team Misty Rain were rather depressed. With the high status gained by being in the pro scene and the mutual benefits gained along with the game company, asking to get the character's sex and appearance changed wouldn't do anything to the balance of the game. However, Misty Rain had been a guy for so long. Everyone was used to it already. If they suddenly changed his sex, then their fans probably wouldn't be able to accept that, so Misty Rain could only endure it. But this time, after acknowledging the strength of the twin sisters that Misty Rain had contracted, they decided that they would make sure to not make the same mistake and contacted the game company to change the sex of the two characters while they still had a little influence.

　

Since this change wasn't a gamechanger, the normal players didn't mind the pro scene having this special benefit. In their eyes, it was a good thing for them to align the sex of the character with the player, especially with two beautiful ladies playing two guys.

For Happy, Su Mucheng and Dancing Rain were good to go, then there was Tang Rou and Soft Mist. With her beauty and grace, she was perfect and the Alliance. The game company viewed her as a treasure, finding a talented team to create a model of Soft Mist with Tang Rou's appearance. Then, they just had to hope that Tang Rou would be able to play well and gain fame. After all, this was a competitive scene.

For Happy, they had wanted to create three different models and account cards. Su Mucheng and Tang Rou were good, now there was Ye Xiu, who was an entirely different problem.

Originally, their hopes for Ye Xiu were even higher than Su Mucheng and Tang Rou. This was a top tier expert that had hidden himself away for all these years. Now that he was willing to show himself, the Alliance and game company wanted to take this chance. But when it came to collecting the materials, the game company was close to crying.

　

Glory had been designed by them. This, naturally, included the equipment available, and Lord Grim's mix and match equipment could even cause the game company to be lost in wonder. What sort of talent did you have to have to manage to find such an ugly combination of equips! When designing the game, they naturally wouldn't make ugly equipment. The equipment would be perfect and beautiful or have some sort of uniqueness to it that left a lasting impression. However, why was Lord Grim's set so uncomfortable to look at? In that moment, the game company had a thought to cheat and modify Lord Grim's equipment design and make this mix and match a better sight to look at. But it was only a thought. This sort of change would have too big of an effect. Although the design didn't affect the stats and technically wasn't a game changer, if they made the equipment look good on Lord Grim, what would they do if the equipment looked terrible when someone else wore it?

In the end, it was Lord Grim's abnormal class choice that made his equipment diverge from the beauty of the game.

　

Experts had observed Lord Grim's current design for a long time, discussed it for a long time, but they all shook their heads in the end and admitted defeat.

The Alliance was depressed, the game company was depressed, but they refused to give up on thinking of a way to profit, coming up with another idea. They were going to make a commemorative version of One Autumn Leaf. Yes, that One Autumn Leaf, one with Ye Xiu's appearance. That would probably make up for many people's disappointment, right?

Would it really? Soon enough, someone voiced this doubt.

It wouldn't be hard to make this combination right now. Although One Autumn Leaf already belonged to Samsara, they just had to split some of the profits with Samsara and Happy. The problem was that One Autumn Leaf simply didn't have Ye Xiu's appearance, but the model was already very popular. The commemorative version would be simply adding in Ye Xiu's face.

Models were based primarily on the impressive designs of the characters. Adding in the player's appearance was just to show their love. The Excellent Era One Autumn Leaf had garnered a lot of buyers already and was just lacking Ye Xiu's face. Would adding his face really make any difference? After careful consideration, they hesitated. After all, as players of this competitive scene, their value never lay in their faces.

Why was this Ye Xiu always so troublesome!

The Pro Alliance and Glory game company felt like they were going to cry.

Chapter 1138: Keep Our Spots and Become the Champions

Happy was becoming more and more prosperous by the day. The season hadn't started yet, but the transfers, both accounts and players, were eye-catching enough already. The Pro Alliance and the Glory game company were even more worried than Happy. Let alone new rising teams in the Alliance, most teams didn't get such treatment!

No team was willing to lag behind Happy. Everyone was doing their best to find ways to improve. Team Wind Howl, who had been the backdrop behind Fang Rui's transfer, was currently having a headache about what to do with Doubtful Demon. Team Wind Howl displayed quite the benevolence towards Fang Rui's transfer. Even though they would rather offer him as a package with Doubtful Demon, in the end, they didn't make things difficult for Fang Rui if he wanted to leave alone and let it pass. But as a result, dealing with Doubtful Demon became much more complicated.

They no longer had a Thief player. Doubtful Demon clearly needed to be sold. If not, leaving him there in the team but not using him was just waiting for it to depreciate. Understanding this point, the crafty teams in the Alliance wouldn't be impatient to act. They were planning on patiently waiting. When the time came, they would go and negotiate with a lower price.

For a moment, it was as if no one wanted Doubtful Demon.

Just when the teams were patiently waiting for the right moment, the sudden news of another transfer disrupted their plan.

Team Blue Rain's Lin Feng had been transferred to Team Wind Howl for 3.2 million.

The Glory circle was completely stunned.

From the price of 3.2 million, it could be seen that Lin Feng wasn't a top-tier player, but he was a Thief player.

Team Wind Howl sent away Fang Rui and decided to abandon the Thief's dirty playing style. Suddenly, they invited Lin Feng? What were they doing? Could it be that they wanted to raise Doubtul Demon's price, so they intentionally mystified the situation?　　

Quite a few people thought of this possibility, but they also felt it was too ridiculous to believe. But not long afterwards, several skillful people analyzed the background behind this transfer.

It was true that Thieves were very suitable for playing dirty, but that didn't mean that was the only style they could play. As for Wind Howl, they may have given up on dirty play, but that didn't mean that they had given up on Thieves.

As a result, the master of playing dirty, Fang Rui, may have left, but it was ambiguous if the Thief, Doubtful Demon, would leave.

When Wind Howl saw that selling Doubtful Demon wasn't going well, they gave their answer: Doubtful Demon would not be leaving.

Because of Lin Feng.

Lin Feng was a substitute on Team Blue Rain. He had a few opportunities to appear on stage, but his position wasn't as stable as the core members. Even so, he had his own style. His Thief didn't play dirty. Team Blue Rain wasn't suited for playing dirty.　

As a result, he grabbed the attention of Team Wind Howl. The dirty Doubtful Demon was gone. A new Doubtful Demon had risen. In the press conference for Lin Feng's addition to the team, it wasn't hard to see Team Wind Howl's hopes for the new Doubtful Demon.

Up until now, Team Wind Howl's lineup for the new season seemed to have surfaced. After two summers, this team had replaced their Criminal Partners. Their Brawler and Thief were still there, but their players were different. It would be hard to say if the old criminal air around the team would appear again.　　

After Lin Feng transferred, another mid-level transfer came out.

Lu Yining, Team Misty Rain's Sharpshooter, the Best Sixth Player. The sixth player was oftentimes the main sub in the team competition. The sixth player would sometimes be the person that would turn the situation around. However, at other times, the sixth player wouldn't appear on stage because their team's main five players smoothly defeated the opponents without the need for a sixth player.

In any case, he was a skilled player. Lu Yining's transfer price of 4.6 million proved this point.

In the end, Lu Yining transferred to Team Thunderclap. It was hard not to pay attention to this team.　

Team Thunderclap had been hard-pressed money for many years. Over their many years of existence, their biggest transfer was to get back their former core character, Life Extinguisher, from Excellent Era. It truly made people speechless.

A 4.6 million transfer might not mean too much to some of the powerhouses, but for Team Thunderclap, it was no small sum of money. It looked like this team had quite the ambition this new season. Was it because of Xiao Shiqin's and Life Extinguisher's return? Had Xiao Shiqin found new growth from Excellent Era's defeat?

Misty Rain sold their Sharpshooter player entirely for the beautiful sisters Shu Keyi and Shu Kexin to take position. They obviously didn't need to find any replacements. Adjustments had been made to the beautiful sisters' characters, which had been displayed last season. It looked like the new season would be their time to shine.

Apart from that, various teams had a few transfers to fix up some minor patches. There were a few retirements and a few rookies selected for promotion. Overall, besides the huge changes from Excellent Era's disbandment, Fang Rui was the only core player to transfer. The other teams followed their usual path and firmly walked along it. Doubt? Wavering? Each year had two transfer windows. In reality, these windows were for teams to patch these up. Perhaps an issue popped up during the course of the season, but by the time the transfer window ended, the majority of teams would fix these and start walking again. They might be going at different paces, but every team was advancing forward.

Two months passed by in a flash. On 9/1, the transfer window closed. It also happened to be Monday, so the Esports Home gave a summary of this summer's transfers. There wasn't anything extremely shocking, but every team was moving towards a more steady direction. The transfer window had closed and the new season was about to begin. Each team began announcing their goals.　

The powerhouses naturally talked about winning the championships. They had the confidence and the strength to back their words. The vast majority of teams could only aim for the playoffs as their goal. They felt too embarrassed to claim that they would become the champions. As for the bottom-tier teams, their goal was to keep their spots. Even though not much attention was paid to them, they definitely had to achieve it.

As for Happy?

Keep our spot and become the champions! Ye Xiu posted on his Weibo.

The following two comments were two orderly pair of ellipses! For a moment, everyone was speechless. They had heard of the saying: "With second secured, strive for first", but keep our spot and become the champions? The two goals spoken were like the difference between heaven and earth. How could you say that?

As soon as Ye Xiu posted this Weibo, the players on the weak teams started livening up.

"Haha, then our goal will also be to keep our spots and become the champions!" Team Heavenly Sword's Lou Guanning was the team's boss, captain, and core player. Even if he didn't have any spectacular achievements, he was already destined to be a legend in the history of Glory. He suddenly changed his Team Heavenly Sword's goal.

Soon afterwards, Parade and Radiant also changed their goals for fun.

Seconded!

Seconded +1!

Keep our spots and become the champions. This slogan suddenly became the most popular slogan this new season. The powerhouses wanted to cry. Striving to become the champions was supposed to be a grandiose and magnificent goal! With all these people inappropriately making a mess out of things, their goals no longer gave off the same feeling.

In reality, the teams truly aiming to keep their spots didn't have the heart to joke around.　

Parade and Radiant shouldn't have much trouble keeping their spots, but they also didn't have much hope for making it to the playoffs. They were the kind that lacked pressure but also lacked motivation, so they could happily joke around.

But according to one person, while these later teams might just be joking, was Happy joking? Placing the two extremely disparate goals of keeping their spots and being the champions together might be a sign of the uneasiness in the depths of their heart.

"Yeah, even I can't tell if Happy is strong or weak. It's too scary." Ye Xiu unexpectedly replied to this person.

"Ah… God Ye Qiu has noticed me! He replied back. Ah ah ah ah…" This person suddenly dissolved. He was a Ye Xiu fan in the end.

"F*ck, this Weibo commenter is pathetic!"

"Commenter, stand up!"

"Commenter, what happened!"

There were a few who cared about the question of Happy's strength.

"I think we'll know the answer soon!" The Pro Alliance's official Weibo actually gave a reply. At the same time, the official Weibo released the new season's schedule for the first match. The Samsara vs Happy match was highlighted.

Team Samsara, last season's champions. As per convention, the reigning champions would be arranged to play a newly joined team to show the disparity between them. And this newly joined team would be the one invited into the Alliance. However, that was just an unwritten tradition, not an established rule. As a result, this season, the reigning champions would be facing Happy, the team that had advanced their way through the Challenger League.

Team Miracle felt like crying!

Truthfully speaking, the invited teams would usually be favored more than the Challenger League team because the teams that came from the Challenger League were usually the ones relegated from the previous seasons and then revived. Those teams weren't fresh at all. Only these invited teams would be truly new teams. However, Happy was an exception this time. They became the first truly new team that had successfully made their way through the Challenger League. Thus, it was a tragedy for the invited team this time. How could the attention towards them be higher than the attention towards Happy? In the end, the opportunity to have the first match with the reigning champions was given to Happy.

Team Miracle wasn't so delusional to think that they could make a name for themselves by beating the reigning champions. However, it had always been a form of care from the Alliance towards the new team. It looked like the love was being given to Happy though. It was as if Team Miracle was stuck in their stepmother's home. Even more unfortunate for them was that Team Miracle mainly consisted of Team Excellent Era's old players. Being reduced to a new team and being beaten by Happy were not without a relationship. How could they not be having complicated feelings towards them.

Samsara versus Happy might be the Alliance's most hyped welcoming match for a new team. How would this match turn out? From the pro circle to the player circle to the media to the masses, the discussion lasted for days up until 9/5 when the first match took place. The result: Team Samsara swept Team Happy with a clean 10 to 0.

Chapter 1139: Feeling A Little Rusty

10 to 0. A clean sweep. There was no outcome more tragic than this.

The ones who disliked Happy were overjoyed. The ones who supported Happy felt worried. The harsher ones had already started trashing Happy: keep our spot and become the champions? Haha, good luck on the first half of that.

In reality, the newly joined team getting swept by the reigning champions was a common occurrence. Last season, Team Heavenly Swords had also been hyped up, but they returned with big zero as well.

Of course, the hype towards Team Heavenly Swords and Team Happy were very different. In countless people's eyes, Happy wasn't a weak team. A team with three All Stars was enough to qualify them to compete against any team in the Alliance. However, they were swept clean just like any other new team. It was truly too surprising.

In the post-match press conference, the reporters had gathered, but the main guests hadn't arrived yet. The reporters had been quietly discussing this topic for quite a while now. This opening match usually wasn't given much attention. After all, it was a match between a strong team and a weak team. But this time, because of Happy, everyone thought it would be a match worth seeing. No one would have imagined that it would be no different than the opening matches of the past.

Finally, Happy's players arrived at the press conference under the guidance of the staff. According to the Alliance's rules, at least three players needed to attend the post-match press conference. They could come together or separately. It didn't matter. Four players from Happy came out: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Steamed Bun.

The three All-Stars had appeared. The reporters felt pleased but not satisfied. Everyone in Happy was a huge topic for discussion. The reporters hated how they couldn't have every member of Happy reply to their questions. Where's Team Blue Rain's former captain, a grandpa nearly 30, Wei Chen? Where's the beautiful rookie, Tang Rou? Where's the player who came from a champion team and changed classes, Qiao Yifan? Where's the punk who wasn't all that skilled yet dared to play the number one most difficult class, a Summoner? Where was that infamous scrap picker from the Heavenly Domain? Where was that Cleric, who held an important position but was somewhat lacking? Get over here! Only then would their cravings be satisfied!

There was no hope now though.

When the four appeared, the reporters carefully read their expressions. They wanted to see how they were affected by this disastrous loss. However, all they saw were four calm and composed faces. Even Steamed Bun, this new rookie, was unperturbed. Speaking of which, this person had only participated for a brief moment in the final Challenger League press conference, no? He had cultivated such a professional aura that fast?

In the blink of an eye, Happy's four players took their seats. The press conference began. Numerous reporters raised their hands. Ye Xiu picked a random one. The person picked asked what everyone wanted to know.

"What are your thoughts on being swept in your opening match?" The reporter asked.

"I'm very calm, but you guys don't seem to be. It's a commonly seen outcome. What's there to panic about?" Ye Xiu asked back.

Panic? We're not panicking. We're just excited about this subject, okay? The reporters silently criticized. The reporter that had been picked was stumped by this response though. The others could ridicule Ye Xiu in their minds all they wanted, but it wasn't convenient for him to say: "We were just excited because you guys got swept." He could only open his mouth and reply with an "Ah?"

"In the past, new teams being swept by the reigning champions was a common occurrence, no? Our Happy has always stayed low-profile, so of course it turned out the same as everyone else," Ye Xiu said.

"Uh… I don't think there's ever been a new team that claimed that they would become the champions, you call that... low-profile?" In the end, someone wasn't able to resist and stood up to fire back.

"You guys don't understand!" Ye Xiu said, "When Team Heavenly Swords joined the Alliance, they had originally wanted to become the champions too, but it was because of my advice that they stayed low-profile! In the end, they didn't claim they would become the champions."

This reply could be considered a mini scoop. The reporters at the scene quickly passed this news onto their colleagues on the other side. Coincidentally, the other side was the post-match press conference for Heavenly Sword's match. Team Heavenly Swords just happened to be sitting on stage too. The reporters, who received this information, were jumping with joy. Nothing noteworthy had happened and this press conference was about to end. Suddenly, everyone raised their hands in unison and waved it towards the front.

This sudden commotion frightened Lou Guanning. Did he say something wrong? For a moment, Lou Guanning didn't dare call on a reporter and immediately recalled what he had just said. But after confirming several times that he had said nothing wrong, he very carefully picked a reporter at the front.

This reporter was excited. He was talking before he even stood up: "In Team Happy's press conference, God Ye Xiu revealed that Team Heavenly Swords' goal last season had been to become the champions too. It was only because of his advice that you didn't… um… um… is this true?" This reporter was even having trouble finding the right words.

Lou Guanning suddenly started to sweat. It got exposed! Become the champions? Heavenly Swords could only say it was a joke. If they actually said it was real, wouldn't they become the jokes?

"It's just a joke. That was only a joke," Lou Guanning immediately said.　　

"Really? Then, when Heavenly Swords claimed that their goal would be to keep their spot and become the champions, could this be your ambitions showing?" The reporter asked.

"Every pro player has this kind of ambition, no?" Lou Guanning regained his composure and started speaking confidently. It was just a small leak. How could he be stumped by something like this?　

At Happy's press conference, Ye Xiu was currently talking: "Speaking of which, hasn't the Alliance always arranged the other new team to challenge the champions? Why did they suddenly arrange for us to challenge the champions? This sudden change really caught us off guard! We thought we'd be playing against those old devils, Tyranny!"

Old devils! Aren't you one too!!!

The reporters were sullen. They really wanted to fire back! However, what they wanted to say wasn't suitable for a place like a press conference! For the first time, the reporters felt like they were the disadvantaged group and could only watch as Ye Xiu rambled on freely. They really wanted to interrupt, but it wouldn't be good to, so they could only stifle their frustration.

"So you're saying it's the Alliance's arrangements that led to Happy not performing ideally this round?" The reporters could only word it in this way.

"I never said that." Ye Xiu continued to evade the question.

"Then, what are your thoughts on your own individual performance this match?" A reporter asked.

In the previous match, Ye Xiu first came out in the group arena as their third player. He went up against Samsara's third player, Zhou Zekai, but lost. Afterwards, in the team competition, Samsara attacked even more ferociously. Happy wasn't able to hang on for very long. If you only took a look at Ye Xiu's performance, it wasn't too bad. He didn't make any terrible mistakes, but there also weren't any particularly bright spots either.

"Mm, it's been too long since I've played a pro match. I was feeling a bit rusty," Ye Xiu replied.

This… what were they supposed to say! It was true that not competing in high-level league would have an impact on his condition, but he seemed quite fierce when he fought against Excellent Era! Was that a good reason?　

The reporters were doubtful. Their gazes shifted to Su Mucheng. Just when they were about to ask, she took the initiative to speak up: "It's been too long since I've played a pro match. I was feeling a bit rusty."

Su Mucheng had faced Samsara's vice-captain, Jiang Botao, but lost.

A copy and paste! The reporters fumed. But the problem was that Su Mucheng had been relegated along with Excellent Era for a year. She hadn't played in a high-level league either. After serious consideration, Happy's reasoning… held up?

Their gazes shifted again.

"I haven't played a Qi Master in a long time. I was feeling a bit rusty," Fang Rui said.　　

Okay, even though it was another copy paste answer, it was definitely a legitimate reason. He transferred in the last third of June and switched to a Qi Master. It had only been a month since then. It was normal for him to not do too well in his first match with a new class. Fang Rui was the second player for the group arena. Samsara's Sun Xiang had been the first to come out. After Sun Xiang beat Happy's Tang Rou, he nearly completed a 1v2 and almost beat Fang Rui too. In the end, even though Fang Rui won, it didn't take long for him to lose the second round. He practically left two players for Ye Xiu, and one of those was Zhou Zekai.

"Good joke. On the other hand, look at how sincere I am," Fang Rui said to Ye Xiu after leaving the stage, and was met with a kick.

The reporters received three "I was feeling a bit rusty." Afterwards, they looked towards Happy's fourth player, Steamed Bun. He came out in the individual competition, but lost to Samsara's All-Star Grappler, Lu Boyuan. Steamed Bun had given quite a few frights to the enemy. For a new player, this loss could be considered as an honorable one. He could completely feel satisfied with his performance today.

However, Steamed Bun looked at everyone and then immediately copied the previous three's responses: "I've never played in a pro match before. I was feeling a bit rusty."

Fuck! What was that supposed to mean? Are you saying that if you weren't feeling rusty, you would have beaten Lu Boyuan? The others might have been away from the pro scene for too long or switched classes, so "feeling rusty" was possible, but you're a genuine rookie. What do you mean "rusty"? You can't be rusty in the first place!

Fuck! The reporters could only restrain their desire to curse at them. What an uncomfortable feeling! A few people had even left the venue with their hands against their hips. Those guys had probably left out of anger!

"What are your thoughts on Happy's future this season?" A reporter was determined to keep asking questions.

"Keep our spot and become the champions," Ye Xiu said earnestly.　

"Become the champions," Su Mucheng said.

"What else did I come here for?" Fang Rui said.

"What happened to keeping our spot? We don't need it anymore?" Steamed Bun saw that his two seniors had gotten rid of the "keep our spot" part and felt discontent.

"Becoming the champions implies that we'll have kept our spot," Fang Rui lectured Steamed Bun.

"Oh, that makes sense!" Steamed Bun sighed.　　

They couldn't… take it any longer. The reporters felt defeated. They had at least found two things from this interview though. This sweep hadn't damaged Happy's morale. What's more, Fang Rui seemed to be meshing together well with Happy! At least personality wise.

Chapter 1140: First Round

Happy may have been swept by Samsara, but they won versus the press conference reporters. After routing the reporters, the four left the stage in high spirits. When they left through the passageway for the players, they just happened to bump into Samsara, who would be participating in the next part of the press conference.

Zhou Zekai, Jiang Botao, Sun Xiang.

For the opening round and a good beginning, Samsara hadn't held back and had sent out their three All-Stars. Even though Sun Xiang's year at Excellent Era had been a devastating failure, he was still young and people still looked highly upon his future. From this match, it could be seen that Sun Xiang was meshing well with Samsara. There was no point talking about the individual competition, but in the team competition, he had done a great job assuming the responsibilities of an attacker. One Autumn Leaf in the front. Cloud Piercer in the back. The duo tore apart Happy's formation as if everyone in Happy was a dead branch. It was easy to foresee that this wouldn't be the only time the duo would go on a rampage. This duo would certainly become a nightmare in the entire Alliance for a long time. Many reporters were already describing them in this way.

"Senior!" After bumping into Happy in the passageway, Samsara's Jiang Botao gave a polite greeting to Ye Xiu. The winners would often console the losers. It seemed like Jiang Botao wanted to do the same.　　

"Mm, I'm glad to see how outstanding the younger generation is!" Ye Xiu sighed.

Sun Xiang rolled his eyes. Because of this person, he had been put into a difficult situation. However, he had gained a lot of experience from these failures. But if it had to be said that he felt gratitude for Ye Xiu beating him, Sun Xiang wasn't so sweet. He still wanted to ruthlessly crush him. In today's match, he had gone all out, and Samsara had achieved a perfect victory. However, in his heart, he didn't feel like he had beaten Ye Xiu. Was it because it wasn't a direct confrontation? Sun Xiang was somewhat puzzled.

Before anyone in Samsara could reply, Fang Rui nodded his head: "Yes, I'm glad too."

Zhou Zekai stared at Fang Rui but didn't say anything.　

"Haha, aren't you and Little Zhou both from the same generation?" Jiang Botao laughed.

"Really? Who told him to always be so quiet. I forgot." Fang Rui said.

"Pro players should speak with their play!" Jiang Botao said.

"Okay, I'll give a good talk with you guys next time." Fang Rui said.

"See you next time."

"See you next time."

The two sides departed after a brief exchange. Samsara's press conference went more like how an opening round press conference should go. Most of the discussion was focused on their goals for the new season. Their new player Sun Xiang was given a lot of attention and was asked about his thoughts on Samsara and how he was fitting in with the team.

The four passed through the player passageway and returned to the guest team's lounge at Samsara's stadium. They didn't take a moment to sit down and take a break. They pushed open the door and called out to the others inside: "Let's go!"

Happy left Samsara's stadium and returned to City H with their zero points. Saying that they didn't care at all about their zero points obviously wasn't possible. On the plane, Chen Guo was just sitting and she wasn't feeling comfortable. She looked at Su Mucheng, who was seated next to her, and wanted to chat, but then she saw that Su Mucheng was looking at the tablet in Ye Xiu's hands.

"What's he watching?" Chen Guo asked curiously.

"The VOD for the match that just ended." Su Mucheng said.

"Oh…" Chen Guo didn't say anything more.

Happy wasn't the only one playing their first match. Happy was already on their way back home; the matches going on in the other stadiums had already ended as well.

Team Miracle, the other new team alongside Team Happy, hadn't received the champion sweep. Instead, they had been swept by Team Tyranny. Truthfully speaking, Team Miracle wasn't that bad. They had joined when Team Excellent Era disbanded. Seizing this opportunity, they had fished up quite a few things including three of Team Excellent Era's players. In terms of their players, Team Miracle was actually superior to last season's Team Heavenly Swords. Unfortunately, apart from some leftovers from Team Excellent Era, Team Miracle didn't bring anything fresh to the Alliance, so the attention received was less than that of last year's Team Heavenly Swords.

Speaking of Team Heavenly Swords, their announcement that Sun Zheping would be returning and joining their team had led to a heated discussion. After all, the last time they checked, Sun Zheping had been with Happy in the Challenger League. Everyone thought that he would return along with Happy. Who would have thought that he would turn around and run to Team Heavenly Swords?

For Heavenly Sword's opening match, they happened to be matched with Hundred Blossoms.

First, it was Zhang Jiale. Then, it was Sun Zheping. Hundred Blossom's two kings had retired then returned, but neither of them chose to go back to their team.

When Zhang Jiale returned, the fans cried and cursed, unable to understand and accept it. As for Sun Zheping? When he had fought with Happy in the Challenger League, people had foreseen this development. However, Sun Zheping had been away from the scene for a long time now. The sentiment towards him had lessened drastically. What's more, when he returned, he had been in the Challenger League, so everyone felt like he wasn't being too serious about it and was just having some fun. On the other hand, Zhang Jiale had returned and joined Tyranny. It was obvious that he had gone over because of their fame. In comparison, Sun Zheping's return truly didn't set off any big waves. There was still some noise though. The reporters also knew that this could be considered a noteworthy topic. As a result, in the press conference, someone tossed out this question.

Sun Zheping's return didn't unfold as magnificently as Zhang Jiale's, but Sun Zheping himself was a lot fiercer than Zhang Jiale. When he was asked "Why did you choose Heavenly Swords and not Hundred Blossoms," his reply was just three words: I wanted to.

Everything there was to know about Sun Zheping's situation had pretty much been uncovered when he had been with Happy. Everyone already knew that his hand injury wasn't fully healed. He could play, but he couldn't play for long. He was incapable of becoming a pro team's main force.

Thus, many smart people had already guessed why Sun Zheping chose to go to Heavenly Swords.

He clearly had an appropriate reason that everyone could understand, but instead, he gave this three-word reply.

"I wanted to" indicated that he wasn't going to give an explanation.

This was just how Sun Zheping was. His hand injury meant that he could never become a true pro player again, but he himself hadn't changed.

In the match between Hundred Blossoms and Heavenly Swords, Hundred Blossoms won 8 to 2. Heavenly Swords had won two points in the individual competition, one of which had been gotten by Sun Zheping. Many people felt it was regrettable. It had been many years since he had left the pro scene, yet even with an injury, he could still perform to such a level. If he hadn't gotten his injury, what status would Sun Zheping have in the current pro scene?

Unfortunately, there were no ifs in this world....

Apart from that, the opening round had seven other matches. There weren't too many particularly noteworthy confrontations. This was also how the Pro Alliance always arranged the league schedule. It was the opening round! Satisfying the fans' curiosity towards the teams' adjustments during the summer was enough. They didn't need to set up anything special.

Seven matches.

Team Blue Rain beat Team Bright Green 9 to 1.

Team Tiny Herb swept Team Lightly 10 to 1.

Team Wind Howl beat Team Conquering Clouds 9 to 1.

Team Misty Rain beat Team Seaside 8 to 2.

Team Void barely beat Team 301 6 to 4.

Team Thunderclap beat Team Parade 7 to 3.

Team Royal Style beat Team Radiant 7 to 3.

There were no surprises. The teams that should have won won. The teams that should have lost lost. Although, in regards to the competitive format, with everyone vying for points, there wasn't technically a win or lose. However, out of habit, everyone still considered the team with more points as the winner and the other team as the loser for every match.

From this first round, the placings were currently Tyranny, Samsara, and Tiny Herb tied for first with 10 points. Wind Howl and Blue Rain tied for fourth with 9 points. Misty Rain at sixth with 8 points. Royal Style and Thunderclap tied for seventh with 7 points… in last were obviously the three teams that hadn't won a single point: Happy, Miracle, and Lightly.

Team Lightly was a mid-tier team in the Alliance, neither good nor bad and rather invisible. (Author's Note: Yes, very invisible. It wasn't until I officially started writing about the Pro League did I realize that there was still 1 team missing out of 20. And thus, Team Lightly was born!) If they matched against a powerhouse, losing badly was nothing surprising.　

As for Happy and Miracle, the Alliance's tradition continued. Who had these two face against the finalists last season?

These three teams all had 0 points, but Happy was thrown to the bottom. Unfortunately, placings were done by points and then by reverse alphabetical order. Happy started with the letter H, which came before Miracle's M and Lightly's L*.

Season ten's opening round ended with these results. It was hard to predict how this season would go based on these results though. It was just that Happy, the team that had been hyped, was swept by Samsara, so Happy was once again an unfathomable mystery.

Was Happy a good team or a bad team?　　

The media was discussing this question. The players were discussing this question. But all of them were simply outsiders in the scene. The ones with the headache were the Alliance's teams. They were the ones who needed to rack their brains to figure out how they should be looking at Happy. 　

Each team found something from the VOD of Happy versus Samsara. This information was too precious. In general, there were practically no recordings of Happy against high-skill level. Only last year's match versus Happy could be considered as one.

As soon as they started studying Happy, all of the teams realized that there were many things needed to be studied.

Not only did Happy have a bunch of rookies, even among the three old veterans, they were only sort of familiar with Su Mucheng. The other two had switched classes! Since they had started again from scratch, it meant that the teams needed to start up their research on them from scratch too. It was a bit better for Fang Rui. There were footsteps to follow. However, Ye xiu made them feel nauseated.

Unspecialized? Everyone knew what an unspecialized was. They knew the theory behind one and could train one too. But the problem was that they didn't have a Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. An unspecialized without the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was completely different from an unspecialized with one. They had no way of testing an unspecialized themselves nor could they imitate one. Their only source of information was from match VODs. There were really only two matches significant enough to watch though, so they could only watch these over and over again.

Ye Xiu was clearly someone that everyone was incomparably familiar with, but he was a completely mystery right now. This sort of feeling didn't feel good at all.

You bastard! You've already retired, so why'd you have to return? If you're going to return, why'd you switch classes? If you're going to switch classes, why'd you have to choose an unspecialized? If you're going to choose an unspecialized, why'd you have to have an exclusive weapon?

Chapter 1141: Which Match to Watch?

In the eyes of the pro teams, Happy was a troublesome existence. In the past, when had they ever needed to spend so much effort studying a new Alliance team? Those teams on the border of relegations were no different than cheerleader teams in the eyes of the powerhouses. However, for Happy, they felt uneasy not taking them seriously. Fortunately, matches were played one by one. Over the entire season, each team would at most bump into Happy twice. The teams scheduled far from Happy weren't in a rush. On the other hand, the teams scheduled closer to Happy were rather worried such as Team Hundred Blossoms, who would be playing Happy next.

Team Hundred Blossoms had made it to the playoffs last season and even gave quite the trouble to Team Tyranny. After waving goodbye to Blood and Blossoms, their team became better and better. Yu Feng, the new generation's number one Berserker stood firm in Team Hundred Blossoms. His strength had erased Sun Zheping's influence to some extent. Along with the passing of time, Team Hundred Blossoms had been rather indifferent about encountering Sun Zheping, at least, they hadn't been as nervous as facing Happy.

Because Hundred Blossoms was a team on the fringe of the playoff level, it was very possible that a slight slip would lead to their playoff spot being taken, so in their view, Happy was an especially worrisome opponent. The difference in points this round might determine which of the two teams would be making into the playoffs.

However, no matter how diligent they might be, there were only two real matches of Happy to look at. In their match against Excellent Era, Happy had displayed closely interlinked and masterful strategic planning, but against Samsara, before Happy could even get their tactics going, Samsara had scattered them.

"Samsara is even stronger this season!" Team Hundred Blossom's Cleric, Mo Chuchen, said.

But soon afterwards, under the gazes of everyone else in the team, Mo Chuchen shifted topics in a fluster: "Focus on Happy, focus on Happy."　　

Yes, he had mistaken what was important here. But the problem was that there really wasn't much to see from Happy this match. Happy hadn't been able to display any of their tactics before collapsing.

In the post-match press conference, Happy threw the word "rustiness" left and right, leading to a complete collapse of the reporters. But from Team Hundred Blossom's careful analysis, they felt like this rustiness might really be the truth?

Samsara had won two consecutive championships. Their strength didn't need to be questioned. Their team was an aggressive team, especially after the addition of Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf. With such strong attackers, their tempo only quickened. As a result, when Happy ran into Samsara, from their performance in the team competition, they indeed had been overwhelmed by Samsara's fast pace. Happy's decisions were always a half beat too slow. Even though they tried hard to make adjustments to their tactical rhythm, by the time they finished adjusting, Samsara was already on the next beat.

After all, Samsara was different than Excellent Era. Excellent Era was a team that Ye Xiu understood all too well. When fighting against Excellent Era, his tactics were clearly targeted towards them. Excellent Era had also been crushing noobs in the Challenger League for an entire year, so they had somewhat fallen from the pace of the pro scene. How could they compare to the reigning champions?

Happy needed to adapt to the pace of the pro matches. For Hundred Blossoms, this was undoubtedly good news. Thus, the general direction of this upcoming match was more or less confirmed now.

Fight fast!

Hundred Blossom's players reached a consensus. As for the specifics, each team had their own class compositions and styles. For the following week, they would be undergoing targeted practice for utilizing this playstyle. This was the pro scene. This was a pro match. How each battle played out depended on the opponents.

The week passed quickly. The second round of the league had begun.

In this round, there were two important matches. The first was between Team Happy and Team Hundred Blossoms. Everyone had been discussing how strong Happy was exactly over the course of the week.

The other match was between Team Thunderclap and Team Void. After Xiao Shiqin returned to Thunderclap, there had been a few more adjustments made during the summer transfer window, revealing the team's newfound ambition. As for Void, their dual Ghostblades were legendary, but this duo always gave people a feeling that these two weren't able to support the general picture. However, people saw room for growth from Void, not from transfers but from the interior.

Last season, Blue Rain's rookie Lu Hanwen shined. In his first year in the Alliance, he had been chosen as an All-Star. Another star was rising. In the end, the Best Rookie went unsurprisingly to Lu Hanwen. However, was this decision truly without controversy? For Team Void's fans, that was absolutely not the case.

Last season, a formidable rookie had appeared in their team too. An Exorcist: Ge Caijie.

Ge Caijie was 19 this year. No matter how it was looked at, he was at an age brimming with youth. However, placed among pro players in an competitive scene getting younger and younger, compared to the 15 year old Lu Hanwen, the 19 year old Ge Caijie was immediately labelled with traits such as mature and staid, words that didn't suit youths.

Ge Caijie was indeed a serious person with an air of a great general. Alongside Glory's famous Ghostblade duo, he displayed a terror never before seen in a rookie. His performance was always consistent. Even though the Ghostblade duo was still the core of Team Void, the air of a leading role appeared around him. This wasn't him trying to overtake his seniors. It was simply his playstyle. He was someone with the potential to become the core of a team, a person that could carry the team's banner.

Everyone had always been waiting for a good helper to the Ghostblade duo, but right now, a youth, who sometimes made the Ghostblade duo change from leads to support, had appeared. The two seniors seemed to have no disagreements towards him. And whenever team Void's Ge Caijie performed spectacularly, they always obtained good results.

For this type of player, even if he didn't grow to become the core of a team, he would still be a great general in a team. It was just a pity that his seriousness made him different than Lu Hanwen, who was brimming with energy and passion. The attention towards him was far less. Team Void had always been lamenting at this injustice. In the selection for Best Rookie, Lu Hanwen snatched away the majority of the votes, leaving a huge gap between the second place Ge Caijie.

This didn't affect Ge Caijie though. Another summer had passed and he became even more mature. Last season, he had been the new rookie of the team and now he had already come a player that Team Void couldn't lack. The opening round of the league further proved this point.

In the opening round, Team Void fought against Team 301 in a bitter battle. In this round, Ge Caijie had been crucial to the points won by Team Void. He had won a point in the individual competition. In the team copetition, Team 301 took the initiative, but he stood firm and led the team for a counterattack, resulting in a huge victory..　　

In the post-match press conference, Team 301's captain, Yang Cong, praised Ge Caijie. He even said that Ge Caijie reminded him of Wang Jiexi despite their playstyles being entirely different. Afterwards, Team 301's All-Star Grappler Li Yihui, who had once been a part of Team Tiny Herb but had been traded for Team 301's Xu Bin, also expressed his approval towards his captain's praise for Ge Caijie.

Team Thunderclap versus Team Void was the match chosen to be broadcast. Even though everyone's curiosity towards Happy hadn't been erased, the broadcast could only choose a single match. They couldn't only broadcast Happy's matches this season, no?

On 9/12, the second round of the Glory Professional League's tenth season started. The viewers tuning into watch saw Team Void's stadium as scheduled. But the commentator Pan Lin seemed to be even more uneasy than anyone else.

"Hello friends, this is the second round of the Glory Professional League's tenth season, Thunderclap versus Void. The players on both sides have entered the stadium. First up will be the individual competition, of course. And at the same time, there's another important match between Hundred Blossoms and Happy, which is taking place in City H. I'm sure everyone knows that after Excellent Era was defeated in the Challenger League last season, their boss Tao Xuan sold practically all of Excellent Era's assets. Many people probably thought that Excellent Era's competitive stadium was a part of these assets, but in reality, Excellent Era's stadium used to be called Xiaoshan Gymnasium, a public gymnasium in City H. When the Glory Professional League was established, the competition soon needed this type of venue, so Excellent Era rented it for long-term use. Later on, the name was changed to the Excellent Era Stadium. The lease was suspended ahead of time and the stadium has returned to the original Xiaoshan Gymnasium. Right now, Happy is temporarily leasing it for their stadium. In truth, this isn't surprising! This is the only venue in City H with the conditions to display Glory's projection technology!"

"Ahem!" A cough interrupted Pan Lin's introduction. After a pause, Pan Lin realized that he was currently commentating the match between Thunderclap and Void, but after only a short introduction, he had suddenly shifted focus to Happy. The director had told him to give updates on the situation between Happy and Hundred Blossoms. It would be enough to just say a few words when a result came out. He wasn't supposed to go too far though!

"Let's get back to the scene." Pan Lin immediately pulled the subject back from Xiaoshan Gymnasium. His old partner Li Yibo gave a loud laugh: "It looks like our Little Pan has quite the interest in the match between Hundred Blossom and Happy!"

"Uh, we'll be giving updates on that match from time to time." Pan Lin said.

"Okay, the match between Thunderclap and Void will be starting soon. First up is the individual competition. The first two players to come up will be… Thunderclap's Dai Yanqi and Void's Li Xun!" Pan Lin started focusing on the present match.

And at the same time, standing inside the venue renamed to "Xiaoshan Gymnasium", Ye Xiu let out a deep sigh.

Even though the name had changed, the venue itself hadn't. The only addition to it was equipment for the projection technology.

I'm back. A year and eight months to stand back here. My name has changed. My character has changed. But my will to compete will never change.

"I'll be going." Ye Xiu called out to his teammates and stepped towards the stage.

"Dai Yanqi has open fired! For now, Li Xun is unable to approach and is moving around. A beautiful Air Jump! He jumped backwards in midair to dodge the magic coming at him! Ah! Happy sent out Ye Xiu as their first player!!"

The viewers tuning into the match were listening to Pan Lin commentating the intense battle between Elemenalist and Assassin, when a piece of news about Happy suddenly popped up out of nowhere.

Chapter 1142: A Nervous Rookie

Ye Xiu was the first one to walk onto the stage for Happy. Pan Lin was not the only one who was shocked. Everyone in the stadium, including the players from Team Hundred Blossoms, were astonished.

According to the usual practices, the ace player would appear in the group arena to fight for the two points. The ace player rarely appeared in the individual competition. With Happy's arrangements, was Happy giving up on the group arena, targeting the three points in the individual competition?

There was no need to dwell on this thought. The list of names for the matches were set before the game. Zeng Xinran from Team Hundred Blossoms went on stage for this away-game.

Who was Zeng Xinran?

Before this match, no one knew.

He was a rookie promoted from the Hundred Blossom's training camp this season. When his name was submitted to the league in the new season's players list, it could be considered as his first public appearance in the circle. After that, he appeared Esport Home's September 1st edition, introducing the team rosters for the Alliance's twenty teams. All officially registered appeared in this list. Important transfers would have short introductions, but Zeng Xinran only had his name listed and popped up on Hundred Blossom's team roster just like this. No press conference had been convened for him, so no reporters thought about interviewing him.

He was not a rookie who had gained the adoration of millions, but the team gave him a chance because of his skill. He became an official player and waited for the chance to appear on stage. Then, he would use his play to earn a name for himself in the league.

Hundred Blossom didn't send him up for the opening match, so he sat idly on the bench. However, he wasn't annoyed. Unless he was one of those so-called heavenly talents, this was something almost all rookies had to experience, even more so in Team Hundred Blossoms. They had watched as player came out of their training camp, sign a contract with them, and sit on the bench. He found opportunities here and there. He gradually became a part of the main roster, then the core of the team, then a God in the Alliance.

Tang Hao!

For every rookie sitting on the benches, there was nothing more encouraging than Tang Hao's story.

Zeng Xinran inherited Delillo, the Brawler account Tang Hao left behind when he left Hundred Blossoms. He promised himself that he would be like Tang Hao and conquer the world, starting from the bench. He was able to get a chance to fight in their second round. For someone who knew Tang Hao's story very well, he knew that he had gained an opportunity even earlier than Tang Hao. This fact raised his spirits.

He was moved and excited and didn't even sleep well last night. He could finally step onto the stage. Unfortunately, his opponent just had to be Ye Xiu.

Who didn't know of Ye Xiu's accomplishments in the early days? New rookies didn't feel too pressured facing him though. This was because that era of glory was too far in the past. Only players who had played Glory for over ten years had the chance to personally witness that era. Zeng Xinyan obviously hadn't played Glory for that long. By the time he started playing Glory and entered Hundred Blossoms' training camp, Ye Xiu had already been labelled as outdated. Not long afterwards, he retired. When he returned, Excellent Era disbanded. Zeng Xinran indeed admired the amount of commotion this God could make, but he only started to learn about Ye Xiu's skill when his team was preparing to fight Happy. Like everyone else, he only knew about the unspecialized and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in theory, but not much in actual practice.

Team Hundred Blossoms had been distressed for this very reason. However, Zeng Xinran was relatively at ease because he didn't think he would have the opportunity to fight Ye Xiu. He would be appearing in the individual competition, so the team competition was irrelevant. He didn't expect to meet Happy's core and God in the individual competition.

However, what he didn't think would happen happened. He was a rookie who would playing in his first competitive match in his professional career. Unfortunately, he just had to face a God who had fought hundreds of battles.

The thunderous applause given to Ye Xiu in the stadium caused half of Zeng Xinran's body to go numb. He realized that competition wasn't as simple as he had imagined. Why did he feel so suffocated in such a big stadium? Happy was a new team that had only recently entered the league, yet they already had so many fans. So noisy…...

Zeng Xinran entered the player booth. The player booth was completely cut-off from the outside world. However, his brain was still in a mess. The amount of noise and the feeling of suffocation lingered in his mind, and he was unable to wipe it away.

One minute had passed. Ye Xiu pressed ready after logging on with Lord Grim and joining the arena room. However, there was no sign of activity from Zeng Xinran.

What happened? The crowd became restless, so the referee immediately took action to see what was up with Zeng Xinran. Then, he saw a player whose body was completely rigid and tense.

It was pressure.

The referee was experienced and this wasn't the first time he had encountered such a situation. He only needed to glance at the player to tell that he was too nervous.

"Are you ready?" The referee sighed and knew the player was definitely not prepared, but the match couldn't give him liimitless time to prepare. He could only confirm with this method: if he was ready, then the match would start at once, if not, then he would forfeit.

Zeng Xinran obviously knew the rules, so he immediately nodded. Under the guidance of the referee, he logged on, entered the room with his character, and pressed ready…...

They soon reached the end of the countdown. Both Lord Grim and Delillo loaded into the map.

Delillo was the character Tang Hao had previously used. When he had been present, Hundred Blossoms made an effort to upgrade it. But after his departure, Hundred Blossom went back to their old Berserker and Spitfire combo. Delillo was no longer an account the club focused on. After the Level 75 update, Delillo naturally wasn't a priority. Now that the account had been handed down to a rookie, the majority of the equipment was still as Tang Hao had left it. Upgrades in the equipment were made through upgraded Level 75 Orange equipment instead of upgraded Level 75 Silver equipment.

In comparison, Happy's character weakness wasn't so obvious before Delillo. Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestation Umbrella was at Level 70. Even though he didn't have any other Silver equipment, a full set of Level 75 Orange equipment was enough to compare with Silver equipment at Level 70. As for character-player suitability, in reality, only the powerhouses had the resources to be so picky.

The moment Ye Xiu entered the room, he had Lord Grim sprint ahead. As for Zeng Xinran, he was still in a daze. He didn't do anything and was still trying to sort out his emotions.

The audience didn't know about Zeng Xinran's situation. All they saw was that the old general was charging forward impatiently, while the rookie calmy stood his ground. Had those two switched accounts?

The audience didn't know about Zeng Xinran's situation, neither did Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu didn't have any way to learn about such a new rookie, so he could only learn as the match progressed.

However, when Lord Grim reached the center of the map, he didn't see his opponent.

Is he moving strategically?

For any pro player, this observation was instinctive. Ye Xiu immediately looked over the terrain. This was a home game for Happy, so they picked the map themselves. Even if he closed his eyes, he wouldn't walk the wrong way on this map. He immediately took note of any locations that were possible for a sneak attack, but he couldn't sense any movement from the opponent.

Is he playing dirty?

Ye Xiu wondered. The Brawler was a class that could play dirty, so Ye Xiu took caution and carefully looked around. He had Lord Grim move ahead while deliberately making mistakes. No response.

Zeng Xinran from Hundred Blossom was still trying to regain his composure at the spawn point, so he hadn't moved. Even if the audience watched from a bird's eye view, none of them knew what was happening. Those who had watched Happy's matches in the Challenger League sent glaces towards Wei Chen at Happy's bench. Playing dirty by standing at the spawn point was similar to this old player! Happy had once used this tactic against their opponents. Was this retribution for Happy?

If this was the Challenger League, the audience might have been a bit excited, but this was different! This was an official league match, as well as a home game for Happy. Even though their popularity couldn't be compared with the early years of Excellent Era, it was definitely enough for the bottom-tier and mid-tier teams be jealous of! Having a large audience meant that lot of people bought tickets. This was probably where teams earned most of their day to day income from.

At this home game, Happy's fans started to feel a little worried. They were afraid of the strange moves this foreign rookie from Hundred Blossoms would make.

The atmosphere in the stadium started to grow heavy. Everyone watched Lord Grim gradually get closer to Delillo while the latter was calm as always.

At last, the two characters appeared in each other's view. Ye Xiu saw Delillo, and Zeng Xinran saw Lord Grim.

After that, Delillo charged forward!

He sprinted straight without showing any signs of turning. There was no touch of tactics as he advanced straight ahead as if this was the deciding point.

He must be scheming something!

The audience thought to themselves. If this were really the deciding point in the match, what was he doing earlier? Was he just standing there to nurture his strength while exhausting the enemy? Franking speaking, that wasn't possible in Glory. Many players would do random ineffective actions before they encountered their opponent as warm up. There must be some sort of scheme within all this for Zeng Xinran to just wait there doing nothing. It was just like what Wei Chen had done at Happy…...

The audience didn't have time to think any further because the two had started fighting already. Hundred Blossoms' Zeng Xinran, a schemer in everyone's minds, was sent flying backgrounds in the first exchange.

The audience was stunned, and Ye Xiu was also a bit astonished. He had been 120% careful, and had numerous variations and follow-ups prepared after Falling Flower Palm, but it turned out that Falling Flower Palm was all it took to send him flying away?

As for his follow-up…...

Lord Grim missed when he struck with his spear. This was a rare mistake for veterans like Ye Xiu. It was simply because that palm hitting was too surprising.

The moment Delillo was about to reach the ground after being blown away, his body twitched and he lay flat on the ground.

What is he doing?

Ye Xiu was dumbstruck. To even fail to Quick Recover, was he... really a pro player?

Even Ye Xiu was slightly dazed. He was playing in a pro match, right? He wasn't in the Arena or the Challenger League, torturing scrubs, right?

Is it a trap? Ye Xiu didn't move forward and instead used long-ranged skills. After a chain of ferocious attacks, his heart finally steadied.

It was impossible for this to be a trap. If it was, then this was way overboard. The player before him was simply playing really bad for some reason. Lord Grim rushed forward without any hesitation. He dispatched his opponent cleanly and won.

The audience was dumbstruck. They even forgot to applause and cheer for their team. What happened? This victory was too simple. Was Hundred Blossoms deliberately playing badly?

Chapter 1143: An Ordinary Veteran

Zeng Xinran wasn't the first to rookie to lose a battle because of nerves, nor would he be the last. But no rookie would ever want their very first battle to have such an embarrassing ending.

This was the very first point obtained by Happy in the pro league, a memorable point won by Ye Xiu. The story stopped there, though, since there was nothing memorable about the process of winning the point. This wasn't a match to be proud of.

Somehow, Happy won the point just like that. Aside from the judge, who had seen with his own eyes how nervous Zeng Xinran was, the only others who could really understand what had happened were his Hundred Blossom teammates.

Others didn't know anything about Zeng Xinran, but his teammates understood his skill very well. After all, he was sent out for this official match because he had the skill necessary to possibly achieve a win. But in the end, his performance didn't suit his actual abilities at all. The Hundred Blossoms players thought, and immediately knew that he had been too nervous.

It was common to be nervous, but strange to be nervous to this extent. But they couldn't put more pressure on Zeng Xinran after this. When he came off stage, his teammates spoke words of comfort and encouragement to him, until the judge called for the second individual competitor to go onstage.

Zhang Wei.

An ordinary name that couldn't get any more ordinary, just like his professional career.

Zhang Wei was a veteran player. After debuting in Season 3, he had played continuously for Team Hundred Blossoms. He wasn't particularly talented, nor did he show any sort of breakthrough growth. Through the years, he was just another ordinary member of Hundred Blossoms.

He had seen Blood and Blossoms wreak havoc upon the Alliance. He had seen Sun Zheping's tragic injury and untimely retirement. He had seen Zhang Jiale alone but still persevering in the fight. He had seen Tang Hao's rapid rise from a benchwarmer to a God at the peak of the Alliance. All of this took place right beside him, and he experienced it all, yet hadn't changed afterwards. In the end, he was just a very ordinary member of Hundred Blossoms. There were actually many pro players like this. They weren't very eye-catching, and they wouldn't often come up in the media or in conversations between ordinary gamers. However, they were still a very important component of the Alliance. It was just like how in real life, the majority of people were just ordinary people. Pro players were an extraordinary subset of Glory players, and Zhang Wei and the others were the most ordinary of this subset.

The second player in the individual competition for Hundred Blossoms' away match at Happy was this ordinary player, Zhang Wei.

Zhang Wei went onstage, entered the player booth, swiped his account card, logged into the game, and joined the match room. He had repeated this process many times over the years and so didn't need any sort of preparation. To him, it was as simple as eating a meal. Soon after entering the room, he saw his opponent enter: Steamed Bun Invasion.

Oh, it's that confusing player.

Zhang Wei thought back to the research they had done prior to this match. This player named Bao Rongxing had earned that evaluation. This guy! He had good technical skill for sure, but his performance in matches was sometimes good and sometimes bad. If that were his only problem, they could just treat him as a player whose condition was unstable. But this guy… Sometimes his good would become bad, and sometimes his bad would miraculously produce good. His play followed no rules, and so it was impossible to devise any tactics to counter him. In the end, the plan was just four words: play it by ear.

And now the task of playing by ear had fallen upon Zhang Wei's head.

Countdown. Loading match.

Zhang Wei's character was a Witch called Endless Forest. Although he was an ordinary player, he had played in Hundred Blossoms for many years now, and his position was relatively stable, so his character Endless Forest was fairly good. Of course, it couldn't compare to Vaccaria. Zhang Wei had debuted the same year as Wang Jiexi and played the same class, but his name was never mentioned with Wang Jiexi's, because in people's eyes there was nothing to compare.

Zhang Wei used this decent Witch, Endless Forest. The strategy of this match was to play by ear, so Zhang Wei's original plan was to open with strategic change of position. But the map that Happy had chosen was simple and flat. With no cover, there was no way to surprise the opponent, so he had no choice but to directly charge forward.

Steamed Bun didn't hesitate at all. As soon as the match started, he brazenly charged out, at the same time sending a message: "Let's decide the winner!"

"Alright." Upon seeing the opponent's message, Zhang Wei sent a reply.

Soon enough, without dodging, or rather with nowhere to dodge, the two players met at the center of the map.

Both Brawler and Witch were close to mid-range fighters, but the Witch's range of control was a bit larger. As a Mage, a Witch absolutely had to have some sort of AoE.

Zhang Wei's actions were extremely simple. Endless Forest tossed a Lava Flask, which was the most common opening move for Witches in PvP. Throw a Lava Flask, it didn't matter if you burned the opponent, just limit their movements. If they didn't want to suffer damage from the lava, they could only go around…

Okay, he's jumping over here!

The Lava Flask had instantly turned the area into a field of lava, but Steamed Bun Invasion leapt into the air. With a powerful Knee Attack, half jumping half attacking, he continued straight towards Endless Forest.

He managed to avoid the Lava Flask this way, but this kind of attack was just too reckless!

Endless Forest stepped to the side, and with a wave of his sleeve, a dark purple shadow flew out. It was the Witch skill Night Cloak, which could grab, and because it had a higher priority than Knee Attack, the grab could not be avoided with this skill.

The midair Steamed Bun Invasion looked like he crashed right into the Night Cloak, and he was immediately bound by the shadows and fell into the lava. But Zhang Wei wouldn't let him get away with just that amount of damage. Endless Forest raised his broom and prepared to launch further attacks, only to see something small flying toward him and steadily growing larger. In an instant it filled his field of view, and he was hit by the Brick.

When was this Brick thrown?

Zhang Wei didn't know, but he was sure that it was before his Night Cloak, otherwise it would have been interrupted by the Night Cloak's grab. And now, the Brick had hit him and interrupted his attack, while the binding effect of Night Cloak had worn off already. Steamed Bun Invasion was in the lava, and although he was taking damage, it didn't affect his movements.

Tyrannical Chain Punch!

Zhang Wei immediately wanted to have Endless Forest to dodge, but it was already too late. Steamed Bun Invasion was right in front of him. He got up and turned over, ignoring the lava's damage and coming with a ruthless hammering blow. Zhang Wei would suffer in this exchange. But he didn't really understand Steamed Bun Invasion's usage of Tyrannical Chain Punch right now. Although this was a fierce attack, there were no good follow-up skills. It would make more sense to first use some smaller attacks to pave the way, then finish the combo with a Tyrannical Chain Punch. But Steamed Bun Invasion was decisive, directly using the final step and leaving it at that.

Right, leaving it at that.

After the Tyrannical Chain Punch, Steamed Bun Invasion rolled backward and retreated. This was the motion prescribed by the system at the end of this skill and was unavoidable. Of course, Endless Forest, who had just been battered by the Tyrannical Chain Punch wouldn't be able to counterattack in such a short period of time. Otherwise, this attack would just become a skill where after it was used the player would be forced to suffer an attack.

So after this, the two characters stood up at almost the same time, and tossed out items at the same time.

Steamed Bun Invasion used Sand Toss, while Endless Forest used a Disperse Powder. If the opponent had any buffs, the Disperse Powder would get rid of them, and if they didn't, then the Disperse Powder would reduce their speed.

The two scattered materials intersected in midair and continued toward their targets, neither affecting the other. Because they were close to each other and were both attacking, neither had time to dodge, and they were both struck at the same time. Steamed Bun Invasion's movements instantly became slower, and Endless Forest had been a little late in turning his camera, so the Sand Toss reached his face. His field of view turned black.

Being Blind didn't mean that you couldn't move, so Zhang Wei immediately had Endless Forest to jump backward. The Blind effect from Sand Toss didn't last very long, while the effects of Disperse Powder would last a solid 10 seconds. After the Blind wore off, he would still have plenty of time to counterattack.

Zhang Wei hopped backwards in darkness, but while doing so suddenly felt like his character had been hit by something. After seeing the status effect appear, he was startled. This… wasn't this the lowered speed effect caused by Disperse Powder?

Tooth for Tooth!

Zhang Wei immediately knew that Steamed Bun had used this skill before his Disperse Powder, which allowed him to secretly learn the Disperse Powder skill. But as to why Steamed Bun activated Tooth for Tooth, Zhang Wei couldn't understand at all. Even though the events had already passed and Disperse Powder had been stealthily learned, Zhang Wei still couldn't understand why he would make such a move. Using such a powerful attack and then a Disperse Powder just pulled their speeds to the same level, he hadn't established any sort of advantage!

While he was confused, the Blind wore off and his vision recovered, only for him to see Steamed Bun Invasion charging toward him..

This… there was still a large distance between them! How would Zhang Wei let himself be attacked so easily? He saw Steamed Bun Invasion raise his hand in preparation to throw something, and he was prepared to dodge, but he quickly saw that the direction in which he had raised his hand was simply too far off-target.

What direction is that?

Zhang Wei turned his camera to see where Steamed Bun Invasion had thrown that missed Poison Needle, and then suddenly, there was a clunk at the back of his head. He was hit by a Brick, knocked Dizzy!

Brick! Where'd it come from?

Zhang Wei didn't know, but he had been Blind for a moment, so Steamed Bun Invasion must have used that time to find the right angle to pull it out. But Steamed Bun Invasion of course wouldn't run around behind him to throw the Brick. After all, he couldn't Teleport.

This Brick had originally been thrown at him almost head-on. The blind on Zhang Wei had worn off, but while he had still been fuzzy, Steamed Bun had come up with a diversion. That missed Poison Needle caused Zhang Wei to turn his camera, so he didn't see the Brick and left the back of his head wide open.

This this this...

What kind of strategy was this? He'd never heard of such a thing before! Zhang Wei was utterly baffled. And in that Tooth for Tooth exchange, what was with that Disperse Powder? He understood that even less…

Chapter 1144: A Hurried Core

Zhang Wei couldn't grasp Steamed Bun's train of thought. At this moment, his Endless Forest was in a Dizzy state. No Glory player would miss this kind of opportunity to attack. Steamed Bun Invasion stepped forward. He gripped Endless Forest's neck with a Strangle and let loose punches and kicks. 　　

Witches had far better close combat capabilities compared to Elementalists. Enhancing the broom with magic dust had once been a popular playstyle. However, for defense, besides Battle Mages, who could activate Magic Shield to forcefully take a burst of damage, Mages were quite frail. After a Strangle combo along with the previous Tyrannical Chain Punch, Endless Forest's health had dropped by 20%.

The opening wasn't going well!

Endless Forest was able to escape from the combo and fly away with his broom. He hadn't been able to find an opening to launch a counterattack, so he planned on resetting back to neutral and starting over.

However, this map had a vast empty horizon. Endless Forest could only pull a bit of distance between them. He wasn't able to actually hide anywhere. While in the air, Zhang Wei had his character look back and saw Steamed Bun Invasion chasing closely after him. He could see all sorts of openings to attack and felt an unbearable urge to act.

"Could it be some sort of weird trick again?"

Zhang Wei carefully analyzed the situation and repeatedly reassured himself. Endless Forest leaped in the air and swept with his broom, using a Witch's unique way of attacking to strike Steamed Bun Invasion.

Then, he saw Steamed Bun Invasion turn around and immediately run away.　

Zhang Wei was puzzled. He was truly at a loss.

What is going on? As soon as I turned around to attack, he ran away. What is he thinking? He can't be thinking of chasing me from behind and hoping that I stand still for him to attack me, right?

While still in a daze, he suddenly noticed an object flying towards him in his field of vision!

Another one!

This time, Zhang Wei was prepared. Endless Forest swept his broom in the air and twisted his body to dodge the Brick.

How dangerous!

It was a very normal attack, but Zhang Wei could feel cold sweat running down his back. He had lost focus for just an instant again. A little bit closer and that Brick would have hit. When fighting against this Steamed Bun, it's really hard to concentrate!

During this time, Steamed Bun raised his hand again.

Zhang Wei didn't even think about what Steamed Bun might be doing. He immediately had Endless Forest sweep his broom again to dodge.

A Poison Needle flitted by. Brawlers had quite a few mid-range attacks. After this Poison Needle, Steamed Bun Invasion raised his hand once more.

You're going to keep going? What's the point!

Zhang Wei didn't know whether to laugh or cry. He had his Endless Forest sweep his broom in the air another time.

Huh? I didn't move!　　

Zhang Wei blanked out. He immediately realized what had happened and wanted to cry. Trying to react now was too late. A Molotov Cocktail smashed into Endless Forest, setting him ablaze. Endless Forest turned into a giant fireball and crashed towards the ground.

"Hahahaha, Witches can only sweep their brooms six times. You don't even understand that? What a noob!" Steamed Bun even typed some trash talk in the chat. Zhang Wei was so angry that his lungs were about to explode. Pro players made mistakes. Sometimes, those mistakes were low-level ones. For example, he had forgotten to count how many sweeps he had left, which was indeed a beginner mistake. As the saying goes "A man is prone to stumbling when walking, and a horse is prone to stumbling when galloping." In any case, the word "noob" shouldn't be used to describe a pro player, let alone one that had fought in the pro scene for eight years. He was undoubtedly a veteran that had stood the test of time.

Zhang Wei was furious. Unfortunately, Endless Forest's current fireball appearance was truly a manifestation of his mistake. On the ground, Steamed Bun was already waiting for him with a Sand Toss ready in his hands.

Zhang Wei didn't even need to think to dodge. Endless Forest twisted his body, turning his head at the same time. Suddenly, a Brick hit him.

Zhang Wei was about to go crazy. A Sand Toss to force him to turn his head and then a Brick? What a shallow and outdated move… who does that anymore? But the guy in front of him was happily using it with gusto. That previous Poison Needle had been the same principle. Was this guy treating this pro match like the in-game Arena? Zhang Wei would occasionally go there to have some fun, and quite a few outdated moves in the pro scene were used a lot among normal players like Steamed Bun's previous move…

But the important part was that this shallow and outdated move had actually worked.

After being put into a Dizzy state, Endless Forest was given a fierce beating. His health dropped a large chunk again. And this time, Zhang Wei was bent on revenge. He wasn't going to retreat and wait for an opportunity like before. He was planning on directly finding an opening and attack the other side. Even ordinary old-timers could be angry.

Steamed Bun obviously wasn't able to execute a perfect combo. Not long afterwards, Zhang Wei found an opening. Endless Forest swept his broom at Steamed Bun Invasion and fiercely attacked him. Steamed Bun Invasion went on the defensive and soon found an opportunity too. He seized it and gave Endless Forest a blow or two. Bang bang bang. The two got into a messy scuffle. In the end, Zhang Wei was experienced. There was order to his randomness. He was constantly calculating the costs to each trade. However, like before, Zhang Wei was unable to figure out Steamed Bun. In this scuffle, he clearly had the advantage. He had almost caught up; their health bars were nearly even now. But Steamed Bun didn't seem to have any intentions of trying anything different. He seemed as if he were content with continuing this fight in this way.

What is he planning?

Zhang Wei couldn't help think to himself, but he was unable to make heads or tails out of it.　

Their team had analyzed that when fighting Steamed Bun, he should play it by ear and act whenever he saw an opportunity, but the problem was that he couldn't find any "opportunities", so how could he act on them?

Whatever, let's just keep going!

Zhang Wei threw caution to the wind, and he kept fighting Steamed Bun in this way. And then he won, just like that.

"You're pretty good."

When Endless Forest cleaned up the last of Steamed Bun Invasion's health, Steamed Bun left these "dying words".　

During the entire match, the two hadn't really talked with each other. Only Steamed Bun Invasion had said a few words. The first time he talked, he called Zhang Wei a noob. The second time he talked, he said Zhang Wei was good. His two remarks were polar opposites. There hadn't been any set-up for this sudden turnaround.

I won?

The word Glory jumped onto his screen. Steamed Bun Invasion had turned into a corpse on the ground. Zhang Wei was still in a daze.

I won, just like that?　　

What type of match was that? Had there been any crazy technical moves? Had there been any meaningful interactions? Had there been anything noteworthy enough to reflect upon? Zhang Wei came out from his player booth. When he came down, his brows were furrowed the entire time as if he had been the loser. He couldn't help but look towards Happy. He looked at that guy, Bao Rongxing, who returned to Happy's player bench in high spirits, walking confidently and freely as if he had been the winner.

"What a pity. I almost won." Zhang Wei could hear Steamed Bun say to his teammates. Zhang Wei nearly tripped. What do you mean almost won? It wasn't even close! With your inability to adapt, any knowledgeable person could have foreseen that you would lose. Could it be that you couldn't see it? Even if you couldn't, the others in Happy should be able to! What about Ye Xiu?

"Mm, it was a pity. Better luck next time." Ye Xiu said.

Fuck! Ye Xiu was agreeing? What the heck? Had he really been in danger just before? I had narrowly escaped from the gates of hell by just a fluke? Zhang Wei was a veteran that had joined the scene in Season 3. He had witnessed the pinnacle of Ye Xiu's career and didn't doubt this God's capabilities. With even Ye Xiu agreeing with Steamed Bun's remark, Zhang Wei suddenly started to doubt himself.

"Nice job." A teammate said to him at this moment. It was a common encouragement from a teammate.

"What a close call!" Zhang Wei subconsciously blurted out.

"Ah? How was that close?" His teammate looked weirdly at him.

"Huh?" Zhang Wei also looked weirdly at his teammate. It wasn't close? He couldn't help but look at Happy's side. Steamed Bun had already sat back down, chatting exuberantly with the person next to him. Zhang Wei couldn't hear him clearly, but it sounded like he was very proud of himself. How come the listener looked like he wanted to cry out SOS though?

What exactly went wrong? Zhang Wei went into deep thought.　

At this moment, the individual competition's third round began. Hundred Blossom's Zou Yuan versus Happy's Su Mucheng.　

It was a confrontation between two Gunners. However, Su Mucheng had become famous far earlier than Zou Yuan. Zou Yuan was also very famous right now, but this fame had always made him feel uneasy. He had originally been a normal second-year player, ready to stand up from the bench. He would do his best whenever the team needed him and strive for more opportunities. After the team dragged him from the bench, they refused to let him sit back down and even gave him the team's symbol, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Such treatment should be the dream of any pro player. Zou Yuan had dreamt of this before too, but he would have never imagined this dream would come true. When Zhang Jiale suddenly retired, the team wasn't able to find a suitable Spitfire player, so they pushed him forward to take on the role.

In the span of a single night, he became everyone's hope. He became the future of Team Hundred Blossoms. He became the successor to Zhang Jiale.

Before that day, no one had every said these words to him. After that day, Zou Yuan didn't feel happiness and joy, but fear and panic. He felt like he had been tossed into a maelstrom without anyone to guide him out of it.

That season, Zou Yuan didn't perform too well, but because of the fan's love for Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, he had been pushed into All-Stars...

All-Star, team core, ace player...

Zou Yuan obtained what many strived for without any difficulties to the extent that he couldn't escape from these responsibilities even if he wanted to.　

However, Zou Yuan knew very well that nothing here was real. That season, he had risen along with Tang Hao, who shined endlessly. Tang Hao had been Team Hundred Blossom's true pillar. And him? He had probably been seen as a burden who occupied a toilet but didn't shit.

Zou Yuan bitterly hung on for an entire season, persevering with something he simply couldn't do. When that season ended, Zou Yuan was at a loss for his future. He had been the core of a team for a season, but he didn't feel confident in himself in the slightest.

Then, Zhang Jiale returned and joined Team Tyranny, who purchased Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Having lost this character, Zou Yuan thought he would be kicked out. Who would have thought that the team would immediately look for him and discuss creating a new Spitfire for him. They would also find him a suitable partner to rebuild the team's core.

This time, he wouldn't be pushed to do something beyond his abilities like last season. This time, the team truly wanted to nurture him.

After a season of struggle and confusion as the core, the team still wanted him as the core? Zou Yuan truly felt like a dream had come true. Then, Team Blue Rain's Yu Feng joined and together they formed the new Hundred Blossoms. The team didn't break their promise and created a new Spitfire, Blooming Blossoms, according to his habits and strengths.

He was capable. He shouldn't be considered Zhang Jiale's substitute. Team Hundred Blossoms introduced him as such.

Chapter 1145: Launcher versus Spitfire (1)

The five second countdown passed quickly. This match was undoubtedly the first highlight of today's battle. Two All-Star players, two All-Star characters. Although Zou Yuan's status as an All-Star was partly fueled by the emotions of Hundred Blossoms fans, after one season, his ability was beginning to gain attention and recognition, and he himself steadily gained confidence.

The match began, and Zou Yuan had his Spitfire Bright Blossoms rush towards the center of the map.

Blood and Blossoms.

Team Hundred Blossoms had wanted to recreate this duo. But it was a shame, for this world had only one Zhang Jiale, and only one Sun Zheping, and therefore only one Blood and Blossoms.

Recreating this pairing was Hundred Blossoms' dream, or at least the blueprint that they drew out for their fans. But in reality, Zou Yuan had his own style, and Yu Feng wasn't very much like Sun Zheping. No matter what, it would be impossible for these two to completely mimic the partnership between Zhang Jiale and Sun Zheping. But, so what? The inimitable wasn't necessarily the strongest. From the start, Yu Feng hadn't been very interested in recreating their style anyway. He had come from Blue Rain, a team aiming for the championship win, because he wanted to build an era that was entirely his. He certainly wasn't here to be a copy of anyone else.

During the first half of last season, they had attempted to recreate Blood and Blossoms, but Hundred Blossoms' performance hadn't been very good. Afterwards, Yu Feng and Zou Yuan made adjustments. They coordinated with one another in a more comfortable way based off their personal habits and personal styles. Hundred Blossoms' immediately performance went up.

Now, neither of them would become confused. They would use their own style to surpass their seniors and establish a partnership that was entirely their own. Even though the outside world still called them Blood and Blossoms, they believed that they would eventually earn a name that was entirely their own.

Carrying this belief, Zou Yuan and Hundred Blossoms greeted the new season together.

In the first round, they encountered Heavenly Swords, and with them one of the previous creators of Blood and Blossoms, Sun Zheping. In that match, Sun Zheping won one point in the individual round, and although his opponent was neither Zou Yuan nor Yu Feng, the world still made the comparison between junior and senior. Heavenly Swords lost overall, but Sun Zheping's one point stood out, and later discussions painted him as if he were the victor.

These sort of irresponsible remarks left Zou Yuan feeling helpless. All he could do was focus and battle well.

I must win this point beautifully. This was the goal that Zou Yuan set for himself. He knew that the opponent he was about to face was no pushover, but the greater the difficulty, the greater the value of this point.

Bright Blossoms quickly reached the center of the map, and Zou Yuan saw Dancing Rain rapidly approaching from the other side of the map.

Dancing Rain was absolutely an All-Star character, but after her return to the league, everyone discovered that Dancing Rain hadn't grown as much as expected of such an All-Star character. For most teams, their All-Star characters were the focus of their upgrades after the level cap was raised. After Happy upgraded Boundless Sea's Silver weapon Mirror Moon to level 75, every All-Star character's weapon was level 75. As for their other Silver equipment, that varied between teams and depended on their conditions.

But although Dancing Rain was an extremely qualified character, an All-Star Launcher, her current equipment was somewhat lacking. Her weapon Devouring Sun was the only Silver equipment she had. It was clear that while she was in Excellent Era, after the Level 75 update, Dancing Rain hadn't had an important place in their upgrading plans. Of course, another reason was that Excellent Era's materials gathering hadn't progressed very smoothly during that time.

Now, comparing these All-Stars just by their equipment, Bright Blossoms was in much better shape. This account was wearing five Level 75 equipment, which was considered very good.

In terms of characters, Hundred Blossoms had the upper hand.

What about player condition? Su Mucheng had gone a whole year without playing any pro matches, while Zou Yuan had improved his technique, awareness, and temperament over the course of the past year. In terms of condition, it seemed that Hundred Blossoms held the upper hand here as well.

This was the analysis conducted by Hundred Blossoms on Su Mucheng and Dancing Rain. Now in this confrontation, Zou Yuan was completely confident. He didn't make any move to avoid her, and prepared to meet her head on.

He might not have moved strategically, but when Su Mucheng saw Bright Blossoms, she was the one to change direction.

Zou Yuan was confident, but not arrogant. Seeing Su Mucheng's careful avoidance, he didn't rush forward. The map for this battle consisted of narrow streets, and in theory it didn't really suit long-ranged classes, because there were simply too many ways to find cover from an attack. But both players were Gunners here, so there wasn't any advantage to be had here. It couldn't be forgotten that this was Happy's home game, they were the ones to choose the map, and Su Mucheng was no rookie, having more experience than even Zou Yuan. She chose this map, so she must have some plan. Her current maneuvering must be to take advantage of the special characteristics of this map. So, Zou Yuan didn't rush forward. He studied his surroundings, and after studying the paths he could take, he chose to circle around to intercept her.

But right when Bright Blossoms changed directions, quote a commotion arose from the audience. From their omniscient view, the audience saw the full picture of what was going on. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain, after changing paths, wasn't trying to move around in a roundabout way, but instead chose to stand and wait in that position. After Bright Blossoms decided to circle around, Dancing Rain emerged again, and came around behind Bright Blossoms.

Glory wasn't Counterstrike, there was no chance of a one-hit knockout. But in a battle between experts, the first to attack had a high chance of seizing the initiative for the entire battle. In the current situation, Su Mucheng undoubtedly had the advantage. Dancing Rain quietly crept around behind Bright Blossoms, and began to launch an attack at his exposed back.

But who would have thought, at this moment Zou Yuan's Bright Blossoms suddenly stopped moving, and just stood there in that narrow street, as though in deep thought. The audience couldn't see anything from the projection, but onscreen, where they were displaying Bright Blossoms' camera view, everyone suddenly saw that from Bright Blossom's currently slightly-diagonal position, he could see both in front and behind him. Zou Yuan hadn't neglected his back, he had made preparations for two possibilities.

With this method, he hadn't really seized any opportunities, but at least he wouldn't let his opponent have an easy time. He wanted to pull this battle back to a face-to-face confrontation, which, in a way, reflected Zou Yuan's confidence.

Of course, Su Mucheng had no way of predicting all of Zou Yuan's plans. She circled around, and as soon as she appeared, Zou Yuan saw her out of the edge of his vision. Su Mucheng saw that Bright Blossoms was just standing there as though he had gone offline, so she didn't move to dodge or hide, and immediately fired an attack.

The sneak attack didn't work, and the two were now directly throwing attacks at each other. The battle was progressing the way Zou Yuan had hoped it would. He readjusted this focus and prepared for a good direct fight. But Bright Blossoms had barely managed to take two steps forward. He hadn't even fired his first shot, when Dancing Rain's powerful smothering attack arrived. Zou Yuan had no choice but to first evade the attack, but with this evasion, he immediately lost the initiative.

Even a Launcher's normal attacks carried an AoE effect, not a single one was a point attack, and so all their attacks were AoE, the only difference was the extent of the area of effect. .

As a result, Zou Yuan discovered that he had made a mistake. He had picked this position so that Bright Blossoms could see both sides, but it was too narrow here. When the Launcher attack here, Zou Yuan suddenly found that he had no way of dodging.

This position...

Zou Yuan finally realized how disadvantageous this position was for him. For the Launcher, it was like shooting fish in a barrel.

It was impossible to go forward, so his only choice was to control Bright Blossoms to retreat backward, which would be a difficult task. Of the 24 classes in Glory, the Launcher had the largest attack range, and Dancing Rain was an All-Star character. In Excellent Era, she would often have to use a Screen Cannon strategy to coordinate, and so her equipment boosted her attack range even further. And now he wanted to try to increase the distance and escape her range, but how could it be that easy?

Zou Yuan of course couldn't rely just on movement to escape. Under the rain of bullets, Bright Blossoms ate the damage and tossed out two grenades.

One of the grenades instantly exploded. The screens displaying the match to the audience turned a flashing white.

It was a Flash Bullet, and Dancing Rain was clearly affected. That flashing white screen was her current camera view.

But, the attacks didn't stop...

In these conditions, Dancing Rain was still using her heavy cannon, spitting out dense blasts in front of her. Bright Blossoms' other grenade was a Smoke Bullet, and the smoke was already roiling in the air. But not even the Flash Bullet was enough to stop Su Mucheng's attacks, would the reduced vision caused by the smoke be an obstacle for her?

It didn't seem so...

Dancing Rain was engulfed in the smoke, but her footsteps didn't stop, nor did her attacks. To attack here, she didn't even need to see. Flash Bullet, Smoke Bullet, these things became meaningless.

The audience was stunned. What kind of skill did it take to be able to fight blind like this?

Immediately, sound of applause rose from the audience. Of course, Zou Yuan obviously couldn't hear. He had come into the match filled with confidence, but now he was already a little planicked. From the audience's perspective, neither of his grenades had affected Dancing Rain's attacks at all. But Zou Yuan, in game, could see more clearly, and he knew that Su Mucheng's attacks had changed. The instant her vision was blocked, her attacks became even stronger, even fiercer. The area affected by her attacks instantly became even larger. In such a condition, she actually gained an even greater initiative.

But Zou Yuan wasn't prepared to lose just like this. Ever since he had built up his confidence, his playstyle had became tougher. Flash Bullet, Smoke Bullet, these skills could be used to create a turning point, and Zou Yuan wasn't about to let them go to waste. Su Mucheng wasn't affected by her loss of vision, so he could add some more attacks to cause trouble for her.

Bright Blossoms didn't retreat and counterattacked.

Chapter 1146: Launcher versus Spitfire (2)

Under the pressure of Dancing Rain's relentless attacks, Zou Yuan pushed forward instead of retreating. He had Bright Blossoms steadily advance, so he could get into a range from which he could attack her.

Under normal circumstances, Zou Yuan's current strategy would certainly lead to Bright Blossoms taking a lot of damage, and there was the possibility that he wouldn't even be able to break through Dancing Rain's attacks at all. But now, the Flash Bullet and Smoke Bullet were serving their purpose. Dancing Rain didn't stop attacking because Su Mucheng was relying on her technical skill to continue, but Zou Yuan knew that she had no way of aiming accurately when she couldn't see.

Bright Blossoms fiercely charged forward, and as expected, there were no changes in Dancing Rain's attack patterns. Su Mucheng had just increased her firepower, but since she couldn't see anything, she had no way of adjusting to Bright Blossoms' change in movements.

This unchanging attack pattern posed no difficulty to Zou Yuan, for he was now a confident core player. Bright Blossoms endured the damage, and Dancing Rain finally entered his attack range.

He lifted his gun and prepared to fire a Freezing Bullet, but just as he was about to shoot, he heard three sounds of cannon fire. Three Anti-Tank Missiles, spitting fire, had flown in front of him.

Zou Yuan was shocked. The effects of the Flash Bullet on Dancing Rain still hadn't faded, so how did Su Mucheng know his movements?

Bright Blossoms could obviously take the damage from the Anti-Tank Missiles, but the problem was the impact caused by the explosions would shake his character and prevent him from attacking. This was a special characteristic of Gunner classes. Even for normal attacks, as long as the target was accurately hit, there would be a Stun effect to the part hit. And the Launcher had heavy firepower compared to the other Gunner classes, so this characteristic was the most apparent out of all of them.

As a result, Zou Yuan had Bright Blossoms duck to the side. But then he heard a series of bangs, Dancing Rain had fired an artillery shell in a low arc which exploded, sending Stingers flying in all directions.

Seeing this attack, Zou Yuan suddenly understood. In reality, Su Mucheng hadn't seen Bright Blossoms' movements, but she understood what kind of attack she was most vulnerable to at the moment. So, she kept track of the time and took preventative measures. As it turned out, Zou Yuan had done what she was guarding against, allowing Su Mucheng stop him with her eyes closed. You want to continue? The effects of the Flash Bullet had faded, and Su Mucheng could see Bright Blossoms closing in ahead, so she used Aerial Fire. Her character flew backwards and pulled away, and in an instant he was smothered under her attacks again.

Zou Yuan despised this narrow little road. If the map weren't like this, he wouldn't be suffering so badly right now. If the map weren't like this, Su Mucheng couldn't have crushed him with her eyes closed like that. If the map weren't like this, he wouldn't have once again fallen under Dancing Rain's suppression.

In reality, a Spitfire could also similarly render an opponent helpless with their firepower, but unfortunately for him, Su Mucheng was taking full advantage of the Launcher's superior range. Despite facing a Spitfire, another long range-attacker, she could still use distance to suppress him.

If he charged forward, Dancing Rain would retreat back; if he tried to retreat, Dancing Rain would approach. The precision of her attacks and technique left Zou Yuan stunned.

Su Mucheng… One year without playing any pro matches. Even though she might not be able to immediately adjust to the tempo of high-level battles so quickly, but her personal skill had unexpectedly advanced over this past year. As a result of her skilled usage of the map, Bright Blossoms was beautifully trapped in this narrow alley, and Zou Yuan couldn't find any opening to escape.

Was this Su Mucheng?

Zou Yuan, beaten down, was puzzled.

Personally, he didn't really understand Su Mucheng. He had debuted as a pro in Season 7, becoming a rookie in Team Hundred Blossoms alongside Tang Hao. But because he played the same class as Zhang Jiale, he had pitifully few chances to play during that season, and he wasn't much different from an audience member. In Season 8, he was suddenly thrust into the role of the main character, and he stumbled through that season in a trance. He wasn't able to find his own bearings, how could he pay attention to anyone else? Then, by Season 9, when he became a truly stable main player, Su Mucheng wasn't among his list of opponents, so he had no reason to investigate her.

What kind of player was Su Mucheng?

Zou Yuan's understanding only came from gossip. He knew that although Su Mucheng was extremely popular, many people didn't think much of her. They would say that she relied on her physical appearance, that her strength was overrated. Some people directly called her a flower vase, and some radical Excellent Era fans blamed on her the team's decline after its three consecutive championship victories. After all, she joined Excellent Era in Season 4, and after then, Excellent Era had never managed to win another championship.

To the public, Su Mucheng was a controversial player, but what about in the pro circle? Zou Yuan knew that, aside from some rookies who didn't know anything, no one viewed her like that.

Then what about Zou Yuan himself?

Zou Yuan was forced to admit that he was biased against Su Mucheng. And this bias didn't come from his own analysis, but was influenced by surrounding opinion.

Rookies within the same team always tended to have good relationships with each other. And the year Zou Yuan debuted, his fellow rookie was a player named Tang Hao.

Given Tang Hao's personality, it wasn't hard to guess that he would have an opinion about such a controversial player. And because Zou Yuan had the most interactions with this fellow rookie Tang Hao, his opinion of Su Mucheng was influenced by Tang Hao, so he tended not to think much of her.

But at that time, they were just two gossiping rookies. Neither he nor Tang Hao had the status to treat Su Mucheng as an opponent!

By the time the two of them had that status and position, Su Mucheng had run off to the Challenger League.

Zou Yuan didn't remember much of the gossip of his rookie days, but that impression from back then lingered in his heart. On the battlefield, Zou Yuan didn't carry that mentality with him. No matter the opponent, he wouldn't underestimate them. But Su Mucheng's demonstrated skill still truly shocked him - it far surpassed his expectations of the Su Mucheng he thought he knew. Because of his bias, the Su Mucheng he thought he knew didn't have all that much skill.

But now, he was thoroughly suppressed by Su Mucheng. Zou Yuan wasn't as arrogant as Tang Hao, so he quickly recognized this reality.

But so what?

This realization came too late. At the end of this battle, Zou Yuan was defeated.

In the individual round, Happy gained an early lead of 2 to 1. As this was Happy's home game, there were of course cheers and applause from the crowd.

In the midst of the cheers, Su Mucheng walked out of the player booth and offstage.

She was calm when facing victory, just like when facing criticism. She would always smile and not reply.

Because she didn't care about that.

She walked offstage and returned to Happy's player area, where Ye Xiu stood and clapped to welcome her.

"Heehee," Su Mucheng giggled, making a victory sign with her hands.

"Impressive," Ye Xiu praised. "You suppressed him without leaving a single opening, you played really well."

"Don't you think?" Su Mucheng was still smiling as she sat beside Ye Xiu. She would always strive for victory, but beside this person, she felt that her hard work had greater meaning.

"Alright, next is the group round, those who are going…" Ye Xiu turned to call for those who were playing in the next round. Of course, Su Mucheng couldn't go on again, so she simply sat to the side and watched. Her smile was even brighter than it was when she had obtained victory.

Happy was bright, but Hundred Blossoms was lost.

They had lost two points in the individual round, and the one point they had won was under strange circumstances, the opponent clearly wasn't in good condition.

"Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng already went in the individual round. No matter what, we can't lose the group round," Yu Feng said to the two players who would be playing with him in the group round. The two of them nodded determinedly, and then they looked over at Happy.

In their eyes, Happy's strongest players were Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng. Although Fang Rui was also an All-Star, he was in the midst of changing classes, and he couldn't completely adjust so quickly. If he were still a Thief, Hundred Blossoms would also treat him as a dangerous opponent, but as a Qi Master, he was a little weaker.

There was a short break between the individual and group rounds, but Hundred Blossoms' three players were already walking toward the player booths. The large screens at the stadium displayed to the audience the players of both teams who would be playing in the group round.

Team Hundred Blossoms: Zhou Guangyi, Yu Feng, Zhu Xiaoping.

Team Happy: Fang Rui, Mo Fan, Tang Rou.

The first matchup was Fang Rui against Zhou Guangyi. Both characters had already logged on, and it was now the pre-match display segment. In their player booths, the players could see this on their screens as well. Fang Rui, this number one Thief in Glory, suddenly becoming a Qi Master… to be honest, Zhou Guangyi respected his courage.

Zhou Guangyi was familiar with Fang Rui, as they had both debuted in Season 5. He had better opportunities at the beginning than Fang Rui did, because he had been in Tyranny, and at that time, Tyranny had just toppled Excellent Era's dynasty to win the Season 4 championships and officially stand at the summit. Zhou Guangyi began in a championship team, and his future was nothing but bright.

The next few seasons, Zhou Guangyi's development was smooth. Although he didn't become a star, he was continually improving, and he became a very strong player.

However, while Zhou Guangyi was improving, Tyranny was declining. After Season 4, they didn't managed to fight their way to the finals again.

Last season, Tyranny made huge adjustments, inviting two top experts Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale. Tyranny's plan was clear, they wanted to let these veterans at the end of their careers shine brilliantly one last time. Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale shone brilliantly, exciting the players, but at such a time, it was inevitable that there would be grief for some members of Tyranny. There were only so many spaces on a roster, and if a player came, that meant that another one had to go.

Every player longed for a chance to play onstage, so that season, Zhou Guangyi left Tyranny sadly, the team where he had fought for four years. He had originally thought he could play on that team until he retired…

Chapter 1147: Qi Master versus Assassin (1)

The first round of the group arena between Happy and Hundred Blossoms:

Fang Rui, Qi Master Boundless Sea

Zhou Guangyi, Assassin Cold Seasons.

The two had debuted the same season, so they were quite familiar with each other. It was a long-standing tradition for the rookies of each season to make a chat group and share experiences and tips with one another. As long as a player wasn't too antisocial, then they'd be able to make friends during this time. Even if they ended up in different places and positions, the days they had spent messing around together weren't forgotten easily. Fang Rui and Zhou Guangyi were by no means unfamiliar with each other, and they got along fairly well. When these players matched up with each other, it was natural for them to chat.

"Old Zhou, admit your defeat. I know your Assassin very well, but have you ever witnessed my Qi Master?" Fang Rui started to provoke him.

"Witness your unfamiliarity with the class?" Zhou Guangyi responded.

"That was last week," Fang Rui said.

"How about this week?"

"A bit rusty in the right hand, but my left hand is very adept," Fang Rui said.

"Then I hope your right hand won't be a burden for your left," Zhou Guangyi said.

"Impossible. With the title of Golden Right Hand, even if my right hand is a little rusty, it far surpasses your imagination," Fang Rui said.

"Let's hope so!" Zhou Guangyi laughed.

In Glory, the left hand used the keyboard while the right controlled the mouse. The mouse was mainly used to control an attack's trajectory and positioning. Fang Rui had the title of the Golden Right Hand due to his right hand's godly speed and precision, but unfortunately, his right hand was outstanding to the extent that his left hand couldn't keep up with the right hand's pace. All in all, playing required coordination between both hands, so without the assistance of a Golden Left Hand to support his Golden Right Hand, Fang Rui couldn't display his full potential.

As a result, Fang Rui's left hand was always dragged his right hand back. Zhou Guangyi obviously knew about this, so "I hope your right hand won't be a burden for your left" was a fairly fierce slap to the face.

The two friends continued to talk trash to each other. Soon afterwards, Zhou Guangyi's Assassin reached the center of the map, but Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was nowhere to be seen. Zhou Guangyi wasn't surprised, because even if Fang Rui had changed to a Qi Master, he probably wouldn't drop his dirty playing. A direct confrontation was never his style.

As an Assassin, it was more effective to launch a sudden ambush. The passive skill that Assassins received after advancing classes at Level 20 was Assassination. Its use was to increase the attack damage struck at the back of characters by 20%. Players already had a bonus of a 20% increase in damage for attacks hit on the back, an addition of another 20% would make it reach a shocking 40%. This was why when players were in a dungeon, regardless whether they were fighting a mob or boss, that strike on the back was always reserved for Assassins.

On top of this, Assassin's Level 50 active Awakening skill Vitals Strike was an active skill. When it was activated, the Assassin could pinpoint a vital point on the target, and when an attack accurately struck that vital point, the damage could reach as high as 200%.

Assassination, Vital Attack, and Life-Risking Strike. Among the 24 classes, the Assassin was the only class who could truly instant kill. As long as those skills were fully combined, even classes with high health like the Knight or Paladin might not be able to resist an Assassin's strike.

Instant killing was probably the boldest and most hot-blooded attack in Glory, but it was rare to see it in professional matches. This was because everyone would naturally watch out when they knew the Assassin had such skills. In addition, Life-Risking Strike was a skill in which both sides would suffer, so it might not give their team a chance to gain the upper hand.

However, throughout the course of Glory's competitive history, it wasn't as if no Assassin had made such a heroic move. There was a time when such a move became extremely well-known, and that one time was made through the character Zhou Guangyi was currently using.

That one assassination was completely worth it, whether judging by the target killed or the result it achieved. That attack was enough to cement Cold Season's place in the annals of Glory. When Zhou Guangyi and Cold Seasons transferred to Hundred Blossoms together, the fans of Tyranny even got quite emotional.

In the final match of the Season 4 finals, Cold Season's Life-Risking Strike assassinated One Autumn Leaf.

With this strike, Tyranny was able to win the championships and end Excellent Era's dynasty.

With this strike, the MVP of the final match was neither Han Wenqing nor Zhang Xinjie, but the user of Cold Seasons, who was called… Ji Leng. In reality, he wasn't an extremely outstanding or special player, but such a breathtaking strike made everyone remember his name.

Cold Season retired after that season and Zhou Guangyi joined Tyranny, taking over Cold Season the Assassin. Because of how exciting the finals were, whenever people saw Cold Season, they all hoped to see another stunning Life-Risking Strike. However, things weren't so simple in real life. Everyone's attention towards him gradually died down as they realized that the miracle wouldn't happen again. Most Assassins wouldn't really use such a suicidal method as their main playstyle. In recent years, only Li Xun from Team Void would pull off such a move, but that was because Team Void was able to provide him with the right conditions. As a team who possessed the strongest Phantom Demon, they could control their targets well, while also providing buffs for Li Xun's Assassin. This was why when Li Xun launched Life-Risking Strike, his chance of succeeding was greater, and the damage he took to himself was lower. This was why he was able to utilize this move more often than others in team matches.

As for Zhou Guangyi? Although he had inherited the Assassin who made the most stunning instant kill in the league, he wasn't someone who enjoyed pulling off an instant kill. His fighting style was similar to that of Yang Cong from Team 301 Degrees, who fought in a dominant and direct manner. In reality, it was the same for Ji Leng because it was Team Tyranny's style. For whatever reason, the conditions just happened to give him the opportunity to execute this surprise Life-Rising Strike. But because of how astonishing this trike was, the impressions towards his original style had been erased. Ji Leng had originally been like Zhou Guangyi. Both of them had the same style as Team Tyranny, straightforward and direct.

Cold Season rushed to the center, and as expected, Fang Rui was nowhere to be seen. If this was before, he would have been able to predict and guess Fang Rui's train of thought. However, Fang Rui had changed to a Qi Master, so Zhou Guangyi had no idea how he would fight.

However, considering Fang Rui's playstyle, it was too risky to wait for him to appear. Who knew how many tricks Fang Rui would set up to dupe you. Zhou Guangyi thought to himself. He decided to take the initiative. He couldn't just sit there doing nothing and wait for Fang Rui to find the perfect opening.

The group arena's map size was the same as the individual competition's. The map wouldn't change from the start to the end of the match, so it would even leave behind the marks created by the players who had fought previously. The map that Happy picked this time was called "Life-Seeking Path."

One would only need to hear the name to know that it was a disgusting, maze-like map which was suitable for dirty playing. As a result, it wouldn't be a surprise for Fang Rui to sneakily hide somewhere as soon as the battle began. After Zhou Guangyi had Cold Season enter the tangled and complicated maze from the vast, open land, he still couldn't find any signs of Boundless Sea. Instead, he saw Fang Rui roar in the channel: "What's going on? I've arrived, why did you run away? Where did you run off to?"

Zhou Guangyi ignored him. He wouldn't fall for such a childish trap.

However, maps like Life-Seeking Path tended to make him lose his temper. It was obvious that Tyranny, the team he had been in, would never use such a disgusting map. As for Hundred Blossoms, their ace was a long-ranged Spitfire, so they also wouldn't prefer maps with too many crisscrosses.

A shadow suddenly flashed before him!

Only two people existed in this match, so there was no doubt that the shadow must be Boundless Sea. Zhou Guangyi trusted his eyes and was resolute about sprinting ahead. However, considering Fang Rui's dirtiness, it would be too risky if he tailed directly behind. He had to change directions to catch him off guard.

Zhou Guangyi was still scouting out another direction when the shadow from before appeared again.

"Fuck, there you are, making me go to so much effort to find you. Why'd you start playing dirty after transferring to Hundred Blossoms?" As Fang Rui spoke, he rushed straight ahead, much to everyone's surprise.

Qi Bullet!

Boundless Sea shot out the Qi Master's lowest-level skill with a lift of his hands. It was obvious that such a skill wouldn't cause Zhou Guangyi too much trouble. He dodged it easily, but he felt like there was something fishy about Boundless Sea charging straight towards him. Was there some sort of trap lying around?

The match with Zou Yuan was a lesson to learn from!

One could say that he was completely oppressed by a single wave after being lured into an extremely advantageous terrain for the opponent. What about now? This place wasn't spacious. Although Qi Masters didn't have the Launcher's extremely long shooting distance or strong fire power, they had reduced versions of such abilities. Was Fang Rui planning to repeat the same scene?

Sky Piercing Strike!

As he thought, Boundless Sea leapt up while pushing his hands down in midair. An airwave shot towards Cold Season. Zhou Guangyi immediately had Cold Season dodge by jumping back. The Sky Piercing Strike hit the ground and shockwaves spread from the ground. One jump wasn't enough for Cold Season, so he jumped again. If he followed his usual habits and style in a match, he would have charged forward and made a counterattack before Boundless Sea had a chance to reach the ground. However, his opponent was Fang Rui! How could he possibly fight head on? There must be other reasons.

"Don't think too much! We know each other so well, let's just fight it out!" Fang Rui yelled.

"Oh, really? It's too narrow here, shall we pick another place?" Zhou Guangyi said.

"Sure, lead the way." Fang Rui was very generous.

Zhou Guangyi grew suspicious. Glory's matches had a lot of freedom. Players could chat as they fought and it wouldn't count as cheating. This was because there could be traps and tactics hidden within the conversations. For example, Zhou Guangyi believed that there must be something fishy with Fang Rui's suggestion. Although he was leading the way, he did it by jumping backwards. He would never turn his back on someone who was titled the master of playing dirty and the Golden Right Hand…

Chapter 1148: Qi Master versus Assassin (2)

"Old Zhou, your distrust wounds me right in the heart!" Fang Rui's Boundless Sea casually followed the other player, and he even found time to send a message in chat.

With this message, not just Zhou Guangyi but every single person who had any understanding of the Glory pro circle was shouting in their hearts: Glory's master of playing dirty, if even you could be trusted, then nothing would be impossible in this world!

Zhou Guangyi, of course, was unmoved. He didn't see any clear signs, but he had a gut feeling that Fang Rui's trickery was about to unfold. If this were in the past, Zhou Guangyi absolutely could have guessed that this guy had traps over there to lure him into, but a Qi Master couldn't lay traps, so what kind of danger would be waiting for him to discover? Zhou Guangyi didn't dare slow down, so of course he didn't want to type a reply. He scrutinized the grass and trees and rocks around him as he moved.

Shortly thereafter, Cold Seasons retreated all the way to the center of the map, Boundless Sea following him along all the while.

"As former partners, let's have a clean and dignified fight to determine who wins!" Fang Rui called out in the chat.

Zhou Guangyi was speechless. What do you mean, "former partners"? For one, they had never been teammates before. Besides, in their personal relationship, they had always been friends and had never had any sort of conflict. They were on opposing teams, but that never affected their relationship. So what was with that "former"?

But Zhou Guangyi was in no mood to chatter with Fang Rui. Tyranny's players might have a word or two with you in a match, but it was never their style to talk on and on.

"Watch my attack, Sky Piercing Strike!"

Another message was sent to the chat. And then Boundless Sea waved his hands, but he released a fast Qi Bullet.

How dirty!

The audience all thought this, but would Zhou Guangyi be tricked? Of course not, he had known Fang Rui for many years now and had lots of experience facing him in battle. He wouldn't believe a single thing Fang Rui said in his messages and just pretended he didn't see them.

A Qi Bullet of course couldn't instantly kill an opponent. But Boundless Sea directly used a Qi Flowing Cloud, which was a skill that caused Qi to surround the user and increase the user's speed in all aspects. Next, he directly charged toward Cold Seasons.

The Qi Master was a Fighter subclass, so of course this class was very good at close combat, and many explosive skills were better at close range. But the problem was, Qi Masters wore cloth armor with very low physical defense, and most close-range classes were physical attackers. So, if Qi Masters wanted to stay close to an opponent and fight explosively, they needed to find a good opportunity. It was very rare to see a Qi Master shoot a Qi Bullet and then just directly rush an opponent like this.

Especially since he was facing an Assassin right now, who possessed extremely high physical attack and numerous skills that could deal explosive damage. And this Assassin was in the hands of a former Tyranny player. Players from Tyranny excelled at this sort of direct fighting. Anyone who had some analytical understanding of Glory all thought that Fang Rui's actions right now were illogical.

An All-Star level player should never be making such illogical actions.

But, this person was Fang Rui.

Thus, the illogical immediately smelled of something suspicious.

There must be some trickery here - this thought crossed the minds of everyone watching this match. They were using their advantage of being able to see the entire battlefield to try and discover the truth that was hidden behind the deceit.

Everyone thought this way, and Zhou Guangyi was no exception. He was 180% sure that Fang Rui was not planning to have a face-to-face confrontation with him.

So, when Boundless Sea activated Qi Flowing Cloud, he immediately had Cold Seasons activate Swift Movements. An Assassin sprinting with this buff would move the fastest out of all 24 classes. Even with Qi Flowing Cloud, Boundless Sea couldn't catch up. As a result, a close combat specialist Assassin was increasing his distance from the mid-range Qi Master. It seemed extremely illogical and counterintuitive.

But no one thought this way. Everyone felt that Zhou Guangyi acted completely correctly, as expected of an experienced player. At this time, how could he let himself fall into Fang Rui's a? Better to first spar with him a bit.

In a footrace, Boundless Sea wasn't Cold Seasons's opponent, but he had attacking skills. As they ran, he launched Qi Bullet after Qi Bullet, occasionally interspersed with other skills. Many of a Qi Master's skills required a cast time. It was like the Mages' spellcasting, but here they called it chants. The biggest difference between this and spellcasting was that when spellcasting, a Mage had to focus, so they couldn't move or make any other actions. Qi Masters were different, their chants could be done at the same time as other actions. This characteristic was similar to a Ninja's seals.

They chased and fought for a while, but no trickery was revealed. But the Assassin was a class that focused on explosive bursts of power, including buffs. They were powerful when used, but their effects were short-lasting. The duration of Fleet Foot was much shorter than Qi Flowing Cloud, so after the effect wore off, Boundless Sea steadily caught up to Cold Seasons.

Of course, this was also partly because Zhou Guangyi didn't want to run completely away in the first place. He just wanted to try and figure out what Fang Rui was up to. But after using up this Fleet Foot, he truly didn't discover any kind of hidden mystery.

Next… give it a try?

This was Zhou Guangyi's thought. These Tyranny players never liked running around in circles like this. Today, it was only because he was facing Fang Rui that he was careful and went to the effort to spend so much time wandering around. But now, Zhou Guangyi's patience had reached its limit. Cold Seasons was in front, Boundless Sea was behind using all sorts of skills to attack nonstop. But Cold Seasons suddenly stopped and spun around, riding a cold light as he flew toward his opponent, prepared to kill.

Shining Cut!

An attack skill that also involved the character moving at an extremely fast speed, and in an instant he had appeared next to Boundless Sea. The audience roared in excitement. This counterattack was extremely sudden, but as soon as he decided to take action, it was with such a decisive move. The Assassin's momentum could change with a glance.

The Shining Cut came very quickly, but Fang Rui wouldn't just waiting to be hit. If an attack like this was enough to take him down, did he have the face to stay in this profession?

Boundless Sea jumped to the side. With a movement of his hands, a mass of Qi sparking with electricity formed between his palms, and he forced it toward Cold Seasons.

Qi Master skill: Flash Burst. After hitting the target, it would pour qi into the target, dealing continuous damage. This skill, if used in coordination with a team CCing the target, a Flash Burst lasting until the end could be extremely painful.

Although this wasn't as strong as that situation, Zhou Guangyi didn't dare slow down. Cold Seasons sheathed his knife from the Shining Cut and jumped, directly to Boundless Sea's side.

Then, Boundless Sea also turned with him. He was still holding the Flash Burst in his hands, pushing it in this new direction.

You're using that as a shield!

Zhou Guangyi thought this, Cold Seasons instantly jumped up, and then double-jumped. In an instant, he was behind Fang Rui, and he straightened his legs into a Diving Arrow kick.

Boundless Sea was still holding that Flash Burst. This attack was like that, as long as the right controls were being continually inputted, it could be pushed around indefinitely. Even as Cold Seasons ducked around and used that Diving Arrow kick, Boundless Sea's Flash Burst was still prepared to be sent toward him.

But Diving Arrow also had the side effect of giving the user another jump. Regardless of whether or not the kick landed on its target, the user could borrow its power for movement. Zhou Guangyi of course wouldn't let Cold Seasons crash into that Flash Burst, so he used the force of the kick to move backward.

Fang Rui finally gave up on this Flash Burst, and pushed out a Qi Bullet. This low-level attack didn't cause much damage, nor did it have any particular effects, so Zhou Guangyi didn't prepare to dodge it. But this Qi Bullet was actually launched inaccurately. Given its trajectory, it was going to pass right by Cold Seasons without his doing anything.

But the Golden Right Hand!

Fang Rui had the title of the Golden Right Hand because of his accuracy in attack. How could he miss this attack?

This guy was thinking too much!

This was Zhou Guangyi's instant judgment. He hadn't planned to dodge this attack, but Fang Rui thought he would, so he aimed slightly elsewhere as a predictive attack, making the attack miss?

No! It wasn't like that!

The instant the Qi Bullet passed him, Zhou Guangyi realized it. Even if it was supposed to be a predictive attack, there was no way it should have that trajectory, and given his Golden Right Hand, there was no way he picked the wrong position by accident. This was...

It didn't have much power, but the Qi Bullet was a flashing white mass, and as it passed by his face, it filled Zhou Guangyi's camera with that flashing whiteness.

This guy wanted to make this effect!

Zhou Guangyi finally realized it, but it was too late...

He couldn't see Boundless Sea's movements, only guess at them, and in the end he couldn't escape the evil claws of this master of playing dirty. This time, the Golden Right Hand's attack was extremely accurate. Boundless Sea thrust two pointed fingers towards Cold Seasons, and the qi between his fingers was forced into Cold Seasons's body.

Qi Master Level 75 skill, Pulse Break.

There were many attacks where the goal wasn't to damage the target's health, but the target's stats.

Decrease vitality, decrease strength, decrease intelligence, decrease spirit. With a successful Pulse Break, the corresponding attribute of the target would be decreased. The Pulse Break that Boundless Sea used here was Break Intelligence, which decreased Cold Seasons's intelligence stat.

Decreasing intelligence affected the target's magic attack, magic defense, and total mana.

An Assassin didn't rely on magic attacks, and the class's magic defense wasn't particularly good either. After being hit by this decreased intelligence, his magic defense became even more flimsy. And a Qi Master mostly dealt magic damage. This was obviously the effect that Fang Rui wanted.

After that attack finished, another immediately followed. A palm landed on Cold Seasons's body, a Qi Blast, and the qi was forced into Cold Seasons's body. There were no flashing effects, but the equipment on Cold Seasons's body suddenly looked like it was malfunctioning, and Cold Seasons's health slid down at an extreme rate. When a Qi Master dealt damage, it was just that quiet and incredible.

The combination of a Level 75 and a Level 70 effect instantly stole away a quarter of Cold Seasons's health. Cold Seasons was ultimately sent flying by the Qi Blast, but after he got up, he saw that Fang Rui hadn't controlled Boundless Sea to chase him over here.

"Hurry and get up, victory still hasn't been decided!" Fang Rui, filled with righteousness, continued to talk in the chat…